<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Additional options on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/</link><description>Recent content in Additional options on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Certificate Transparency Monitoring</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/certificate-transparency-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/certificate-transparency-monitoring/</guid><description>Certificate Transparency MonitoringCertificate Transparency Monitoring sends you emails when certificates — including backup certificates — are issued for your domain. This feature is in public beta and is opt-in. If you use a shared certificate, you may receive notifications for domains or subdomains that do not belong to you. &amp;#8203;​ Overview Every website must have a certificate to be trusted by major browsers. A certificate is a proof of identity — it says that you are who you say you are.</description></item><item><title>HTTP Strict Transport Security (HSTS)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/http-strict-transport-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/http-strict-transport-security/</guid><description>HTTP Strict Transport Security (HSTS)HSTS protects HTTPS web servers from downgrade attacks. These attacks redirect web browsers from an HTTPS web server to an attacker-controlled server, allowing bad actors to compromise user data and cookies. HSTS adds an HTTP header that directs compliant web browsers to:
Transform HTTP links to HTTPS links Prevent users from bypassing SSL browser warnings Before enabling HSTS, review the requirements.
For more background information on HSTS, see the introductory blog post External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>Certificate Signing Requests (CSRs)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/certificate-signing-requests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/certificate-signing-requests/</guid><description>Certificate Signing Requests (CSRs)Generate a Certificate Signing Request (CSR) to get a custom certificate from the Certificate Authority (CA) of your choice while maintaining control of the private key on Cloudflare. The private key associated with the CSR will be generated by Cloudflare and will never leave our network. A CSR contains information about your domain: your organization name and address, the common name (domain name), and Subject Alternative Names (SANs).</description></item><item><title>TLS 1.3</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/tls-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/tls-13/</guid><description>TLS 1.3TLS 1.3 enables the latest version of the TLS protocol (when supported) for improved security and performance. &amp;#8203;​ What is TLS 1.3? TLS 1.3 is the newest, fastest, and most secure version of the TLS protocol. SSL/TLS is the protocol that encrypts communication between users and your website. When web traffic is encrypted with TLS, users will see the green padlock in their browser window.
By turning on the TLS 1.</description></item><item><title>Minimum TLS Version</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/minimum-tls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/minimum-tls/</guid><description>Minimum TLS VersionTransport Layer Security (TLS) guarantees encrypted communications between a client and a web server via HTTPS. It replaces the now deprecated Secured Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. When web traffic is encrypted with TLS, users see a green padlock in their browser window, near the URL box.
Minimum TLS Version only allows HTTPS connections from visitors that support the selected TLS protocol version or newer. For example, if TLS 1.</description></item><item><title>Automatic HTTPS Rewrites</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/automatic-https-rewrites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/automatic-https-rewrites/</guid><description>Automatic HTTPS RewritesAutomatic HTTPS Rewrites prevents end users from seeing &amp;ldquo;mixed content&amp;rdquo; errors by rewriting URLs from http to https for resources or links on your web site that can be served with HTTPS. &amp;#8203;​ Availability Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability Yes Yes Yes Yes &amp;#8203;​ Additional details If your site contains links or references to HTTP URLs that are also available securely via HTTPS, Automatic HTTPS Rewrites can help.</description></item><item><title>Total TLS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/total-tls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/total-tls/</guid><description>Total TLSTotal TLS allows Cloudflare to issue individual certificates for every proxied hostname. These certificates will protect proxied hostnames not covered by Universal certificates. When issued, these certificates will have a type of Advanced - Total TLS.
When you enable Total TLS, Cloudflare will also show a warning on proxied DNS records that are not covered by a TLS certificate.
&amp;#8203;​ Availability Total TLS is available for domains that have purchased Advanced Certificate Manager and are currently using a full DNS setup.</description></item><item><title>Always Use HTTPS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/always-use-https/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/always-use-https/</guid><description>Always Use HTTPSAlways Use HTTPS redirects all http requests to https for all subdomains and hosts in your application. Cloudflare recommends not performing redirects at your origin web server, as this can cause redirect loop errors.
&amp;#8203;​ Availability Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability Yes Yes Yes Yes &amp;#8203;​ Encrypt all visitor traffic To redirect traffic for all subdomains and hosts in your application, you can enable Always Use HTTPS.</description></item><item><title>Opportunistic Encryption</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/opportunistic-encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/additional-options/opportunistic-encryption/</guid><description>Opportunistic EncryptionOpportunistic Encryption allows browsers to access HTTP URIs over an encrypted TLS channel. It&amp;rsquo;s not a substitute for HTTPS, but provides additional security for otherwise vulnerable requests. Use HTTPS when both strong encryption and authentication are required. HTTP Opportunistic Encryption provides a means of enabling TLS when needed for other protocols such as HTTP/2. It does not provide the same indications of security as HTTPS (the green lock icon in most browser address bars).</description></item></channel></rss>