<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workers Sites on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/</link><description>Recent content in Workers Sites on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Start from existing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/start-from-existing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/start-from-existing/</guid><description>Deploy an existing static site Cloudflare PagesConsider using Cloudflare Pages for hosting static applications instead of Workers Sites. Workers Sites require Wrangler External link icon Open external link — make sure to use the latest version.
To deploy a pre-existing static site project, start with a pre-generated site. Workers Sites works with all static site generators, for example:
Hugo External link icon Open external link Gatsby External link icon Open external link , requires Node Jekyll External link icon Open external link , requires Ruby Eleventy External link icon Open external link , requires Node WordPress External link icon Open external link (refer to the tutorial on deploying static WordPress sites with Pages) &amp;#8203;​ Getting started Run the wrangler init command in the root of your project’s directory to generate a basic Worker:</description></item><item><title>Start from scratch</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/start-from-scratch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/start-from-scratch/</guid><description>Start a Workers Sites project from scratch Cloudflare PagesConsider using Cloudflare Pages for hosting static applications instead of Workers Sites. This guide shows how to quickly start a new Workers Sites project from scratch.
&amp;#8203;​ Getting started Ensure you have the latest version of git External link icon Open external link and Node.js External link icon Open external link installed.
In your terminal, clone the worker-sites-template starter repository. The following example creates a project called my-site:</description></item><item><title>Start from worker</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/start-from-worker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/start-from-worker/</guid><description>Add static assets to an existing Workers project Cloudflare PagesConsider using Cloudflare Pages for hosting static applications instead of Workers Sites. Workers Sites require Wrangler External link icon Open external link — make sure to use the latest version.
If you have a pre-existing Worker project, you can use Workers Sites to serve static assets to the Worker.
&amp;#8203;​ Getting started Create a directory that will contain the assets in the root of your project (for example, .</description></item><item><title>Workers Sites configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/sites/configuration/</guid><description>Workers Sites configurationWorkers Sites require the latest version of Wrangler External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Commands wrangler generate proj --site
Creates a project with a Worker serving a generic HTML file and favicon with the directory structure:
├── public # files to serve | ├── favicon.ico | └── index.html ├── workers-site | ├── index.js # Workers script that serves the assets | ├── package-lock.json | └── package.</description></item></channel></rss>