<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access Waiting Room</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/waiting-room-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/waiting-room-dashboard/</guid><description>Access Waiting RoomUse Cloudflare Waiting Room to create a holding area where users can queue to access a high-traffic area of your enterprise website. For an introduction, refer to the Overview page.
To access Waiting Room on the Cloudflare dashboard:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your application. Click Traffic &amp;gt; Waiting Rooms. Use the dashboard to create, edit, update, and delete waiting rooms.</description></item><item><title>Create a waiting room</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/create-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/create-waiting-room/</guid><description>Create a waiting roomA waiting room can be created from the dashboard or via API.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a waiting room from the dashboard For additional context on creating a waiting room, refer to Get started. Within your application, go to Traffic &amp;gt; Waiting Rooms. Select Create. Customize the settings for your waiting room. For additional guidance refer to Best practices. Select Next. If you can customize your waiting room, update the HTML and CSS as needed.</description></item><item><title>Customize a waiting room</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/customize-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/customize-waiting-room/</guid><description>Customize a waiting roomA waiting room can be customized from the dashboard or via API.
&amp;#8203;​ Customize a waiting room from the dashboard To design and preview the appearance of a waiting room, select the Customization tab in the Create Waiting Room page.
Cloudflare offers options to customize the appearance of your waiting room:
Default waiting room: An unbranded waiting room that displays an estimated waiting time to visitors. Select a language for your default waiting room page.</description></item><item><title>Monitor waiting room status</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/monitor-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/monitor-waiting-room/</guid><description>Monitor waiting room statusYou can monitor the status of your waiting rooms using the dashboard or the API.
Note that the Total active users and Queued users shown in the dashboard, as well as through API endpoints are estimates. That data corresponding to each of these metrics is cached for around 30 seconds after the time it takes to be synced from all data centers globally. Therefore, the status will range between 20-50 seconds in the past, depending on the exact moment the data was queried, aggregated, as well as the age of the cache.</description></item><item><title>Control waiting room traffic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/control-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/control-waiting-room/</guid><description>Control waiting room trafficTo change whether and how traffic reaches a waiting room, update the values for Enabled, Queue All, and Queueing Method on your waiting room.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable a waiting room To enable a waiting room:
Go to Traffic &amp;gt; Waiting Rooms. On a waiting room, set Enabled to On. &amp;#8203;​ Queue options By default, an active waiting room puts visitors in a queue when traffic approaches the target thresholds defined in Total active users and New users per minute.</description></item><item><title>Edit and delete waiting rooms</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/edit-delete-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/edit-delete-waiting-room/</guid><description>Edit and delete waiting roomsYou can manage your waiting rooms using the Waiting Room dashboard or the API.
For details about updating an active waiting room, refer to Best practices. &amp;#8203;​ Using the dashboard &amp;#8203;​ Edit a waiting room In your application, go to Traffic &amp;gt; Waiting Rooms. On a record, click Edit. Click Settings. Edit the settings. For a description of settings, refer to Configuration settings. Click Next. If you have access to customized templates, you could also adjust the template.</description></item><item><title>Get JSON response for mobile and other non-browser traffic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/json-response/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/json-response/</guid><description>Get JSON response for mobile and other non-browser trafficIf you need to manage traffic in a non-browser environment such as a mobile app or web app, Cloudflare provides a JSON-friendly waiting room that can be consumed via your API endpoints:
When a user is queued, we return our own JSON response. When a user leaves the waiting room, we forward the request to your origin server and return the response from your origin server (be it JSON, XML, an HTML page, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>