<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Certificate Management on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/security/certificate-management/</link><description>Recent content in Certificate Management on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/security/certificate-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TLS Management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/security/certificate-management/enforce-mtls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/security/certificate-management/enforce-mtls/</guid><description>TLS Settings — Cloudflare for SaaS Mutual TLS (mTLS) External link icon Open external link adds an extra layer of protection to application connections by validating certificates on the server and the client. When building a SaaS application, you may want to enforce mTLS to protect sensitive endpoints related to payment processing, database updates, and more.
Minimum TLS Version allows you to choose a cryptographic standard per custom hostname. Cloudflare recommends TLS 1.</description></item><item><title>Webhook definitions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/security/certificate-management/webhook-definitions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/security/certificate-management/webhook-definitions/</guid><description>Webhook data definitionsWhen you create a webhook notification for SSL for SaaS Custom Hostnames, you may want to automate responses to specific events (certificate issuance, failed validation, etc.).
The following section details the data Cloudflare sends to a webhook destination.
&amp;#8203;​ Certificate validation Before a Certificate Authority will issue a certificate for a domain, the requestor must prove they have control over that domain. This process is known as domain control validation (DCV).</description></item></channel></rss>