<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/load-balancing-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/load-balancing-analytics/</guid><description>Load balancing analyticsUsing load balancing analytics, you can:
Evaluate traffic flow. Assess the health status of origin servers in your pools. Review changes in pools and pool health over time. Load balancing analytics are only available to customers on paid plans (Pro, Business, and Enterprise). &amp;#8203;​ Dashboard Analytics &amp;#8203;​ Overview metrics To view Overview metrics for your load balancer, go to Traffic &amp;gt; Load Balancing Analytics.
These metrics show the number of requests routed to specific pools within a load balancer, helping you:</description></item><item><title>Common load balancer configurations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/common-configurations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/common-configurations/</guid><description>Common load balancer configurations &amp;#8203;​ Active - Passive Failover An active-passive failover sends traffic to the servers in your active pool until a failure threshold (configurable) is reached. At the point of failure, your load balancer then redirects traffic to the passive pool.
This setup ensures uninterrupted service and helps with planned outtages, but it might lead to slower traffic overall.
To set up a load balancer with active-passive failover:</description></item><item><title>DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/dns-records/</guid><description>DNS records for load balancingWhen you create a load balancer, Cloudflare automatically creates an LB DNS record for the specified Hostname. This functionality allows you to use a hostname with or without an existing DNS record.
&amp;#8203;​ Supported records For customers on non-Enterprise plans, Cloudflare supports load balancing for A, AAAA, and CNAME records.
For customers on Enterprise plans, Cloudflare supports load balancing for A, AAAA, CNAME, MX, and SRV records.</description></item><item><title>Regions API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/region-mapping-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/region-mapping-api/</guid><description>Load Balancing Regions APICloudflare’s Load Balancing Regions API has several uses:
Identify which countries/areas (states/provinces in the case of the U.S. and Canada) are part of a specific Cloudflare Load Balancer region. Identify the Cloudflare Load Balancer region for a particular country/area (states/provinces in the case of the U.S. and Canada). The Region API uses 2-letter ISO-3166-1 alpha-2 codes External link icon Open external link for countries/areas and, in the case of the U.</description></item></channel></rss>