<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Register a new domain</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/register-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/register-domain/</guid><description>Register a new domain &amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites and restrictions Cloudflare Registrar is only available for customers that use Cloudflare as their authoritative DNS provider (also known as a full setup). Cloudflare Registrar does not currently support internationalized domain names (IDNs), also known as Unicode. If you have an unverified account email address, you will not be able to transfer or register domains. Verify your account email address before proceeding. &amp;#8203;​ How to register a new domain If you are registering a .</description></item><item><title>Transfer your domain to Cloudflare</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/transfer-domain-to-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/transfer-domain-to-cloudflare/</guid><description>Transfer your domain to CloudflareTransferring your domain to Cloudflare tells your registry that a different registrar can now set those authoritative records for you. The relationship is based on trust. Registries only trust one registrar at any given time to make changes on your behalf.
Transferring a domain to a new registrar informs the registry that they should instead trust that new registrar to modify information. The process requires some action steps at your new and previous registrar.</description></item><item><title>Transfer a .UK domain to Cloudflare</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/transfer-uk-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/transfer-uk-domain/</guid><description>Transfer a .UK domain to Cloudflare &amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites The domain must not be locked or suspended. There must be an active zone for the domain in your Cloudflare account. The domain must have Cloudflare nameservers. The domain must not be expiring within the next 10 days. &amp;#8203;​ How to transfer a .UK domain to Cloudflare Cloudflare currently supports the transfer of .uk, co.uk, org.uk, and me.uk domains. To transfer a .</description></item><item><title>WHOIS redaction</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/whois-redaction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/get-started/whois-redaction/</guid><description>WHOIS redactionCloudflare Registrar provides personal data redaction on WHOIS information, if permitted by the registry.
WHOIS is a standard for publishing the contact and nameserver information for all registered domains. Each registrar maintains their own WHOIS service. Anyone can query the registrar’s WHOIS service to reveal the data behind a given domain.
However, broadcasting the registrant contact information via the WHOIS service can cause spam mail to be delivered to your personal addresses.</description></item></channel></rss>