<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DNS policies on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/</link><description>Recent content in DNS policies on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/common-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/common-policies/</guid><description>Common DNS policiesThe following policies are commonly used to secure DNS traffic.
&amp;#8203;​ Block content categories Block content categories which go against your organization’s acceptable use policy.
Selector Operator Value Action Content categories in Adult Themes, Gambling Block &amp;#8203;​ Block applications Block content categories which go against your organization’s acceptable use policy.
Selector Operator Value Action Application in Netflix Block After 7 days, view your Shadow IT analytics and block additional applications based on what your users are accessing.</description></item><item><title>Test DNS filtering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/test-dns-filtering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/test-dns-filtering/</guid><description>Test DNS filteringThis section covers how to validate your Gateway DNS configuration.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before you start, make sure you are connected to a network that is associated with the DNS location where the policy is applied.
&amp;#8203;​ Test a DNS policy Once you have created a DNS policy to block a domain, you can use either dig or nslookup to see if the policy is working as intended.</description></item><item><title>Scheduled DNS policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/scheduled-dns-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/dns-policies/scheduled-dns-policies/</guid><description>Scheduled DNS policiesCloudflare Gateway allows you to configure any DNS policy to activate or deactivate on a regular time interval.
By default, Gateway policies are unscheduled and apply at all times. You can use the Gateway Rules API to create a new DNS policy with a schedule or add a schedule to an existing policy. To schedule a policy, send a POST or PUT request with the schedule parameter set to your desired days of the week, times of day, and an optional time zone.</description></item></channel></rss>