<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Confirm DNS Records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/confirm-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/confirm-dns-records/</guid><description> Confirm DNS recordsBefore you change your nameserver, confirm your DNS records are displaying correctly.
Open your Cloudflare dashboard and select your account. Select your domain from the dropdown. Select the DNS &amp;gt; Records tile. DNS management for your domain displays. To add a record, select Add record. To edit an existing record, select Edit for the appropriate record. After making your changes, select Save.</description></item><item><title>Change nameservers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/change-nameservers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/change-nameservers/</guid><description>Change nameserversUpdating your domain to use Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s nameservers is a critical step to ensure Cloudflare can optimize and protect your site. Nameservers are your primary DNS controller and identify the location of your domain on the Internet.
Domain registrars can take up to 24 hours to process the nameserver updates. You will receive an email from Cloudflare once your site is activated.
&amp;#8203;​ Lookup domain name registration Visit WHOIS External link icon Open external link to look up your domain name registration.</description></item><item><title>Activate the Cloudflare WordPress plugin</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/activate-cf-wp-plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/activate-cf-wp-plugin/</guid><description>Activate the Cloudflare WordPress pluginFor users on the free plan, be sure to purchase APO before installing the WordPress plugin. For users on a Pro plan or higher, continue to Install and activate the Cloudflare WordPress plugin.
&amp;#8203;​ Purchase APO Open your Cloudflare dashboard. Select the Speed tile and locate the Optimized Delivery section. From Automatic Platform Optimization for WordPress, select Purchase. Enter your payment information and select Confirm payment.</description></item><item><title>Verify APO works</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/verify-apo-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/automatic-platform-optimization/get-started/verify-apo-works/</guid><description>Verify APO worksYou can check whether or not APO is working by verifying APO headers are present. When APO is working, three headers are present: CF-Cache-Status, cf-apo-via, cf-edge-cache.
Visit Uptrends.com External link icon Open external link . In the text field, enter the URL for your WordPress homepage including the https://www.. Select Start test. The Response Headers table displays. Locate the three header responses and their description. APO is working correctly when the headers exactly match the headers below.</description></item></channel></rss>