<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reporting on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/</link><description>Recent content in Reporting on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mail Trace</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/mailtrace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/mailtrace/</guid><description>Mail TraceMail Trace allows you to search through and view all emails that have been processed by Area 1, whether or not they were marked with a detection disposition.
You would commonly use Mail Trace to review whether and when an email passed through Area 1, as well as what Area 1 communicated to the following mail provider.
To only review emails marked with a disposition, use Detection search. &amp;#8203;​ Use Mail Trace To access Mail Trace in the dashboard:</description></item><item><title>Phish reports</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/phish-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/phish-reports/</guid><description>Phish reportsArea 1 automatically generates phish reports to provide an overview of your email traffic.
&amp;#8203;​ In the dashboard To view phishing reports in the Area 1 dashboard, log in External link icon Open external link and explore the non-Settings areas of the Area 1 dashboard (Home, Email, Web, and Detection Details).
&amp;#8203;​ Through an email subscription The same reports that are visible through the dashboard can also be delivered through an email.</description></item><item><title>SIEM integration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/siem-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reporting/siem-integration/</guid><description>SIEM integrationWith a bit of configuration, you can also bring Area 1 data into your SIEM tools to view message-level information outside of the dashboard and create your own custom reports.
&amp;#8203;​ Connect a SIEM tool &amp;#8203;​ Step 1 - Set up your SIEM tool For help setting up the proper configuration in your SIEM tool, refer to the following guides:
Splunk Integration Guide (PDF) Sumologic Integration Guide (PDF) &amp;#8203;​ Step 2 - Create a webhook To create a webhook in Area 1 and send data into a SIEM tool:</description></item></channel></rss>