<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Main components</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/about/components/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/about/components/</guid><description>Main components
&amp;#8203;​ Autonomous Edge The Cloudflare Autonomous Edge is powered by the denial-of-service daemon (dosd), which is a home-grown software-defined system. A dosd instance runs in every single server in every one of Cloudflare’s edge data centers External link icon Open external link around the world. These dosd instances can detect and mitigate DDoS attacks autonomously without requiring centralized consensus. Cloudflare users can configure this system through DDoS Attack Protection managed rulesets.</description></item><item><title>Attack coverage</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/about/attack-coverage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/about/attack-coverage/</guid><description>DDoS attack coverageThe DDoS Attack Protection managed rulesets provide protection against a variety of DDoS attacks across L3/4 (layers 3/4) and L7 of the OSI model. Cloudflare constantly updates these managed rulesets to improve the attack coverage, increase the mitigation consistency, cover new and emerging threats, and ensure cost-efficient mitigations.
Advanced TCP Protection, available to Magic Transit customers, provides additional protection against sophisticated TCP-based DDoS attacks.
As a general guideline, Cloudflare customers are protected up to the layer on which their service operates.</description></item></channel></rss>