<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security Events on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/</link><description>Recent content in Security Events on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free plan</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/free-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/free-plan/</guid><description>Security Events — Free planSecurity Events is available at Security &amp;gt; Events.
&amp;#8203;​ Adjusting displayed data You can apply multiple filters and exclusions to narrow the scope of Security Events and adjust the report duration. Modifying the duration, filters, or exclusions affects the analytics data displayed in the Activity Log.
&amp;#8203;​ Add filters You can adjust the scope of analytics by manually entering filter conditions. Alternatively, select Filter or Exclude to filter by a field value.</description></item><item><title>Paid plans</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/paid-plans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/paid-plans/</guid><description>Security Events — Paid plansSecurity Events is available at Security &amp;gt; Events.
&amp;#8203;​ Adjusting displayed data You can apply multiple filters and exclusions to narrow the scope of Security Events and adjust the report duration. Modifying the duration, filters, or exclusions affects the analytics data displayed on the entire page including the Activity Log and all graphs.
&amp;#8203;​ Add filters You can adjust the scope of analytics by manually entering filter conditions.</description></item><item><title>Additional information</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/additional-information/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/security-events/additional-information/</guid><description>Additional information &amp;#8203;​ Validation checks Cloudflare performs a validation check for every request. The Validation component executes prior to all other WAF features like custom rules or WAF Managed Rules. The validation check blocks malformed requests like Shellshock attacks and requests with certain attack patterns in their HTTP headers before any allowlist logic occurs. Actions performed by the Validation component appear in the Activity log associated with the Validation service and without a rule ID.</description></item></channel></rss>