<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private networks on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/</link><description>Recent content in Private networks on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Connect private networks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/connect-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/connect-private-networks/</guid><description>Connect private networksCreating a private network has two components: the server and the client. The server&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure (whether that is a single application, multiple applications, or a network segment) is connected to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge by Cloudflare Tunnel. This is done by running the cloudflared daemon on the server. Simply put, Cloudflare Tunnel is what connects your network to Cloudflare. On the client side, end users connect to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge using the Cloudflare WARP agent.</description></item><item><title>Private hostnames and IPs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/private-hostnames-ips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/private-hostnames-ips/</guid><description>Private hostnames and IPs Traffic handlingWhen the old replica is stopped, it will drop long-lived HTTP requests (for example, Websocket) and TCP connections (for example, SSH). UDP flows will also be dropped, as they are modeled based on timeouts. When the new replica connects, it will handle all new traffic, including new HTTP requests, TCP connections, and UDP flows. Building out a private network has two primary components: the infrastructure side and the client side.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel Virtual Networks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/tunnel-virtual-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/private-net/tunnel-virtual-networks/</guid><description>Tunnel Virtual NetworksCloudflare Tunnel supports the creation and configuration of virtual networks. Tunnel Virtual Networks allow you to manage different private networks which have overlapping IP ranges.
For example, an organization may want to expose two distinct virtual private cloud (VPC) networks which they consider to be “production” and “staging”. However, if the two private networks happened to receive the same RFC1918 IP assignment, there may be two different resources with the same IP address.</description></item></channel></rss>