<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloudflare's data products on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/</link><description>Recent content in Cloudflare's data products on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Cloudflare Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/about-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/about-analytics/</guid><description>About Cloudflare AnalyticsIn an effort to make analytics an ubiquitous component of all Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s products, Cloudflare has implemented, and continues to evolve, several ways in which customers can access and gain insights from Internet properties on Cloudflare.
You can access root-level analytics that give you an overview of metadata related to your Cloudflare account, analytics related to specific properties and products, and the GraphQL API that gives you more control over how you visualize the analytics and log information available on the Cloudflare dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Types of analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/types-of-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/types-of-analytics/</guid><description>Types of analyticsCloudflare Analytics is a comprehensive product that encompasses all metadata generated by the Cloudflare network. You can access these insights through the Cloudflare dashboard. Depending on where in the dashboard you are, it will show you different aspects from the collected metadata.
&amp;#8203;​ Root-level analytics &amp;#8203;​ Account Analytics (beta) Available at the root of your Cloudflare dashboard when you log in, Account Analytics (beta) shows you an overview of traffic for all sites External link icon Open external link on your Cloudflare account, such as requests and bandwidth by country, information related to security, cache, and errors, among others.</description></item></channel></rss>