<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference Architecture on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/reference-architecture/</link><description>Recent content in Reference Architecture on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/reference-architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CDN</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/reference-architecture/cdn-reference-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/reference-architecture/cdn-reference-architecture/</guid><description>Cloudflare CDN Reference Architecture &amp;#8203;​ Overview Every day, users of the Internet enjoy the benefits of performance and reliability provided by content delivery networks External link icon Open external link (CDNs). CDNs have become a must-have to combat latency and a requirement for any major company delivering content to users on the Internet. While providing performance and reliability for customers, CDNs also enable companies to further secure their applications and cut costs.</description></item><item><title>Magic Transit</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/reference-architecture/magic-transit-reference-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/reference-architecture/magic-transit-reference-architecture/</guid><description>Magic Transit Use Cases and Reference Architecture &amp;#8203;​ 1 Introduction The purpose of this document is to describe the key architecture, functionalities, and network deployment options of Cloudflare Magic Transit — a BGP-based DDoS protection and traffic acceleration service for Internet-facing network infrastructure.
&amp;#8203;​ 2 What Is Magic Transit? Protecting network infrastructure from DDoS attacks demands a unique combination of strength and speed. Volumetric attacks can easily overwhelm hardware boxes and their bandwidth-constrained Internet links.</description></item></channel></rss>