<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Device posture on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/</link><description>Recent content in Device posture on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CrowdStrike</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/crowdstrike/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/crowdstrike/</guid><description>CrowdStrikeDevice posture with CrowdStrike requires the CrowdStrike agent and the Cloudflare WARP client to be deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the integration.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up CrowdStrike as a service provider &amp;#8203;​ 1. Get CrowdStrike settings The following CrowdStrike values are needed to set up the CrowdStrike posture check:</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Endpoint Manager</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/microsoft/</guid><description>Microsoft Endpoint ManagerCloudflare Zero Trust can integrate with Microsoft Endpoint Manager and Intune to require that users connect to certain applications from managed devices. Our service-to-service posture check identifies devices based on their serial numbers.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Device posture with Microsoft Endpoint Manager requires:
An Intune license Microsoft Endpoint Manager managing the device Cloudflare WARP client deployed on the device &amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain Microsoft Graph settings The following values are required:</description></item><item><title>Tanium</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/tanium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/tanium/</guid><description>Tanium Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link Any OS supported by Tanium WARP with Gateway All plans Cloudflare Access can use endpoint data from Tanium™ External link icon Open external link to determine if a request should be allowed to reach a protected resource. When users attempt to connect to a resource protected by Access with a Tanium rule, Cloudflare Access will validate the user&amp;rsquo;s identity, and the browser will connect to the Tanium agent before making a decision to grant access.</description></item><item><title>Uptycs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/uptycs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/uptycs/</guid><description>UptycsDevice posture with Uptycs requires that the Uptycs agent and the Cloudflare WARP client are deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the check.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain Uptycs Settings The following Uptycs values are needed to set up the Uptycs posture check:
Client key Client Secret Customer ID To obtain these values:</description></item><item><title>Workspace ONE</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/workspace-one/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/workspace-one/</guid><description>Workspace ONEDevice posture with Workspace ONE requires the Workspace ONE agent and the Cloudflare WARP client to be deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the posture check.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain Workspace ONE Settings The following Workspace ONE values are needed to set up the Workspace ONE posture check:</description></item></channel></rss>