<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Override examples on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/</link><description>Recent content in Override examples on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Set WordPress rules to Block</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/deploy-cmr-wordpress-block/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/deploy-cmr-wordpress-block/</guid><description>Use tag overrides to set WordPress rules to BlockFollow the steps below to create a rule that executes a managed ruleset and defines an override for rules with a specific tag.
Add a rule to a phase entry point ruleset that executes a managed ruleset. Configure a tag override that sets a specified action for all rules with a given tag. The example below uses the Update ruleset operation to perform the two steps in a single PUT request.</description></item><item><title>Enable only Joomla rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/deploy-cmr-joomla-only/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/deploy-cmr-joomla-only/</guid><description>Use category overrides to enable Joomla rulesUse the Rulesets API to configure the execution of a managed ruleset and override its behavior. By default, enabled rules perform the actions defined by the managed ruleset issuer. This example uses overrides to ensure that only rules with a specific tag are enabled.
Follow the steps below to configure the execution of a managed ruleset with two overrides for enabling only the rules tagged with joomla.</description></item><item><title>Enable only selected rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/enable-selected-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/enable-selected-rules/</guid><description>Use rulesets and rule overrides to only enable selected rulesUse a ruleset override and a rule override in a phase entry point ruleset to execute only selected rules in a managed ruleset.
Add a rule to a phase entry point ruleset that executes a managed ruleset. Configure a ruleset override that disables all rules in the managed ruleset. Configure a rule override to set an action for the rules you want to execute.</description></item><item><title>Deploy a managed ruleset with ruleset, tag, and rule overrides</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/override-ruleset-tag-rule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/override-ruleset-tag-rule/</guid><description>Deploy a managed ruleset with ruleset, tag, and rule overridesCustomize the execution of managed rulesets with a combination of ruleset overrides, tag overrides, and rule overrides in your phase entry point ruleset.
Add a rule to a phase entry point ruleset to execute a managed ruleset. Configure a ruleset override that disables all rules in the managed ruleset. Configure a tag override that sets an action for rules with a given tag.</description></item><item><title>Adjust the sensitivity of an HTTP DDoS rule to Low</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/override-ddos-rule-sensitivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-examples/override-ddos-rule-sensitivity/</guid><description>Adjust the sensitivity of a specific HTTP DDoS rule to LowFollow the steps below to override the sensitivity of a specific rule of the Cloudflare HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset.
Add a rule to a phase to deploy the Cloudflare HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset. You only need to deploy this specific ruleset when you wish to define one or more overrides, since it is enabled by default.</description></item></channel></rss>