<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Universal SSL on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/</link><description>Recent content in Universal SSL on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enable Universal SSL certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/enable-universal-ssl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/enable-universal-ssl/</guid><description>Enable Universal SSL certificatesBy default, Cloudflare issues — and renews — free, unshared, publicly trusted SSL certificates to all Cloudflare domains. The process for activating a Universal SSL certificate depends on your domain&amp;rsquo;s DNS setup.
&amp;#8203;​ Full DNS setup For domains on a full setup1, your domain should automatically receive its Universal SSL certificate within 15 minutes to 24 hours of domain activation2.
This certificate will cover your root domain (example.</description></item><item><title>Disable Universal SSL certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/disable-universal-ssl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/disable-universal-ssl/</guid><description>Disable Universal SSL certificatesSome customers may need to manage their own SSL certificates or rely on specific Certificate Authorities.
If you disable your domain&amp;rsquo;s Universal SSL certificate, Cloudflare removes that certificate from our network and will not order or renew any additional Universal SSL certificates.
&amp;#8203;​ Potential errors To avoid errors with your domain, either upload a custom certificate or purchase Advanced Certificate Manager before disabling Universal SSL.
If you disable Universal SSL, you may experience errors with the following scenarios:</description></item><item><title>Limitations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/limitations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/limitations/</guid><description>Limitations for Universal SSLUniversal SSL certificates are limited by the hostnames they cover and the browsers they support.
&amp;#8203;​ Hostname coverage &amp;#8203;​ Full setup Universal SSL certificates only support SSL for the root or first-level subdomains such as example.com and www.example.com. To enable SSL support on second, third, and fourth-level subdomains such as dev.www.example.com or app3.dev.www.example.com, you can:
Purchase Advanced Certificate Manager, to cover more than one level of subdomain, remove Cloudflare branding from the Universal certificate, or adjust the shortest certificate lifespan.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/universal-ssl/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Troubleshooting Universal SSL &amp;#8203;​ Resolve a timed out state If a certificate issuance times out, Cloudflare tells you where in the chain of issuance the timeout occurred: Initializing, Validation, Issuance, Deployment, or Deletion.
To resolve timeout issues, try one or more of the following options:
Change the Proxy status of related DNS records to DNS only (gray-clouded) and wait at least a minute. Then, change the Proxy status back to Proxied (orange-clouded).</description></item></channel></rss>