<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Log the payload of matched rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/</link><description>Recent content in Log the payload of matched rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure payload logging in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/configure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/configure/</guid><description>Configure payload logging for a managed ruleset in the dashboardConfigure payload logging for a ruleset in the ruleset configuration page.
Open Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Managed rules.
To configure payload logging for a ruleset you had already deployed in the WAF, select Edit next to the managed ruleset name.
To deploy a managed ruleset and configure payload logging, select Configure next to the managed ruleset under Managed Rulesets.
At the bottom of the page, select Configure payload logging.</description></item><item><title>View the payload content in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/view/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/view/</guid><description>View the payload content in the dashboardView the content of the matched rule payload in the dashboard by entering your private key.
Open Security &amp;gt; Events.
Under Activity log, expand the details of an event triggered by a rule whose managed ruleset has payload logging enabled.
Under Payload match, select Decrypt payload log.
Enter your private key in the pop-up window and select Decrypt.
The private key is not sent to a Cloudflare server.</description></item><item><title>Configure payload logging via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/configure-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/payload-logging/configure-api/</guid><description>Configure payload logging for a managed ruleset via APIYou can use the Rulesets API External link icon Open external link to configure payload logging for a managed ruleset.
&amp;#8203;​ Configure and enable payload logging To configure:
Use the Update rule in ruleset API method to update the rule that executes the managed ruleset.
In the configuration of the rule that executes the managed ruleset, include a matched_data object in action_parameters to configure payload logging.</description></item></channel></rss>