<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Performance on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/</link><description>Recent content in Performance on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Argo Smart Routing for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/argo-for-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/argo-for-saas/</guid><description>Argo Smart Routing for SaaSArgo Smart Routing uses real-time global network information to route traffic on the fastest possible path across the internet. Regardless of geographic location, this allows Cloudflare to optimize routing to make it faster, more reliable, and more secure. As a SaaS provider, you may want to emphasize the quickest traffic delivery for your end customers. To do so, enable Argo Smart Routing.</description></item><item><title>Cache for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/cache-for-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/cache-for-saas/</guid><description>Cache for SaaSCloudflare makes customer websites faster by storing a copy of the website’s content on the servers of our globally distributed data centers. Content can be either static or dynamic: static content is “cacheable” or eligible for caching, and dynamic content is “uncacheable” or ineligible for caching. The cached copies of content are stored physically closer to users, optimized to be fast, and do not require recomputing.
As a SaaS provider, enabling caching reduces latency on your custom domains.</description></item><item><title>Early Hints for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/early-hints-for-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/performance/early-hints-for-saas/</guid><description>Early Hints for SaaSEarly Hints allows the browser to begin loading resources while the origin server is compiling the full response. This improves webpage’s loading speed for the end user. As a SaaS provider, you may prioritize speed for some of your custom hostnames. Using custom metadata, you can enable Early Hints per custom hostname.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before you can employ Early Hints for SaaS, you need to create a custom hostname.</description></item></channel></rss>