<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keyless SSL on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/</link><description>Recent content in Keyless SSL on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/configuration/</guid><description>Get started with Keyless SSL &amp;#8203;​ Before you begin &amp;#8203;​ Supported platforms Keyless has been tested on amd64 and arm architectures. The key server binary will likely run on all architectures that Go supports. Code support may exist for other CPUs too, but these other architectures have not been tested.
In addition to running on bare metal, the key server should run without issue in a virtualized or containerized environment.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade your key server</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/upgrading-your-key-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/upgrading-your-key-server/</guid><description>Upgrade your key serverTo upgrade your key server:
Back up the contents of /etc/keyless. Update your OS’ package listings, for example, apt-get update or yum update. Upgrade the gokeyless server: Debian/Ubuntu: apt-get upgrade gokeyless RHEL/CentOS: yum install gokeyless Restart the keyless instance: systemd: service gokeyless restart upstart/sysvinit: /etc/init.d/gokeyless restart Confirm that HTTPS connections are working as expected. If you are running a high availability configuration, upgrade one server at a time as new TLS connections will fail to terminate at Cloudflare’s edge without a functioning key server.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/keyless-ssl/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Troubleshooting Keyless SSL &amp;#8203;​ Check the logs To check logs, use a command similar to the following.
systemd: sudo journalctl -f -u gokeyless upstart/sysvinit: sudo tail -f /var/log/gokeyless.log &amp;#8203;​ Enable debug logging To enable debug logging, use a command similar to the following.
$ cd /etc/keyless $ sudo -u keyless gokeyless --loglevel 0 &amp;#8203;​ Browsers are seeing a TLS connection failure after trying to connect Make sure your key server is accessible from outside your network (tcp/2407).</description></item></channel></rss>