<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Best practices on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/</link><description>Recent content in Best practices on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minimal ruleset</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/minimal-ruleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/minimal-ruleset/</guid><description>Minimal suggested rulesetThe suggested minimal ruleset blocks some known common vectors for DDoS attacks and permits all other ESP, TCP, UDP, GRE and ICMP traffic.
This is a suggested list and not an exhaustive list. Review your environment and add more rules as necessary.
&amp;#8203;​ Recommended rules Rule ID: 1 Description: Single rule that blocks all traffic with UDP source ports which are used in attacks or invalid in Magic Transit ingress.</description></item><item><title>Extended ruleset</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/extended-ruleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/extended-ruleset/</guid><description>Extended suggested rulesetIf you are unable to export your current perimeter firewall rules, consider identifying categories of systems or user-groups that reside on your MT prefixes, for example:
Endpoints (user devices) Internal routers Web servers Non-web servers For each item above, consider the requirements in terms of their permitted Internet access. For example, permit what is required for legitimate traffic and block the rest.
&amp;#8203;​ Create lists for using Magic Firewall rules For more information on lists, refer to Use rule lists.</description></item><item><title>Magic Transit egress</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/magic-transit-egress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/best-practices/magic-transit-egress/</guid><description>Magic Transit egressThe suggestions in the Minimal ruleset and Extended ruleset are recommendations for ingress traffic.
For Magic Transit egress traffic, consider the following information:
The Magic Firewall rules will apply to both Magic Transit ingress and egress traffic passing via Cloudflare. Magic Firewall is not stateful for your Magic Transit egress traffic. If you have a Magic Firewall &amp;ldquo;default drop&amp;rdquo; catchall rule for ingress traffic, you will need to add an earlier rule to permit traffic sourced from your Magic Transit prefix with the destination as any to allow outbound egress traffic.</description></item></channel></rss>