<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/about/</guid><description>About Cloudflare RegistrarCloudflare Registrar offers several advantages over other registrars External link icon Open external link , such as domain name registration renewal without markups fees External link icon Open external link . You only pay what is charged by registries and ICANN External link icon Open external link . Cloudflare Registrar also offers additional security features, such as free, one-click activation for Domain Name System Security Extensions (DNSSEC), custom domain protection, and WHOIS redaction.</description></item><item><title>Top Level Domains supported</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/top-level-domains-supported/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/top-level-domains-supported/</guid><description>Top Level Domains supportedCloudflare supports over 200 top-level domains (TLDs)1 and is always evaluating adding new TLDs.
You can find the full list of supported and coming soon TLDs on the TLD policies page External link icon Open external link . If you want to register a .us domain refer to Additional requirements for .US domains.
&amp;#8203;​ Domain availability During your TLD registration process, Cloudflare Registrar will inform you if the TLD you are looking for is available to register.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/faq/</guid><description>FAQBelow you will find answers to our most commonly asked questions. If you cannot find the answer you are looking for, refer to the community page External link icon Open external link to explore more resources.
Domain transfers Domain registrations Billing &amp;#8203;​ Domain transfers &amp;#8203;​ Why did my transfer fail? Domain transfers sometimes fail. Refer to Registrar: troubleshoot stalled domain transfers External link icon Open external link for more information on what might have happened and how to solve the issue.</description></item><item><title>API reference</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>