<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Migration guides on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/migration-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Migration guides on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/migration-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Migrate to new GraphQL nodes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/migration-guides/load-balancing-graphql-nodes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/migration-guides/load-balancing-graphql-nodes/</guid><description>Migrate to new GraphQL nodesAfter 30 September 2021, Cloudflare will make the following changes to the Load Balancing GraphQL schema:
Deprecate nodes: loadBalancingRequestsGroups will be deprecated for loadBalancingRequestsAdaptiveGroups loadBalancingRequests will be deprecated for loadBalancingRequestsAdaptive Deprecate the date field (replace it with the existing datetime field) Add the sampleInterval field &amp;#8203;​ Example query The following example:
Replaces loadBalancingRequestsGroups with loadBalancingRequestsAdaptiveGroups Replaces date with datetime Uses the new sampleInterval field query { viewer { zones(filter: { zoneTag: &amp;#34;your Zone ID&amp;#34; }) { loadBalancingRequestsAdaptiveGroups( filter: { datetime_gt: &amp;#34;2021-06-12T04:00:00Z&amp;#34;, datetime_lt: &amp;#34;2021-06-13T06:00:00Z&amp;#34; } ) { dimensions { datetime coloCode .</description></item><item><title>Health monitor notifications</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/migration-guides/health-monitor-notifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/reference/migration-guides/health-monitor-notifications/</guid><description>Health monitor notificationsCloudflare is migrating the notifications used by load balancing health monitors to use Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s centralized Notifications Service.
&amp;#8203;​ What is changing and why? Cloudflare’s account-level Notifications Service is now the centralized location for most Cloudflare services. This change promotes consistency and streamlined administration, as well as gives you more options for notification delivery such as configuring webhooks or associating multiple pools with the same notification. These new notifications will also be managed at the account level instead of the zone level.</description></item></channel></rss>