<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User management on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/</link><description>Recent content in User management on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access groups</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/groups/</guid><description>Access groups &amp;#8203;​ Definition A group is a set of rules that can be configured once and then quickly applied across many Access applications. You can select a group as a selector in any Zero Trust policy, and all the criteria from the selected group will apply to that application.
Access groups are distinct from groups in your identity provider, like Okta groups. Access groups can contain a mix of individual users, groups from identity providers, and service authentication options like service tokens.</description></item><item><title>Session management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/session-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/session-management/</guid><description>Manage user sessions &amp;#8203;​ Session duration When users log in to an application protected by Access, Access generates two session tokens:
Token Description Storage Global session token Establishes the maximum amount of time for a user’s Access session Your Cloudflare team domain Application token Establishes a session for a specific application The hostname of the application protected When users log in, the global session token will default to the duration of the application token.</description></item><item><title>Seat management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/seat-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/seat-management/</guid><description>Manage user seatsCloudflare Zero Trust subscriptions consist of seats that active users in your account consume. Active users are added to the Zero Trust dashboard through any authentication event.
The amount of user seats available in your Zero Trust account depends on the amount of users you purchase. If you want to increase the number of seats available, you will have to purchase more users. Learn more about adding and removing seats from your account in the Zero Trust FAQ.</description></item><item><title>Short-lived certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/short-lived-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/users/short-lived-certificates/</guid><description>Configure short-lived certificatesCloudflare Access can replace traditional SSH key models with short-lived certificates issued to your users based on the token generated by their Access login. In traditional models, users generate a keypair and commit their public key into an infrastructure management tool, like Salt External link icon Open external link , or otherwise upload it to an administrator. These keys can remain unchanged for months or years.
Cloudflare Access removes the burden on the end user of generating a key, while also improving security of access to infrastructure with ephemeral certificates.</description></item></channel></rss>