<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage accounts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/manage-accounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/manage-accounts/</guid><description>Manage accountsEach customer or team that uses Cloudflare should have their own account. This ensures proper security and access of resources. Each account acts as a container of zones and other resources. Depending on your needs, you may even provision multiple accounts for a single customer or team.
When you create an account with the Tenant API, your Cloudflare user owns that account from creation, ongoing management, and finally deletion.</description></item><item><title>Manage subscriptions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/manage-subscriptions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/manage-subscriptions/</guid><description>Manage subscriptionsOnce your customer has a zone provisioned, you can add zone and account-level subscriptions.
&amp;#8203;​ Zone subscriptions &amp;#8203;​ Create zone subscription To create a zone subscription, send a POST request to the /zones/&amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt;/subscription endpoint and include the following values:
rate_plan object
Contains the zone plan corresponding to what customers would order in the dashboard. For a list of available values, refer to Zone subscriptions. component_values array
Additional services depending on your reseller agreement, such as additional page_rules.</description></item><item><title>Get tenant details</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/get-tenant-details/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/how-to/get-tenant-details/</guid><description>Get tenant detailsA Tenant Admin&amp;rsquo;s unit and membership details will be used for access of resources and all Tenant operations on the API. The unit ID (unit_tag), for example, can be used to create an account on a specific unit.
This is especially useful when a Tenant Admin has multiple units and wants to create an account on a specific unit. All accounts created are associated with the units, each of which can have one or more memberships.</description></item></channel></rss>