<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/</link><description>Recent content in Platform on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Storage options guide</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/storage-objects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/storage-objects/</guid><description>Storage options guideThe Cloudflare Workers platform provides multiple storage options. This guide will inform you on which storage option is appropriate based on your project&amp;rsquo;s use case.
&amp;#8203;​ KV Workers KV is an eventually consistent key-value data store that caches on the edge.
It is ideal for projects that require:
High volumes of reads and/or repeated reads to the same keys. Per-object time-to-live (TTL). Asset storage for websites. To get started with KV:</description></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/pricing/</guid><description>PricingBy default, users have access to the Workers Free plan. The Workers free plan includes limited usage of Workers, Pages Functions and Workers KV. Read more about the Free plan limits.
The Workers Paid plan includes Workers, Pages Functions, Workers KV, and Durable Objects usage for a minimum charge of $5 USD per month for an account. The plan includes increased initial usage allotments, with clear charges for usage that exceeds the base plan.</description></item><item><title>Betas</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/betas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/betas/</guid><description> Beta StatusThese are the betas relevant to Cloudflare Workers.
Product Private Beta Public Beta More Info Email Workers ✅ Blog External link icon Open external link D1 Database ✅ Blog External link icon Open external link Green Compute ✅ Blog External link icon Open external link Pub/Sub ✅ Docs Queues ✅ Docs TCP Workers ✅ Blog External link icon Open external link Workers Analytics Engine ✅ Docs Workers Deployments ✅ Docs</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog &amp;#8203;​ 2022-08-12 A Headers object with the range header can now be used for range within R2GetOptions for the get R2 binding. When headers are used for onlyIf within R2GetOptions for the get R2 binding, they now correctly compare against the second granularity. This allows correctly round-tripping to the browser and back. Additionally, secondsGranularity is now an option that can be passed into options constructed by hand to specify this when constructing outside Headers for the same effect.</description></item><item><title>Compatibility dates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/compatibility-dates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/compatibility-dates/</guid><description>Compatibility datesCloudflare regularly updates the Workers runtime. These updates apply to all Workers globally and should never cause a Worker that is already deployed to stop functioning. Sometimes, though, some changes may be backwards-incompatible. In particular, there might be bugs in the runtime API that existing Workers may inadvertently depend upon. Cloudflare implements bug fixes that new Workers can opt into while existing Workers will continue to see the buggy behavior to prevent breaking deployed Workers.</description></item><item><title>Deploy button</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/deploy-button/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/deploy-button/</guid><description>Deploy button &amp;#8203;​ Background Deploy buttons let you deploy projects to the Workers platform in under five minutes. The deploy buttons use a Worker to deploy to the platform using the Workers GitHub Action External link icon Open external link . You can also make your own deploy buttons for your projects to make sharing your work easier.
Try the deploy button below to deploy a GraphQL server:
External link icon Open external link Refer to deploy.</description></item><item><title>Deployments</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/deployments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/deployments/</guid><description>DeploymentsDeployments are currently in Public Beta. Deployments are an audit log of static historical versions of your Worker. They include the bundled code, configuration, and bindings associated with your Worker at a given point in time. A change to any of these will trigger a new deployment on Cloudflare’s network.
Only one deployment is active at any time. The active deployment is your latest deployment. The active deployment is accessible via any of your configured custom domains, routes, service bindings, schedules, and your *.</description></item><item><title>Environment variables</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/environment-variables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/environment-variables/</guid><description>Environment variablesIn the Workers platform, environment variables, secrets, and KV namespaces are known as bindings. Regardless of type, bindings are always available as global variables within your Worker script.
&amp;#8203;​ Environmental variables with module workers When deploying a Module Worker, any bindings will not be available as global runtime variables. Instead, they are passed to the handler as a parameter – refer to the FetchEvent documentation for further comparisons and examples.</description></item><item><title>Environments</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/environments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/environments/</guid><description>EnvironmentsWe recommend using Deployments in place of Environments. Deployments give you a powerful audit log of changes to your application, and will soon include integrated rollbacks and automated deployment.
We have temporarily disabled the creation of Service Environments while we are improving this feature. Environments made using Wrangler, as described below, are still supported.
&amp;#8203;​ Background Environments are different contexts that your code runs in. The Workers platform allows you to create and manage different environments.</description></item><item><title>Known issues</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/known-issues/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/known-issues/</guid><description>Known issuesBelow are some known bugs and issues to be aware of when using Cloudflare Workers.
&amp;#8203;​ Route specificity When defining route specificity, a trailing /* in your pattern may not act as expected. Consider two different Workers, each deployed to the same zone. Worker A is assigned the example.com/images/* route and Worker B is given the example.com/images* route pattern. With these in place, here are how the following URLs will be resolved:</description></item></channel></rss>