<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>URL normalization on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/</link><description>Recent content in URL normalization on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How it works</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/how-it-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/how-it-works/</guid><description>How URL normalization worksURL normalization modifies separators, encoded elements, and literal bytes in incoming URLs so that they conform to a consistent formatting standard.
For example, consider a firewall rule that blocks requests whose URLs match www.example.com/hello. The rule would not block a request containing an encoded element — www.example.com/%68ello. Normalizing incoming URLs at the edge helps simplify Cloudflare firewall rules expressions that use URLs.
The URL normalization performed according to RFC-3986 External link icon Open external link is as follows:</description></item><item><title>Configure in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/manage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/manage/</guid><description>Configure URL normalization in the dashboardUse the Rules app in the Cloudflare dashboard to define URL normalization settings.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and website.
Go to Rules &amp;gt; Settings.
Under Configure Normalization, configure the available URL normalization settings.</description></item><item><title>Available settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/normalization/settings/</guid><description>URL normalization settingsThe Cloudflare dashboard provides the following settings to manage URL normalization:
Normalization type (default: RFC-3986)
Selects the type of normalization to perform:
RFC-3986 – Applies URL normalization strictly according to RFC-3986 External link icon Open external link .
Cloudflare – In addition to what is defined in RFC-3986, applies the following URL normalization techniques:
Normalize back slashes (\) into forward slashes (/). Merge successive forward slashes (for example, // will be normalized to /).</description></item></channel></rss>