<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Investigate on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/</link><description>Recent content in Investigate on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTTP requests</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/http-requests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/http-requests/</guid><description>HTTP requestsWhile in Netflows we can inspect bytes and packets reaching Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge routers, in HTTP requests we are a layer above in the OSI model External link icon Open external link . HTTP requests examines complete HTTP requests from end users that reach websites served by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s CDN External link icon Open external link .
HTTP traffic includes both HTTP and HTTPS traffic coming from end users. Most of the charts in the Adoption and Usage External link icon Open external link section on Radar come from this data source.</description></item><item><title>Netflows</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/netflows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/netflows/</guid><description>Netflows Netflows External link icon Open external link shows network traffic data from end users collected from Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge routers. Netflows&amp;rsquo; data also feeds the Internet traffic change External link icon Open external link chart.
Netflows includes all types of traffic from Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s routers, not just traffic to websites served by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s CDN External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ List of endpoints &amp;#8203;​ Timeseries &amp;#8203;​ Example: filtering by product Besides comparing time series across locations or date ranges (discussed in Make comparisons), we can also examine ALL traffic versus only HTTP traffic using the product filter.</description></item><item><title>Application layer attacks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/application-layer-attacks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/application-layer-attacks/</guid><description>Application layer attacksWhile in HTTP requests you can examine all kinds of web requests, in application layer attacks you have access only to mitigated HTTP requests. These requests can be mitigated by one of several Cloudflare products, like WAF, Cloudflare DDoS Protection, Cloudflare bot solutions and others.
Mitigated trafficMitigated traffic is any HTTP request from an end-user that has a terminating action applied by the Cloudflare platform. These include actions like BLOCK or CHALLENGE in captchas or JavaScript based challenges.</description></item><item><title>DNS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/dns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/dns/</guid><description>DNSAccess aggregated and anonymized DNS queries to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s 1.1.1.1 public resolver service.
&amp;#8203;​ List of endpoints &amp;#8203;​ Top locations &amp;#8203;​ Example: Geographical distribution of google.com versus yandex.ru In the next example, we will request the top originating locations for google.com DNS queries:
curl -X GET &amp;#34;https://api.cloudflare.com/client/v4/radar/dns/top/locations?domain=google.com&amp;amp;dateRange=1d&amp;amp;format=json&amp;amp;limit=2&amp;#34; \ -H &amp;#34;Authorization: Bearer &amp;lt;API_TOKEN&amp;gt;&amp;#34; The response shows that most queries come from the United States and Brazil:
{ &amp;#34;clientCountryAlpha2&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;US&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;clientCountryName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;United States&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;43.</description></item><item><title>Domains ranking</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/domain-ranking-datasets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/domain-ranking-datasets/</guid><description>Domains rankingCloudflare regularly generates a domain ranking based on DNS queries to 1.1.1.1, Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s public DNS resolver. Refer to the blog post External link icon Open external link for a deep dive. In short, Cloudflare generates two types of listings:
An ordered list of the top 100 most popular domains globally and per country. This includes the last 24 hours and is updated daily. An unordered global most popular domains dataset, divided into buckets of the following number of domains: 200, 500, 1,000, 2,000, 5,000, 10,000, 20,000, 50,000, 100,000, 200,000, 500,000, 1,000,000.</description></item><item><title>Network layer attacks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/network-layer-attacks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/network-layer-attacks/</guid><description>Network layer attacksNetwork layer attacks show DDoS External link icon Open external link attack trends at the network layer. These attacks can be split by the network protocol they use: ICMP External link icon Open external link , TCP External link icon Open external link , UDP External link icon Open external link and others.
Unlike what happens in Application Layer Attacks, in network layer attacks location attribution does not use the location associated with the client&amp;rsquo;s IP address.</description></item><item><title>Outages</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/outages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/investigate/outages/</guid><description>Outages Cloudflare Radar Outage Center (CROC) External link icon Open external link provides data on outages occurring around the world.
Refer the blog post External link icon Open external link for more information but, in short, Radar provides the following information:
Location: Where was the outage? ASN: What autonomous system experienced a disruption in connectivity? Type: How broad was the outage? Did connectivity fail nationwide, or at a sub-national level?</description></item></channel></rss>