<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bulk Redirects on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/</link><description>Recent content in Bulk Redirects on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Concepts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/concepts/</guid><description>Bulk Redirect conceptsBulk Redirects involve the following elements:
URL Redirect: A simple object with a source URL, a target URL, a status code, and redirect parameters. URL Redirects are the list items of Bulk Redirect Lists.
Bulk Redirect List: A list, similar to an IP List, containing one or more URL Redirects. To enable all the URL Redirects in a Bulk Redirect List, reference the list in a Bulk Redirect Rule.</description></item><item><title>How it works</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/how-it-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/how-it-works/</guid><description>How Bulk Redirects workFor each incoming request, Cloudflare evaluates all URL Redirects of each Bulk Redirect List that is enabled by a Bulk Redirect Rule.
If there is a match for a URL Redirect according to the URL matching algorithm, the redirect action is performed immediately, according to the URL Redirect configuration parameters. Cloudflare performs no further processing once a redirect action has been executed.
&amp;#8203;​ Matching the source URL of redirects The following URL Redirect parameters control the matching behavior between the request URL and source URLs of the configured (and enabled) URL Redirects:</description></item><item><title>Create in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/create-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/create-dashboard/</guid><description>Create Bulk Redirects in the dashboardTo create Bulk Redirects in the Cloudflare dashboard you must:
Create a Bulk Redirect List. Add URL Redirects to the list created in step 1. Create a Bulk Redirect Rule to enable the URL Redirects in the list. &amp;#8203;​ 1. Create a Bulk Redirect List Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. (Optional) In the new dashboard navigation, expand Manage Account.</description></item><item><title>Create via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/create-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/create-api/</guid><description>Create Bulk Redirects via APITo create Bulk Redirects via API, you must:
Create a Bulk Redirect List via API. Add items (URL Redirects) to the list created in step 1. Create a Bulk Redirect Rule via API, which enables the list created in step 1. The API token used in API requests to manage Bulk Redirects objects (lists, list items, and rules) must have at least the following permissions:</description></item><item><title>Use cases</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/use-cases/</guid><description>Common Bulk Redirect use casesThe following use cases go through example Bulk Redirect Rule configurations and sample request URLs.
&amp;#8203;​ Redirect all requests from one domain to another domain In this example the original domain was replaced with a different domain. All functionality was maintained, except for the HTTP service (port 80) which was discontinued.
Create a Bulk Redirect List with the following URL Redirect:
Source URL: example.com/ Target URL: https://example.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/url-forwarding/bulk-redirects/faq/</guid><description>FAQ — Bulk RedirectsBelow you will find answers to the most commonly asked questions regarding Bulk Redirects.
To troubleshoot runtime errors related to Bulk Redirects, refer to Troubleshooting Cloudflare 10XXX Errors External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ What happens if the same source URL appears in two different Bulk Redirect Lists? In this situation, Cloudflare will use the URL Redirect of the first rule that triggers. This will be determined by the order of the Bulk Redirect Rules enabling each Bulk Redirect List in the http_request_redirect phase entry point ruleset.</description></item></channel></rss>