<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Available settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/available-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/available-settings/</guid><description>Available settingsWhen you use Version Management, you can edit various configuration settings, such as Page Rules, Firewall Rules, and Cache settings.
Generally, you are allowed to edit all zone-level configurations except for the following:
DNS Spectrum Traffic (Load Balancing, Waiting Rooms, Health Checks, and more) Zero Trust and Access policies SSL certificates (though you can test these with a separate staging certificates feature) For the most up-to-date list of these settings, start editing settings within a version in the Cloudflare dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Traffic filters</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/traffic-filters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/traffic-filters/</guid><description>Traffic filtersWhen you create an environment, you specify a traffic filter for that environment. This filter ensures that all traffic reaching the environment - and, by extension, the configuration changes associated with the environment&amp;rsquo;s version - is intentional.
To send traffic to a specific environment, send requests to your zone that match the pattern specified in your filter. These could be characteristics such as Edge Server IP, Cookie, Hostname, or User Agent.</description></item><item><title>Read-only environments</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/read-only-environments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/reference/read-only-environments/</guid><description>Read-only environmentsWhen an environment is read-only, any versions deployed to this environment will permanently become read-only. This setting protects sensitive environments from accidental changes.
For example, Production is a read-only environment by default. This setting prevents another member of your account from accidentally editing the version associated with your live traffic.
For similar reasons, some organizations may make Staging a read-only environment. Otherwise, another member of your account could make changes to a version in Staging after your organization has performed the validation tests prior to promoting to Production.</description></item></channel></rss>