<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/</link><description>Recent content in Platform on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Authentication and authorization</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/authentication-authorization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/authentication-authorization/</guid><description>Authentication and authorizationPub/Sub supports two authentication modes. A broker may allow one or both, but never none as authentication is always required.
Mode Details TOKEN Accepts a Client ID and a password (represented by a signed JSON Web Token) in the CONNECT packet. The MQTT User Name field is optional. If provided, it must match the Client ID. MTLS Not yet supported. Accepts an mTLS keypair (TLS client credentials) scoped to that broker.</description></item><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/limits/</guid><description>LimitsThe table lists limits that apply to Pub/Sub brokers and clients during the beta release.
These limits are subject to change and many will increase over time. Item Limit Notes Namespaces per Account 1 The maximum number of namespaces allowed on an account. Users may be able to create multiple namespaces in the future. Brokers per Namespace 10 Can eventually be increased. Subscribers per topic 1000 The maximum number of subscribers per MQTT topic.</description></item><item><title>MQTT compatibility</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/mqtt-compatibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pub-sub/platform/mqtt-compatibility/</guid><description>MQTT compatibilityPub/Sub will continue to expand support for MQTT protocol features during the beta period. The documentation will be updated to reflect the expanded features, so check these docs periodically. Pub/Sub supports the core parts of the MQTT v5.0 specification External link icon Open external link , and any MQTT v5.0 compatible client should be able to connect to a Pub/Sub Broker.
MQTT is one of the most pervasive “messaging protocols” deployed today.</description></item></channel></rss>