<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/</link><description>Recent content in Setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add a site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/add-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/add-site/</guid><description>Add site to CloudflareWhen you add a site to Cloudflare, you need to create a new domain within Cloudflare and then perform additional steps to activate that domain.
These instructions are tailored to customers using a full setup for Cloudflare DNS (the most common configuration). If you are using a partial setup or secondary setup, your setup process will be different. &amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites To use Cloudflare, you need to own a domain (example.</description></item><item><title>Minimize downtime</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/minimize-downtime/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/minimize-downtime/</guid><description>Minimize downtimeWhen you add your domain to Cloudflare, it may experience a brief period of downtime due to certificate issuance, misconfigured Cloudflare settings, or limitations at your origin server.
&amp;#8203;​ Step 1 — Update and review DNS records Before activating your domain on Cloudflare (exact steps depend on your DNS setup), review the DNS records in your Cloudflare account.
&amp;#8203;​ Start with unproxied records With a new domain, make sure all your DNS records have a proxy status of DNS-only.</description></item><item><title>Allow Cloudflare IP addresses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/allow-cloudflare-ip-addresses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/setup/allow-cloudflare-ip-addresses/</guid><description>Allow Cloudflare IP addressesBecause of how Cloudflare works, all traffic to proxied DNS records passes through Cloudflare before reaching your origin server. This means that your origin server will stop receiving traffic from individual visitor IP addresses and instead receive traffic from Cloudflare IP addresses External link icon Open external link , which are shared by all proxied hostnames.
This setup can cause issues if your origin server blocks or rate limits connections from Cloudflare IP addresses.</description></item></channel></rss>