<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/settings/</guid><description>Configuration settings &amp;#8203;​ CSP reporting endpoint When enabled, Page Shield uses a Content Security Policy (CSP) report-only HTTP header to gather information about all the scripts running on your application.
By default, reports are sent to a Cloudflare-owned endpoint:
https://csp-reporting.cloudflare.com/cdn-cgi/script_monitor/report?&amp;lt;QUERY_STRING&amp;gt; You can change the reporting endpoint so that the CSP reports are sent to the same hostname:
&amp;lt;YOUR-HOSTNAME&amp;gt;/cdn-cgi/script-monitor/report?&amp;lt;QUERY_STRING&amp;gt; Only available to Enterprise customers with a paid add-on. &amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites for using the same hostname for CSP reports Using the same hostname for CSP reporting may interfere with other Cloudflare products.</description></item><item><title>Statuses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/script-statuses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/script-statuses/</guid><description>Script and connection statusesCloudflare classifies scripts and connections (also known as resources) according to the following:
The number of times a script/connection was reported. Whether the script/connection is considered malicious or not. Use Page Shield&amp;rsquo;s dashboards to review the scripts loaded in your domain and the connections they make. For more information, refer to Monitor scripts on your site and Monitor connections made by scripts on your site.
&amp;#8203;​ Available statuses Infrequent: There are less than three reports for the script/connection.</description></item><item><title>Alerts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/alerts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/alerts/</guid><description>Page Shield alertsYou can configure alerts for resources detected in your domain. Refer to Configure Page Shield alerts for instructions.
&amp;#8203;​ New resource alerts Available for Cloudflare customers on a Business or Enterprise plan. Page Shield New Resources Alert: Triggered daily by any new resources detected in your pages. Page Shield New Domain Alert: Triggered hourly by newly detected resources from new host domains. Page Shield New Resource Exceeds Max URL Length Alert: Triggered when a resource URL exceeds the maximum allowed length.</description></item><item><title>CSP HTTP header format</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/csp-header/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/csp-header/</guid><description> CSP HTTP header formatThe format of the Content Security Policy (CSP) report-only HTTP header added by Page Shield is the following:
content-security-policy-report-only: script-src &amp;#39;none&amp;#39;; connect-src &amp;#39;none&amp;#39;; report-uri https://csp-reporting.cloudflare.com/cdn-cgi/script_monitor/report?&amp;lt;QUERY_STRING&amp;gt; If you configured the CSP reporting endpoint to use the same hostname, the HTTP header will have the following format:
content-security-policy-report-only: script-src &amp;#39;none&amp;#39;; connect-src &amp;#39;none&amp;#39;; report-uri &amp;lt;YOUR_HOSTNAME&amp;gt;/cdn-cgi/script_monitor/report?&amp;lt;QUERY_STRING&amp;gt; &amp;#8203;​ Related resources Mozilla Developer Network&amp;rsquo;s (MDN) documentation on Content-Security-Policy-Report-Only External link icon Open external link</description></item><item><title>Page Shield API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/page-shield-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/reference/page-shield-api/</guid><description>Page Shield APIYou can change the Page Shield status and fetch information about the currently monitored scripts and connections using the Page Shield API.
For authentication instructions, refer to Getting Started: Requests in the Cloudflare API documentation.
Refer to API deprecations for details on Page Shield API changes. &amp;#8203;​ Endpoints You can obtain the complete endpoint by appending the Page Shield API endpoints listed below to the Cloudflare API base URL.</description></item></channel></rss>