<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gateway DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/gateway-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/gateway-dns-records/</guid><description>Gateway DNS recordsOnce you create a gateway, Cloudflare automatically creates and adds records to your Cloudflare DNS so your gateway can receive and route traffic appropriately:
Ethereum gateways: Creates a proxied CNAME record pointing your hostname to ethereum.cloudflare.com. IPFS gateways: Creates a proxied CNAME record pointing your hostname to ipfs.cloudflare.com and a TXT record with the value specified for its DNSLink. Polygon gateways: Creates a proxied CNAME record pointing your hostname to polygon.</description></item><item><title>Gateway status</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/gateway-status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/gateway-status/</guid><description> Gateway statusOnce you create a gateway, it can have one of several statuses.
Status Definition Active The DNS records for your gateway have been created and are functioning correctly. Pending Your Web3 gateway is in the process of becoming Active. Deleting Your Web3 gateway is being deleted. Error The DNS records for your gateway are misconfigured or do not exist. To fix, try refreshing the gateway.</description></item><item><title>Legacy gateway migration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/migration-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/migration-guide/</guid><description>Legacy gateway migrationAs announced in our blog post External link icon Open external link , Cloudflare is deprecating legacy hostnames that point to our public gateway endpoints at cloudflare-eth.com and cloudflare-ipfs.com.
If you created a hostname pointing to these gateways during the private beta External link icon Open external link , you should migrate to use our new Web3 gateways to avoid a disruption in service.
&amp;#8203;​ Migration guide The migration is a simple process.</description></item><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/reference/limits/</guid><description>LimitsThe following limits apply to users of the Cloudflare Web3 Gateways.
&amp;#8203;​ IPFS Gateway The following limits apply to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s IPFS Gateway.
Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability Yes(Usage-based billing) Yes(Usage-based billing) Yes(Usage-based billing) Yes(Usage-based billing) Total gateways 15 15 15 Unlimited Gateway types DNSLink DNSLink DNSLink DNSLink, Universal Gateway Included bandwidth (without additional cost) 50 GB data transfer 50 GB data transfer 50 GB data transfer 100 GB data transfer File size limit None None None None &amp;#8203;​ Ethereum Gateway The following limits apply to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Ethereum Gateway.</description></item></channel></rss>