<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configuring Network Analytics on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/</link><description>Recent content in Configuring Network Analytics on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adjust the time range</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/time-range/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/time-range/</guid><description>Adjust the time range &amp;#8203;​ Using the timeframe drop-down list Use the timeframe drop-down list to change the time range over which Network Analytics displays data. When you select a timeframe, the entire view is updated to reflect your choice.
In Network Analytics v2 dashboard, the range of historical data you can query is 120 days.
When you select Previous 30 minutes, the Network Analytics card will show the data from the last 30 minutes, refreshing every 20 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Adjust the displayed data</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/displayed-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/displayed-data/</guid><description>Adjust the displayed data &amp;#8203;​ Select high-level metric To toggle your view of the data, click the Total packet rate or Total bit rate side panels.
The selected metric will determine the base units (packets or bits) used in the several analytics panels displayed in the dashboard.
&amp;#8203;​ Select a dimension Under Packets summary or Bits summary, select one of the available dimensions to view the data along that dimension.</description></item><item><title>Share and export data</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/share-export/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/network-analytics/configure/share-export/</guid><description>Share and export data &amp;#8203;​ Share Network Analytics filters When you add filters and specify a time range in the Network Analytics page, the URL changes to reflect those parameters.
To share your view of the data, copy the URL and send it to other users so that they can work with the same view.
&amp;#8203;​ Export activity log data You can export up to 100 raw events from the Activity log at a time.</description></item></channel></rss>