<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/general-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/general-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
General FAQ &amp;#8203;​ Once a request has passed through the Cloudflare network, how soon are the logs available? When using Logpush, logs are pushed in batches as soon as possible. For example, if you receive a file at 10:10, the file consists of logs that were processed before 10:10.
When using Logpull, logs become available in approximately one to five minutes. Cloudflare requires that calls to the Logpull API to be for time periods of at least one minute in the past.</description></item><item><title>About Cloudflare Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/about-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/about-analytics/</guid><description>About Cloudflare AnalyticsIn an effort to make analytics an ubiquitous component of all Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s products, Cloudflare has implemented, and continues to evolve, several ways in which customers can access and gain insights from Internet properties on Cloudflare.
You can access root-level analytics that give you an overview of metadata related to your Cloudflare account, analytics related to specific properties and products, and the GraphQL API that gives you more control over how you visualize the analytics and log information available on the Cloudflare dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Access Waiting Room</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/waiting-room-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/how-to/waiting-room-dashboard/</guid><description>Access Waiting RoomUse Cloudflare Waiting Room to create a holding area where users can queue to access a high-traffic area of your enterprise website. For an introduction, refer to the Overview page.
To access Waiting Room on the Cloudflare dashboard:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your application. Click Traffic &amp;gt; Waiting Rooms. Use the dashboard to create, edit, update, and delete waiting rooms.</description></item><item><title>Actions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/actions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/actions/</guid><description>Firewall rules actionsThe action of a firewall rule tells Cloudflare how to handle HTTP requests that have matched the rule expression.
&amp;#8203;​ Supported actions The table below lists the actions available in firewall rules. These actions are listed in order of precedence. If the same request matches two different rules which have the same priority, precedence determines the action to take.
For example, the Allow action takes precedence over the Block action.</description></item><item><title>Activate Polish</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/polish/activate-polish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/polish/activate-polish/</guid><description>Activate PolishImages in the cache must be purged or expired before seeing any changes in Polish settings.
Do not activate Polish and Image Resizing simultaneously. Image Resizing already applies lossy compression, which makes Polish redundant. Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select the account and domain where you want to activate Polish. Select Speed &amp;gt; Optimization. Under Polish, select Lossy or Lossless from the drop-down menu.</description></item><item><title>Adaptive image format</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/serve-images/adaptive-images-format/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/serve-images/adaptive-images-format/</guid><description>Adaptive optimized format deliveryCloudflare Images automatically transcodes uploaded PNG, JPEG and GIF files to the more efficient AVIF and WebP formats. This happens whenever the customer browser supports them. If the browser does not support AVIF, Cloudflare Images will fall back to WebP. If there is no support for WebP, then Cloudflare Images will serve compressed files in the original format.
Uploaded SVG files are served as sanitized SVGs.</description></item><item><title>Add a third-party tool</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/add-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/add-tool/</guid><description>Add a third-party toolYou can add new third-party tools and load them into your website through the Cloudflare dashboard. If the tool you are adding needs to start actions different from the default Pageview trigger, it is recommended that you create the triggers you need first.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain. Select Zaraz &amp;gt; Tools Configuration &amp;gt; Third-party tools.</description></item><item><title>Add rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/how-to/add-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/how-to/add-rules/</guid><description>RulesYou can check for an existing root ruleset from the dashboard or via the Account rulesets API. If you are a new Magic Transit customer, you may not have a root ruleset created for your account. To view examples for root rulesets, review the Magic Firewall Terraform documentation External link icon Open external link .
By default, you can create a maximum of 100 rules. We recommend you create lists of IP addresses to reference within rules to streamline rule management.</description></item><item><title>Aggregation intervals</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/aggregation-intervals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/aggregation-intervals/</guid><description>Aggregation intervalsAggregation intervals allow you to return data in a specified interval (or frequency). If no interval is defined, data will be returned in the default aggregation interval (or frequency). As a general principle, the longer the date range, the bigger the aggregation interval.
For example, when requesting one day of data, the default aggregation interval is 15 minutes. When requesting more than one month of data, the default is one day.</description></item><item><title>Allowed patterns</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/lists/allowed-patterns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/lists/allowed-patterns/</guid><description>Allowed patternsWhen you set up allowed patterns, Cloudflare Area 1 email security exempts messages that match certain patterns from normal detection scanning.
&amp;#8203;​ Add an allowed pattern To create a new allowed pattern:
Log in to the Area 1 dashboard External link icon Open external link .
Go to Settings (the gear icon).
On Email Configuration, go to Allow List &amp;gt; Allowed Patterns.
Select + New Pattern.
Enter the pattern information:</description></item></channel></rss>