<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edit a Notification on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/edit-notifications/</link><description>Recent content in Edit a Notification on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/edit-notifications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Edit PagerDuty</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/edit-notifications/edit-pagerduty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/edit-notifications/edit-pagerduty/</guid><description>Edit a PagerDuty connected serviceTo edit which PagerDuty services are connected to your Cloudflare account, you first have to disconnect PagerDuty from Cloudflare, make any changes you need in PagerDuty, and then reconnect it. Be aware that disconnecting PagerDuty will disable notifications being sent to PagerDuty where currently configured. If other delivery destinations (like email) were selected, then those notifications will still be routed as configured. If PagerDuty was the only configured destination, disconnecting PagerDuty may result in a notification with no destination.</description></item><item><title>Edit webhooks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/edit-notifications/edit-webhook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/edit-notifications/edit-webhook/</guid><description>Edit webhooksYou can only edit the name of webhooks and/or delete them.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Go to Notifications. Select Destinations on the left side of your dashboard. In the Webhooks card, select Edit on the webhook you want to edit. Update the webhook&amp;rsquo;s name and select Save. NoteYou can also delete a webhook after selecting Edit. However, it is faster to select Delete in the list of webhooks displayed in the Destinations card.</description></item></channel></rss>