<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Additional configurations on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/</link><description>Recent content in Additional configurations on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WAF Managed Rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/waf-managed-rulesets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/waf-managed-rulesets/</guid><description>Configure WAF Managed RulesThis page provides examples of deploying and configuring WAF Managed Rules in your zone or account using Terraform. It covers the following configurations:
Deploy managed rulesets Configure skip rules Configure payload logging Configure overrides Configure the OWASP paranoia level, score threshold, and action For more information on WAF Managed Rules, refer to Managed Rules in the Cloudflare WAF documentation. For more information on deploying and configuring rulesets using the Rulesets API, refer to Work with managed rulesets in the Ruleset Engine documentation.</description></item><item><title>DDoS managed rulesets</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/ddos-managed-rulesets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/ddos-managed-rulesets/</guid><description>Configure DDoS managed rulesetsThis page provides examples of configuring DDoS managed rulesets in your zone or account using Terraform. It covers the following configurations:
Configure HTTP DDoS Attack Protection Configure Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection DDoS managed rulesets are always enabled. Depending on your Cloudflare services, you may be able to adjust their behavior.
For more information on DDoS managed rulesets, refer to Managed rulesets in the Cloudflare DDoS Protection documentation.</description></item><item><title>Rate limiting rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/rate-limiting-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/rate-limiting-rules/</guid><description>Configure rate limiting rulesThis page provides an example of creating a rate limiting rule in a zone using Terraform.
For more information on rate limiting rules, refer to Rate limiting rules in the Cloudflare WAF documentation.
For more information on configuring the previous version of rate limiting rules in Terraform, refer to the cloudflare_rate_limit resource External link icon Open external link in the Terraform documentation.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a rate limiting rule This example creates a rate limiting rule in zone with ID &amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt; blocking traffic that exceeds the configured rate:</description></item><item><title>WAF custom rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/waf-custom-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/waf-custom-rules/</guid><description>Configure WAF custom rulesThis page provides examples of creating WAF custom rules in a zone or account using Terraform. The examples cover the following scenarios:
Zone-level configurations:
Add a custom rule to a zone Account-level configurations:
Create and deploy a custom ruleset Add a custom rule checking for exposed credentials For more information on custom rules, refer to Custom rules in the Cloudflare WAF documentation.
&amp;#8203;​ Zone-level configurations &amp;#8203;​ Add a custom rule to a zone The following example configures a custom rule in the zone entry point ruleset for the http_request_firewall_custom phase for zone with ID &amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title>Transform Rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/transform-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/additional-configurations/transform-rules/</guid><description>Configure Transform RulesThis page provides examples of creating Transform Rules in a zone using Terraform. The examples cover the following scenarios:
Create a URL Rewrite Rule Create an HTTP Request Header Modification Rule For more information on Transform Rules, refer to Transform Rules.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a URL Rewrite Rule The following example creates a URL Rewrite Rule that rewrites requests for example.com/old-folder to example.com/new-folder:
resource &amp;#34;cloudflare_ruleset&amp;#34; &amp;#34;transform_url_rewrite&amp;#34; { zone_id = &amp;#34;&amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt;&amp;#34; name = &amp;#34;Transform Rule performing a static URL rewrite&amp;#34; description = &amp;#34;&amp;#34; kind = &amp;#34;zone&amp;#34; phase = &amp;#34;http_request_transform&amp;#34; rules { action = &amp;#34;rewrite&amp;#34; action_parameters { uri { path { value = &amp;#34;/new-folder&amp;#34; } } } expression = &amp;#34;(http.</description></item><item><title>Single Redirects</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item><item><title>Configuration Rules</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item><item><title>Origin Rules</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item><item><title>Cache Rules</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>