<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GraphQL Analytics API on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/</link><description>Recent content in GraphQL Analytics API on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Error responses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/errors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/errors/</guid><description>Error responsesThe GraphQL Analytics API is a RESTful API based on HTTPS requests and JSON responses, and will return familiar HTTP status codes (for example, 404, 500, 504). However, in contrast to the common REST approach, a 200 response can contain an error, conforming to the GraphQL specification External link icon Open external link .
All responses contain an errors array, which will be null if there are no errors, and include at least one error object if there was an error.</description></item><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/limits/</guid><description>LimitsCloudflare GraphQL API exposes more than 70 datasets representing products with different configurations and data availability for different zones and accounts plans.
To support this variety of products, Cloudflare GraphQL API has three layers of limits:
global limits user limits node (dataset) limits &amp;#8203;​ Global limits These limits are applied to every query for every plan:
A zone-scoped query can include up to 10 zones An account-scoped query can include only 1 account &amp;#8203;​ User limits Cloudflare GraphQL API limits the number of GraphQL requests each user can send.</description></item><item><title>Sampling</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/sampling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/sampling/</guid><description>Sampling &amp;#8203;​ Overview In a small number of cases, the analytics provided on the Cloudflare dashboard and GraphQL Analytics API are based on a sample — a subset of the dataset. In these cases, Cloudflare Analytics returns an estimate derived from the sampled value. For example, suppose that during an attack the sampling rate is 10% and 5,000 events are sampled. Cloudflare will estimate 50,000 total events (5,000 × 10) and report this value in Analytics.</description></item></channel></rss>