<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Widget types</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/widget-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/widget-types/</guid><description>Widget typesEvery instance of Turnstile belongs to a Turnstile widget. It is configured on a per-widget level. Every widget has a mode, a label, a sitekey, and a secret key.
The 3 modes for Turnstile are Managed, Non-Interactive, and Invisible.
&amp;#8203;​ Managed (recommended) Cloudflare will use information from the visitor to decide if an interactive challenge should be used. If we show an interaction, the user will be prompted to check a box (no images or text to decipher).</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/turnstile-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/turnstile-analytics/</guid><description>Turnstile AnalyticsUsing Turnstile analytics, you can:
Assess the number of challenges issued. Evaluate the challenge solve rate. View the metrics of issued challenges. &amp;#8203;​ View metrics of your widgets Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Go to Turnstile and then navigate to your website to see an overview of its widget metrics. These metrics show changes in the solve rate, widget traffic, and top actions for your website.</description></item><item><title>Rotate secret key</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/rotate-secret-key/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/rotate-secret-key/</guid><description>Rotate the secret keyYou can rotate the secret key using the following steps:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Go to Turnstile. In the widget overview, select Settings &amp;gt; Rotate Secret Key. Configure your website to use the new secret key. The rotation occurs over the course of two hours. During this time, both the old secret key and the new secret key are valid.</description></item><item><title>Domain management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/domain-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/domain-management/</guid><description>Domain managementYou must specify a list of domains when creating a widget. The widget can only be used on these domains and will not work on any other domains. You can use subdomains to restrict the widgets further.
The domain should not contain a scheme http:// or https://, a port 443, or a path /.
Specifying a subdomain is optional.
For example, using the www.example.com value will allow widgets on the following domains:</description></item><item><title>Tooltips</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/tooltips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/reference/tooltips/</guid><description>TooltipsVisitor Solve Rate: The percentage of humans who have seen the widget and completed it. This can be both interactive and non-interactive.
API Solve Rate: The percentage of humans that the website sees who have successfully completed the widget.
Change in Solve Rate: It is expected to be relatively stable over time. A change in the solve rate is an indication of something happening on the website, such as undergoing attacks from bots.</description></item></channel></rss>