<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Other ways to use 1.1.1.1 on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/</link><description>Recent content in Other ways to use 1.1.1.1 on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DNS in Google Sheets</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-in-google-sheets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-in-google-sheets/</guid><description>DNS in Google Sheets &amp;#8203;​ Create a function 1.1.1.1 works directly inside Google Sheets. To get started, create a Google Function External link icon Open external link with the following code:
function NSLookup(type, domain) { if (typeof type == &amp;#39;undefined&amp;#39;) { throw new Error(&amp;#39;Missing parameter 1 dns type&amp;#39;); } if (typeof domain == &amp;#39;undefined&amp;#39;) { throw new Error(&amp;#39;Missing parameter 2 domain name&amp;#39;); } type = type.toUpperCase(); var url = &amp;#39;https://cloudflare-dns.</description></item><item><title>DNS over Discord</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-over-discord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-over-discord/</guid><description>DNS over Discord1.1.1.1 works from a Discord server, thanks to the 1.1.1.1 bot. Invite the bot to your Discord server External link icon Open external link to start using DNS over Discord.
&amp;#8203;​ Perform DNS lookups Once the bot is in your server, type /dig to start performing DNS lookups. This will provide a native interface within Discord that allows you to specify the domain to lookup, an optional DNS record type and an optional flag for a short result.</description></item><item><title>DNS over Telegram</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-over-telegram/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-over-telegram/</guid><description>DNS over TelegramTo perform DNS lookups over Telegram, you will need Telegram, an end-to-end encrypted messaging app. You can download it on telegram.org External link icon Open external link .
You will also need to add the 1.1.1.1 bot to your friends list in Telegram before using this functionality.
&amp;#8203;​ Add 1.1.1.1 bot to your Telegram friends list Open the Telegram app. Select Contacts. Search for onedotonedotonedotonedotbot. Select the 1.</description></item><item><title>DNS over Tor</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-over-tor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/other-ways-to-use-1.1.1.1/dns-over-tor/</guid><description>DNS over TorThe hidden resolver is still an experimental service and should not be used in production or for other critical uses. If you do not want to disclose your IP address to the resolver, you can use our Tor onion service. Resolving DNS queries through the Tor network guarantees a significantly higher level of anonymity than making the requests directly. Not only does doing so prevent the resolver from ever seeing your IP address, but it also prevents your ISP from knowing that you attempted to resolve a domain name.</description></item></channel></rss>