<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Identity on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/</link><description>Recent content in Identity on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One-time PIN login</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/one-time-pin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/one-time-pin/</guid><description>One-time PIN loginCloudflare Access can send a one-time PIN (OTP) to approved email addresses as an alternative to integrating an identity provider. You can simultaneously configure OTP login and the identity provider of your choice to allow users to select their own authentication method.
For example, if your team uses Okta® but you are collaborating with someone outside your organization, you can use OTP to grant access to guests.</description></item><item><title>Service tokens</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/service-tokens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/service-tokens/</guid><description>Service tokensYou can provide automated systems with service tokens to authenticate against your Zero Trust policies. Cloudflare Access will generate service tokens that consist of a Client ID and a Client Secret. Automated systems or applications can then use these values to reach an application protected by Access.
This section covers how to create, renew, and revoke a service token.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a service token In the Zero Trust dashboard External link icon Open external link , navigate to Access &amp;gt; Service Auth &amp;gt; Service Tokens.</description></item><item><title>Login page</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/login-page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/login-page/</guid><description>Login pageUnder Settings &amp;gt; General, you can customize the login page your end users will see when trying to reach applications behind Cloudflare Zero Trust.
Click Customize to give the login page the look and feel of your organization by adding your organization&amp;rsquo;s name and by choosing a custom header and footer, a logo, and a preferred background color.
Any changes you make will be reflected in real time in the Preview card.</description></item></channel></rss>