<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/configuration-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/configuration-settings/</guid><description>Configuration settingsYou can customize a variety of options for your waiting rooms.
Dashboard settings Additional details &amp;#8203;​ Dashboard settings Settings Notes Dashboard Setting API parameter Required? Description Best practices Name name Yes Unique waiting room name. Hostname host Yes Host name for which the waiting room will be applied (no wildcards). Do not include http:// or https://. Path path No Case-sensitive path of the waiting room. The waiting room will be enabled for all subpaths.</description></item><item><title>API commands</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/waiting-room-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/waiting-room-api/</guid><description>API commandsCloudflare Waiting Room redirect visitors to virtual waiting rooms when they are trying to access web pages that have high volumes of traffic.
The Cloudflare Waiting Room API provides an interface for programmatically managing waiting rooms.
&amp;#8203;​ Request URL format To invoke a Cloudflare Waiting Room API operation, append the endpoint to the Cloudflare API base URL:
https://api.cloudflare.com/client/v4 For authentication instructions, refer to Getting Started: Requests in the Cloudflare API documentation.</description></item><item><title>Best practices</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/best-practices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/best-practices/</guid><description>Best practicesFollow these best practices to avoid potential issues and improve the visitor experience.
&amp;#8203;​ Total active users When specifying the Total active users in your configuration settings, set the value to 75% of your origin&amp;rsquo;s traffic capacity.
&amp;#8203;​ Page path When setting the waiting room Path in your configuration settings, pay attention to potential subpaths. Waiting rooms are enabled on all subpaths, meaning you might be sending more traffic to your waiting room than anticipated.</description></item><item><title>Cookies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/waiting-room-cookie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/waiting-room-cookie/</guid><description>CookiesA waiting room only uses the __cfwaitingroom cookie when a visitor requests access to a host and path combination with an enabled and associated waiting room. When the waiting room is suspended, traffic goes to the origin and the __cfwaitingroom cookie is not created. The __cfwaitingroom cookie is encrypted to prevent modification by users.
Important:Cloudflare Waiting Room requires the __cfwaitingroom cookie. When a waiting room is actively queueing, users cannot visit that host and path combination without enabling cookies.</description></item><item><title>Queueing method</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/queueing-methods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/reference/queueing-methods/</guid><description>Queueing methodThe queueing method determines the order that visitors exit an active waiting room and reach your application.
Only certain customers can use queue methods besides First In First Out (FIFO). For more details, refer to Plans page.
Note:Regardless of the queueing method, if queueAll is enabled or an event is prequeueing, users in the waiting room will not be accepted to the origin. These users will always see a waiting room page that refreshes automatically.</description></item></channel></rss>