<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TLS protocols</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/protocols/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/protocols/</guid><description> TLS protocolsCloudflare supports the following TLS protocols:
TLS 1.0 TLS 1.1 TLS 1.2 TLS 1.3 ( recommended External link icon Open external link )</description></item><item><title>Certificate and hostname priority</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-and-hostname-priority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-and-hostname-priority/</guid><description>Certificate and hostname priorityWhen a new certificate is created, Cloudflare first deploys the certificate and then serves it.
&amp;#8203;​ Certificate deployment For any given hostname, Cloudflare uses the following order to determine which certificate (and associated TLS settings) apply to that hostname:
Hostname specificity: A specific subdomain certificate (www.example.com) would take precedence over a wildcard certificate (*.example.com) for requests to www.example.com.
Zone specificity: A specific subdomain certificate (www.example.com) would take precedence over a custom hostname certificate if the domain is active as a zone on Cloudflare.</description></item><item><title>Certificate authorities</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-authorities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-authorities/</guid><description>Certificate authoritiesCloudflare may issue Universal, Advanced, or SSL for SaaS certificates from any of the following Certificate Authorities (CAs):
Certificate authority Features Limitations Client support DigiCert (soon to be deprecated) RSA and ECDSA certificatesSupports validity periods of 14, 30, and 90 days TLD restrictions External link icon Open external link Browser compatibility External link icon Open external link Let’s Encrypt RSA and ECDSA certificatesSupports validity periods of 90 days.DCV tokens valid for 7 days.</description></item><item><title>Browser compatibility</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/browser-compatibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/browser-compatibility/</guid><description>Browser compatibilityCloudflare attempts to provide compatibility for as wide a range of user agents (browsers, API clients, etc.) as possible. The specific set of supported browsers differs by SSL product, however. See below for specific details.
&amp;#8203;​ Universal SSL Feature/Zone Plan Free Pro Business Enterprise Clients using ECDSA key exchange ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Clients using RSA key exchange ❌ ✅ ✅ ✅ ImportantCloudflare Universal SSL only supports browsers and API clients that use the Server Name Indication (SNI) External link icon Open external link extension to the TLS protocol.</description></item><item><title>Certificate pinning</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-pinning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-pinning/</guid><description>Certificate pinningCloudflare does not support HTTP public key pinning (HPKP)1 for Universal, Advanced, or Custom Hostname certificates.
This is because Cloudflare regularly changes the edge certificates provisioned for your domain and - if you had HPKP enabled - your domain would go offline. Additionally, industry experts External link icon Open external link discourage using HPKP.
For a better solution to the problem that HPKP is trying to solve - preventing certificate misissuance - use Certificate Transparency Monitoring.</description></item><item><title>Certificate statuses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-statuses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-statuses/</guid><description>Certificate statusesCertificates statuses tell you the state of each certificate.
&amp;#8203;​ New certificates When you create a new certificate, it moves through the various stages as it progresses to Cloudflare’s edge:
Initializing Pending Validation Pending Issuance Pending Deployment Active Once you issue a certificate, it should be in Pending Validation, but change to Active within five minutes. If you see any errors, you or your customer may need to take additional actions to validate the certificate.</description></item><item><title>Validation backoff schedule</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/validation-backoff-schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/validation-backoff-schedule/</guid><description>Domain control validation backoff scheduleDomain control validation (DCV) has to happen before a Certificate Authority (CA) will issue a certificate for a domain.
DCV happens with Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s CA partners according to the following schedule:
DigiCert - 30 days Google Trust Services - 14 days Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt - 7 days Afterward, DCV tokens expire as dictated by the CA/B Baseline Requirements, which govern issuance of publicly trusted SSL certificates.
Here is the function that is used to determine the next check:</description></item><item><title>Validity periods</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-validity-periods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/certificate-validity-periods/</guid><description>Certificate validity periodsWhen you order an advanced certificate, you can select the following values for the Certificate validity period:
1 year (soon to be deprecated) 3 months 1 month 2 weeks For more details on the validity_days parameter used in API calls, refer to Order Advanced Certificate Pack. &amp;#8203;​ Benefits of shorter validity periods Cloudflare only issues certificates with validity periods of three months or less for two reasons.</description></item></channel></rss>