<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edit images on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/</link><description>Recent content in Edit images on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Resize images</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/resize-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/resize-images/</guid><description>Resize imagesResizing images in Cloudflare Images works by creating variants of your image. Variants let you specify how images should be resized for different use cases. Cloudflare Images ships with a default public variant, but you can create up to 100 variants to fit your needs.
Each variant has several properties, including the width and height of resized images.
&amp;#8203;​ How to resize an image Cloudflare Images does not resize SVGs.</description></item><item><title>Flexible variants</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/flexible-variants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/flexible-variants/</guid><description>Flexible variantsIf you need more flexibility than regular variants allow, you can create flexible variants. Flexible variants allow you to create variants with dynamic resizing. This option is not enabled by default. You can enable flexible variants through the dashboard or via API.
WarningEnabling flexible variants on your account effectively allows anyone to obtain untransformed, full-resolution images and their metadata by changing variant properties in the URL. Dashboard API Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account.</description></item><item><title>Blur images</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/blur-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/blur-images/</guid><description>Blur imagesYou can apply blur to image variants, except for SVG files. To blur an image, you have to either create a specific variant for this effect first, or edit a previously created variant.
Refer to Resize images to learn how to create variants. You can also refer to the API to learn how to use blur using flexible variants.
To apply blur to an image:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account.</description></item><item><title>Edit images</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/edit-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/edit-images/</guid><description>Edit imagesThe Edit option, available from the main Images screen, is your one-stop location for options related with a specific image. Selecting Edit on the image you are interested in, opens a new page with all the options available, such as:
Require Signed URLs to use with that particular image cURL command you can use as an example to access the image Fully-formed URLs for all the variants configured in your account.</description></item><item><title>Delete images</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/delete-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/delete-images/</guid><description>Delete imagesYou can delete an image from the Cloudflare Images storage using the dashboard or the API.
Dashboard API Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Select Images. Find the image you want to remove and select Delete. (Optional) If you want to delete more than one image, select the checkbox next to the images you want to delete and then Delete selected.</description></item><item><title>Delete variants</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/delete-variants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/delete-variants/</guid><description>Delete variantsYou can delete variants via the Images dashboard or API. The only variant you cannot delete is public.
WarningDeleting a variant is a global action that will affect other images that contain that variant. Dashboard API Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Select Images &amp;gt; Variants. Find the variant you want to remove and select Delete. For detailed information on using the API, refer to the API endpoint documentation.</description></item><item><title>Export images</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/export-image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/transform/export-image/</guid><description>Export imagesCloudflare Images supports image exports. This feature is available both in the Cloudflare dashboard and via API.
Dashboard API Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Select Images. Find the image or images you want to export. If you want to export a single image, select Export. If you need to export several images, first select the checkbox on the images you want to export and then select Export selected.</description></item></channel></rss>