<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/limits/</guid><description>Rate LimitsThe global rate limit for Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s API is 1200 requests per five minutes. If you exceed this, all API calls for the next five minutes will be blocked, receiving a HTTP 429 response.
Some specific API calls have their own limits and are documented separately, such as the Cache Purge APIs:
https://api.cloudflare.com/#zone-purge-files-by-url External link icon Open external link https://developers.cloudflare.com/api/operations/zone-purge-files-by-cache-tags,-host-or-prefix Enterprise customers may contact Cloudflare Support External link icon Open external link to raise the limit of a higher value if needed.</description></item><item><title>API token permissions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/permissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/permissions/</guid><description>API token permissionsPermissions are segmented into three categories based on resource:
Zone permissions Account permissions User permissions Each category contains permission groups related to those resources. DNS permissions belong to the Zone category, while Billing permissions belong to the Account category. Below is a list of the available token permissions.
To obtain an updated list of token permissions, including the permission ID and the scope of each permission, use the List permission groups endpoint.</description></item><item><title>API token templates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/template/</guid><description> API token templatesBelow is a table of the currently available API token templates and the default token permissions they grant. You can start creating a token with one of these templates and modify the permissions and resources from there.
Template Name Permission Resource Edit Zone DNS DNS Write Zone Read billing info Billing Read Account Account resources: Include all accounts Read analytics and logs Analytics Read Zone Logs Read Zone Edit Cloudflare Workers Workers Routes Write Zone Workers Scripts Write Account Workers KV Storage Write Account Workers Tail Read Account Workers R2 Storage Write Account Account Settings Read Account User Details Read User User Memberships Read User Edit load balancing configuration Load Balancing: Monitors and Pools Write Account Load Balancers Write Zone WordPress Analytics Read Zone Zone Read Zone Zone Settings Write Zone Account Settings Read Account DNS Read Zone Cache Purge Zone Account resources: Include all accounts Zone resources: Include all zones Create Additional Tokens API Tokens Write User Read All Resources (All read permissions) Account, Zone, User Account resources: Include all accounts Zone resources: Include all zones</description></item><item><title>API deprecations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/deprecations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/reference/deprecations/</guid><description>API v4 deprecationsCloudflare occassionally makes updates to our APIs that result in behavior changes or deprecations. When this happens, we will communicate when the API will no longer be available and whether there will be a replacement.
&amp;#8203;​ Argo Tunnel End of life Date: February 4, 2024
This endpoint and its related APIs are deprecated in favor of the Cloudflare Tunnels equivalent APIs.
Deprecated API:
GET accounts/:account_identifier/tunnels POST accounts/:account_identifier/tunnels GET accounts/:account_identifier/tunnels/:tunnel_id DELETE accounts/:account_identifier/tunnels/:tunnel_id Replacement: Cloudflare Tunnel API</description></item></channel></rss>