<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Logpull on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/</link><description>Recent content in Logpull on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Understanding the basics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/understanding-the-basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/understanding-the-basics/</guid><description>Understanding the basics &amp;#8203;​ Access pattern The basic access pattern is give me all the logs for zone Z for minute M where the minute M refers to the time the log entries were written to disk in Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s log aggregation system.
To start, try running your query every minute. If responses are too small, go up to 5 minutes as this will be appropriate for most zones. If the responses are too large, try going down to 15 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Enabling log retention</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/enabling-log-retention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/enabling-log-retention/</guid><description>Enabling log retentionBy default, your HTTP request logs are not retained. When using the Logpull API for the first time, you will need to enable retention. You can also turn off retention at any time. Note that after retention is turned off, previously saved logs will be available until the retention period expires (refer to Data retention period).
&amp;#8203;​ Endpoints There are two endpoints for managing log retention:
GET /logs/control/retention/flag - returns whether retention is on POST /logs/control/retention/flag - turns retention on or off NoteTo make a POST call, you must have a Cloudflare account role with edit permissions, such as Super Administrator, Administrator, or Log Share.</description></item><item><title>Requesting logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/requesting-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/requesting-logs/</guid><description>Requesting logs &amp;#8203;​ Endpoints The three endpoints supported by the Logpull API are:
GET /logs/received - returns HTTP request log data based on the parameters specified GET /logs/received/fields - returns the list of all available log fields GET /logs/rayids/&amp;lt;rayid&amp;gt; - returns HTTP request log data matching &amp;lt;rayid&amp;gt; &amp;#8203;​ Required authentication headers The following headers are required for all endpoint calls:
X-Auth-Email - the Cloudflare account email address associated with the domain X-Auth-Key - the Cloudflare API key Alternatively, API tokens with Logs Edit permissions can also be used for authentication:</description></item><item><title>Additional details</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/additional-details/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/logpull/additional-details/</guid><description>Additional details &amp;#8203;​ Estimating daily data volume To estimate the amount of data for a zone per day (the number of log lines and the amount of bytes they take up), request a 1% or 10% sample of data for a 1-hour period (use 10% if your volume is low). Note that start=2018-12-15T00:00:00Z and end=2018-12-15T01:00:00Z span a 1-hour period, and sample=0.1.
curl -s \ -H &amp;#34;X-Auth-Email: &amp;lt;EMAIL&amp;gt;&amp;#34; \ -H &amp;#34;X-Auth-Key: &amp;lt;API_KEY&amp;gt;&amp;#34; \ &amp;#34;https://api.</description></item></channel></rss>