<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/prerequisites/</guid><description>PrerequisitesBefore you can begin using Magic Transit, verify that you meet Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s onboarding requirements.
&amp;#8203;​ Verify router compatibility Magic Transit relies on Anycast tunnels to transmit packets from Cloudflare’s edge to your origin network.
The routers at your tunnel endpoints must meet the following requirements to ensure compatibility with Magic Transit.
Support Anycast tunneling. Allow configuration of at least one tunnel per Internet service provider (ISP). Support maximum segment size (MSS) clamping.</description></item><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/get-started/</guid><description>Get startedBefore you can begin using Magic Transit, be sure to complete the onboarding steps below. Cloudflare can significantly accelerate this timeline during active-attack scenarios.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Scope your configuration The onboarding process begins with an initial kickoff call where Cloudflare engages with your organization to confirm the scope and timeline for setting up Magic Transit.
After your call with Cloudflare, complete the prerequisites.
&amp;#8203;​ 2. Configure tunnels Configure your tunnels to connect Cloudflare to your origin infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare IPs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/cloudflare-ips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/cloudflare-ips/</guid><description>Use a Cloudflare IPIn addition to using Magic Transit with your own IP address, you can use Magic Transit with a Cloudflare-managed IP address. This option is helpful for users who do not meet the /24 prefix length requirements or who want to protect a smaller network.
To protect your network using a Cloudflare IP address, contact your account manager. After you receiving your IP address, you will need to:</description></item><item><title>On-demand</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/on-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/on-demand/</guid><description>Magic Transit on-demandCustomers with access to the Magic Transit on-demand option can configure prefix advertisement from the IP Prefixes page in their Cloudflare account home or via the Cloudflare API.
A common workflow is to enable prefix advertisement during an attack so that you can take advantage of Cloudflare protection and then disable advertisement once the incident is resolved. Prefixes using BGP-controlled advertisements cannot be used in conjunction with on-demand auto-advertisement.</description></item><item><title>Network Interconnect</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/network-interconnect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/network-interconnect/</guid><description>Network Interconnect and Magic TransitCloudflare Network Interconnect (CNI) allows you to connect your network infrastructure directly with Cloudflare – rather than using the public Internet – for a more reliable and secure experience.
Use Cloudflare Network Interconnect with Magic Transit to decrease jitter, drive throughput improvements, and harden infrastructure to attack.
For more information about Network Interconnect, refer to the Network Interconnect documentation.
&amp;#8203;​ Guidelines When working with Magic Transit and CNI, observe these guidelines:</description></item></channel></rss>