<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/about/</guid><description>AboutClient IP Geolocation is currently in closed Beta testing. Cloudflare Client IP Geolocation helps you understand where in the world a given client is located, even if their true client IP address is obscured by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s proxy systems. We offer this service to ensure customers have high-quality experiences interacting with origins that rely on geolocation — such as mapping providers — and origin operators can deliver the right content to the right users.</description></item><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/get-started/</guid><description>Get startedClient IP Geolocation is currently in closed Beta testing. There are several things you can do to best handle traffic from Cloudflare VPN and forward-proxy users:
Origin operators: Do not block IP addresses associated with our VPN and proxy products (see the About section for more details) To get even more accurate geolocation data, ensure your origin is reachable via IPv6 Geolocation data providers: Regularly pull updated geolocation data from the Cloudflare API External link icon Open external link Users of WARP and 1.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/client-ip-geolocation/faq/</guid><description>FAQClient IP Geolocation is currently in closed Beta testing. &amp;#8203;​ Website operators &amp;#8203;​ What does this functionality mean for me as a website operator? If you operate a website or ISP that needs to use IP address geolocation information for geographic content restriction, consider allowing IP addresses associated with a VPN.
You can now restrict content delivery to Cloudflare VPN users using the same client IP geolocation mechanisms used for non-VPN users.</description></item></channel></rss>