<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/get-started/</guid><description>Get started &amp;#8203;​ Step 1 — Contract required services and agree to supplemental terms Ensure that you have a Cloudflare Enterprise plan. If you do not have an Enterprise plan yet, you must upgrade. Add the Cloudflare China Network package (a separate subscription) to your Enterprise plan. Agree to the China Service Supplemental Terms External link icon Open external link . Contact your sales team for more information on these steps.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/faq/</guid><description>FAQ &amp;#8203;​ Requirements &amp;#8203;​ What are the requirements to enable the Cloudflare China Network service from Cloudflare? Refer to Get started for more information.
&amp;#8203;​ Can I use my current account to access the Cloudflare China Network service or do I need a separate account? Yes, you can use your current Cloudflare account and dashboard.
&amp;#8203;​ What are the requirements for requesting a Cloudflare China Network PoC? Cloudflare requires that you have a valid ICP (Internet Content Provider) number and content vetting approval from JD Cloud to provide you with a Cloudflare China Network PoC (proof of concept).</description></item></channel></rss>