<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>URL Rewrite Rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/</link><description>Recent content in URL Rewrite Rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a rule in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/create-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/create-dashboard/</guid><description>Create a URL Rewrite Rule in the dashboardCreate URL Rewrite Rules in the Transform Rules tab under Rules. Refer to URL rewrite examples for examples of rule definitions.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and website.
Go to Rules &amp;gt; Transform Rules.
Click Create transform rule &amp;gt; Rewrite URL.
In the page that displays, enter a descriptive name for the rule in Rule name.</description></item><item><title>Create a rule via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/create-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/create-api/</guid><description>Create a URL Rewrite Rule via APIUse the Rulesets API to create URL Rewrite Rules via API. Define the rewrite configuration in the action_parameters field. Refer to URL rewrite examples for examples of rule definitions.
When creating a URL Rewrite Rule via API, make sure you:
Set the rule action to rewrite. Define the URL rewrite parameters in the action_parameters field according to the type of URL rewrite (static or dynamic).</description></item><item><title>URL rewrite examples</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/url-rewrite/examples/</guid><description>URL rewrite examplesThe following examples illustrate how to perform URL rewrites with Transform Rules:
Rewrite path of welcome page for visitors in specific countries Rewrite URL query string of blog visitors Rewrite path of archived blog posts Rewrite path of moved section of a website Rewrite path with several URL segments to a different URL segment Rewrite blog archive URLs to support a new URL format &amp;#8203;​ Rewrite path of welcome page for visitors in specific countries To have a welcome page in two languages, create two URL Rewrite Rules with a static rewrite of the path component:</description></item></channel></rss>