<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Play video on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/</link><description>Recent content in Play video on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Secure your Stream</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/securing-your-stream/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/securing-your-stream/</guid><description>Secure your Stream &amp;#8203;​ Signed URLs / Tokens By default, videos on Stream can be viewed by anyone with just a video id. If you want to make your video private by default and only give access to certain users, you can use the signed URL feature. When you mark a video to require signed URL, it can no longer be accessed publicly with only the video id. Instead, the user will need a signed url token to watch or download the video.</description></item><item><title>Display thumbnails</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/displaying-thumbnails/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/displaying-thumbnails/</guid><description>Display thumbnailsStream thumbnails are not supported for videos with non-square pixels. &amp;#8203;​ Use Case 1: Generating a thumbnail on-the-fly A thumbnail from your video can be generated using a special link where you specify the time from the video you&amp;rsquo;d like to get the thumbnail from.
https://customer-m033z5x00ks6nunl.cloudflarestream.com/b236bde30eb07b9d01318940e5fc3eda/thumbnails/thumbnail.jpg?time=1s&amp;amp;height=270
Using the poster query parameter in the embed URL, you can set a thumbnail to any time in your video. If signed URLs are required, you must use a signed URL instead of video UIDs.</description></item><item><title>Download videos</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/download-videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/download-videos/</guid><description>Download videosWhen you upload a video to Stream, it can be streamed using HLS/DASH. However, for certain use-cases (such as offline viewing), you may want to download the MP4. You can enable MP4 support on a per video basis by following the steps below:
Enable MP4 support by making a POST request to the /downloads endpoint (example below) Save the MP4 URL provided by the response to the /downloads endpoint.</description></item><item><title>AV1 playback (beta)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/av1-playback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/viewing-videos/av1-playback/</guid><description>AV1 playback Beta Play live video or live recordings using the AV1 codec External link icon Open external link .
AV1 is an open, royalty-free video codec that uses 46% less bandwidth than H.264, the most commonly used codec for streaming video. Learn more about AV1 by reading the announcement blog post External link icon Open external link .
AV1 playback is currently in open beta, and we&amp;rsquo;d love to hear what you think.</description></item></channel></rss>