<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account options on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/</link><description>Recent content in Account options on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Domain management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/domain-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/domain-management/</guid><description>Domain management &amp;#8203;​ Domain status When your domain is registered with Cloudflare, you can review your domain status in the Overview pane.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain. From Overview, scroll down to Domain Registration to review the current expiration date. Select Manage domain to review the Auto-Renew status for your domain. &amp;#8203;​ Billing information Domain registrations will not appear in the Active Subscriptions section of the dashboard, as Registrar is not subscription based.</description></item><item><title>Enable DNSSEC</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/enable-dnssec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/enable-dnssec/</guid><description>Domain Name System Security Extensions (DNSSEC)The domain name system (DNS) translates domain names into numeric Internet addresses. However, DNS is a fundamentally insecure protocol. It does not guarantee where DNS records come from and accepts any requests given to it.
DNSSEC creates a secure layer to the domain name system by adding cryptographic signatures to DNS records. By doing so, your request can check the signature to verify that the record you need comes from the authoritative name server and was not altered along the way.</description></item><item><title>Registrant contact updates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/domain-contact-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/domain-contact-updates/</guid><description>Registrant contact updatesIt is important that you keep your contact details accurate and up-to-date. ICAAN rules state External link icon Open external link that if you do not have updated contact information, your domain name registration may be suspended or even cancelled.
To update your registrant contacts:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account. Select Domain Registration &amp;gt; Manage domains.</description></item><item><title>Renew domains</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/renew-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/renew-domains/</guid><description>Renew domains with Cloudflare Registrar &amp;#8203;​ Automatic renewal of domain Cloudflare Registrar enrolls your domain to auto-renew by default. Unlike other registrars, your domain will only renew at the list price set by the registry. When a domain has the auto-renew setting turned on, Cloudflare will attempt to automatically renew the domain prior to expiration.
There is no guarantee that the renewal will succeed. Renewals may fail for various reasons, including billing failures and registry downtime.</description></item><item><title>Transfer domain out from Cloudflare</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/transfer-out-from-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/registrar/account-options/transfer-out-from-cloudflare/</guid><description>Transfer domain from Cloudflare to another registrarCloudflare Registrar makes it easy to transfer your domain to another registrar. Be aware that ICANN rules prohibit a domain from being transferred if:
The domain has been transferred within the last 60 days; The domain was registered within the last 60 days; If the WHOIS registrant information has been modified in the last 60 days (even if redacted). Follow the instructions below to transfer your domain out from Cloudflare.</description></item></channel></rss>