<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rulesets reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Rulesets reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloudflare Managed Ruleset</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/cloudflare-managed-ruleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/cloudflare-managed-ruleset/</guid><description>Cloudflare Managed RulesetCreated by the Cloudflare security team, this ruleset provides fast and effective protection for all of your applications. The ruleset is updated frequently to cover new vulnerabilities and reduce false positives.
Cloudflare recommends that you enable the rules whose tags correspond to your technology stack. For example, if you use WordPress, enable the rules tagged with wordpress.
Cloudflare’s WAF changelog allows you to monitor ongoing changes to the WAF&amp;rsquo;s managed rulesets.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare OWASP Core Ruleset</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/owasp-core-ruleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/owasp-core-ruleset/</guid><description>Cloudflare OWASP Core RulesetThe Cloudflare OWASP Core Ruleset is Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s implementation of the OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set External link icon Open external link (CRS). Cloudflare routinely monitors for updates from OWASP based on the latest version available from the official code repository.
The Cloudflare OWASP Core Ruleset is designed to work as a single entity to calculate a threat score and execute an action based on that score. When a rule in the ruleset matches a request, the threat score increases according to the rule score.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare Exposed Credentials Check</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/exposed-credentials-check/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/reference/exposed-credentials-check/</guid><description>Cloudflare Exposed Credentials CheckThe Cloudflare Exposed Credentials Check Managed Ruleset is a set of pre-configured rules for well-known CMS applications that perform a lookup against a public database of stolen credentials.
The Cloudflare Exposed Credentials Check Managed Ruleset is only available in the Cloudflare WAF announced on March 2021. The managed ruleset includes rules for the following CMS applications:
WordPress Joomla Drupal Ghost Plone Magento Additionally, this managed ruleset also includes generic rules for other common patterns:</description></item></channel></rss>