<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DNS Firewall on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/</link><description>Recent content in DNS Firewall on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/setup/</guid><description>Set up DNS Firewall &amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Prior to setting up DNS Firewall, you need:
Account access to DNS Firewall (provided by your Enterprise account team). Access to DNS Administrator or Super Administrator privileges on your account. Newly updated IP addresses for your nameservers (protects against previously compromised IP addresses). &amp;#8203;​ Configure DNS Firewall &amp;#8203;​ Create a DNS Firewall cluster &amp;#8203;​ Using the dashboard Log in to the Cloudflare account External link icon Open external link with DNS Firewall.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/analytics/</guid><description>AnalyticsTo access analytics for your DNS Firewall, use the Cloudflare API. Alternatively, set up Logpush to deliver DNS Firewall logs to a storage service, SIEM, or log management provider in order to access DNS Firewall analytics there.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/dns-firewall/faq/</guid><description>FAQs — DNS Firewall How does DNS Firewall choose a backend nameserver to query upstream? DNS Firewall alternates between a customer&amp;rsquo;s nameservers, using an algorithm is more likely to send queries to the faster upstream nameservers than slower nameservers.
How long does DNS Firewall cache a stale object? DNS Firewall sets cache longevity according to allocated memory.
As long as there is enough allocated memory, Cloudflare does not clear items from the cache forcefully, even when the TTL expires.</description></item></channel></rss>