<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure tunnel endpoints</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/configure-tunnels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/configure-tunnels/</guid><description>Configure tunnel endpointsCloudflare recommends two tunnels for each ISP and data center router combination, one per Cloudflare endpoint. Cloudflare will assign two Cloudflare endpoint addresses shortly after your onboarding kickoff call that you can use as the tunnel destinations on your data center routers/endpoints.
To configure the tunnel(s) between Cloudflare and your data centers, you must provide the following data for each tunnel:
Tunnel name — A valid Linux interface name with 15 or less characters.</description></item><item><title>Configure static routes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/configure-static-routes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/configure-static-routes/</guid><description>Configure static routesMagic Transit uses a static configuration to route your traffic through Anycast tunnels from Cloudflare’s edge to your data centers.
You must assign a route priority to each Anycast tunnel–subnet pair in your GRE configuration using the following guidelines:
Lower values have greater priority. When the priority values for prefix entries match, Cloudflare uses equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) packet forwarding to route traffic. You can refer to an example of this scenario with the 103.</description></item><item><title>Advertise prefixes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/advertise-prefixes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/advertise-prefixes/</guid><description>Advertise prefixesCloudflare measures the Magic Transit prefix count based on the number of prefixes a customer announces through Cloudflare. The size of the prefix does not matter; there is no commercial or technical restriction. However, prefixes can only be announced exactly as they were provisioned. For example, a /20 prefix onboarded to Magic Transit can only be announced as a /20. Smaller subnets that constitute the /20 cannot be announced individually.</description></item><item><title>Run endpoint health checks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/run-endpoint-health-checks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/run-endpoint-health-checks/</guid><description>Run endpoint health checksMagic Transit uses endpoint health checks to determine the overall health of your inter-network connections. Probes originate from Cloudflare infrastructure, outside customer network namespaces, and target IP addresses deep within your network, beyond the tunnel-terminating border router. These “long distance” probes are purely diagnostic.
When choosing which endpoint IP addresses to monitor with health checks, use these guidelines:
Provide one IP address for each of the prefixes Cloudflare will advertise.</description></item><item><title>Enable Magic user roles</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/enable-magic-roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/enable-magic-roles/</guid><description>Magic user rolesYou can determine which users have, or do not have, configuration edit access for Magic products, including Magic Transit, Magic WAN, and Magic Firewall.
For example, if you have multiple Cloudflare products managed by different teams on the same account, you may want to provide select users with edit access and other users with read-only access.
&amp;#8203;​ Assign permissions Navigate to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account.</description></item><item><title>Enable per-prefix thresholds</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/auto-advertise-prefixes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-transit/how-to/auto-advertise-prefixes/</guid><description>Enable per-prefix thresholds with prefix auto advertisementUse Flow-based monitoring to configure custom thresholds for specific prefixes and CIDRs.
The system uses the concept of rules, and each rule consists of a group of prefixes. All prefixes inside a rule are evaluated as a whole, and you should set up a rule if you want the prefixes&amp;rsquo; aggregated traffic to trigger an alert or advertisement. For thresholds on singular prefixes or IPs, you can create an individual rule with one prefix and the desired threshold.</description></item></channel></rss>