<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upload images on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/</link><description>Recent content in Upload images on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Images dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/dashboard-upload/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/dashboard-upload/</guid><description>Images dashboard uploadUse the dashboard to quickly upload a single image to your Cloudflare Images account.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account. Select Images. Drag your image to Quick upload, or select Drop images here or select to browse. After the upload finishes, your new image will appear in your list of files.</description></item><item><title>Direct Creator Upload</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/direct-creator-upload/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/direct-creator-upload/</guid><description>Direct Creator UploadThe Direct Creator Upload feature in Cloudflare Images lets your users upload images with a one-time upload URL. By using Direct Creator Upload, you can accept uploads without exposing your API key or token to the client. It also eliminates the need for an intermediary storage bucket and the storage/egress costs associated with it.
To request a one-time upload URL, call the v2/direct_upload endpoint in your back-end (or Worker script):</description></item><item><title>URL upload</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/upload-via-url/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/upload-via-url/</guid><description>Upload via URLSometimes it can be useful to use a URL of an image instead of uploading its data. To accommodate this need, Cloudflare Images provides an option to use a URL to migrate images to Cloudflare without fetching them first.
To learn more about the supported image formats you can upload, refer to Supported image formats. Refer to Make your first API request to learn more about API tokens.</description></item><item><title>Custom ID</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/custom-id/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/custom-id/</guid><description>Custom IDYou can use a custom path to upload images to Cloudflare Images, instead of the path automatically generated by Cloudflare Images’ Universal Unique Identifier (UUID). The custom path has the following properties:
Can be up to 1024 characters long. Can include any number of subpaths. Supports the UTF-8 encoding standard External link icon Open external link for characters. Below is an example of the custom ID feature using upload via URL:</description></item><item><title>Formats and limitations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/formats-limitations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/upload-images/formats-limitations/</guid><description>Supported image formats and limitationsYou can upload the following image formats to Cloudflare Images:
PNG GIF JPEG WebP (Cloudflare Images does not support uploading animated WebP files) SVG &amp;#8203;​ Dimensions and sizes These are the maximum allowed sizes and dimensions Cloudflare Images supports:
Maximum image dimension is 12,000 pixels. Maximum image area is limited to 100 megapixels (for example, 10,000×10,000 pixels). Image metadata is limited to 1024 bytes. Images have a 10 megabyte (MB) size limit.</description></item></channel></rss>