<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/free/</guid><description>Get started with Bot Fight ModeBot Fight Mode is a simple, free product that helps detect and mitigate bot traffic on your domain. When enabled, the product:
Identifies traffic matching patterns of known bots Issues computationally expensive challenges in response to these bots Notifies Bandwidth Alliance External link icon Open external link partners (if applicable) to disable bots &amp;#8203;​ Enable Bot Fight Mode To start using Bot Fight Mode:</description></item><item><title>Pro</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/pro/</guid><description>Get started with Super Bot Fight Mode (Pro)Super Bot Fight Mode is included in your Pro subscription. When enabled, the product:
Identifies traffic matching patterns of known bots Can challenge or block bots Offers protection for static resources Provides limited analytics to help you understand bot traffic &amp;#8203;​ Enable Super Bot Fight Mode To start using Super Bot Fight Mode:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>Business</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/biz-and-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/biz-and-ent/</guid><description>Get started with Super Bot Fight Mode (Business)Super Bot Fight Mode is included in your Business or Enterprise subscription. When enabled, the product:
Identifies traffic matching patterns of known bots and likely bots Can challenge or block bots Offers protection for static resources Provides robust analytics to help you understand bot traffic Note: If you have an Enterprise subscription without Bot Management, your application will also have Super Bot Fight Mode for Business.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Bot Management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/bm-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/get-started/bm-subscription/</guid><description>Get started with Bot Management for EnterpriseBot Management for Enterprise is a paid add-on that provides sophisticated bot protection for your domain. Customers can identify automated traffic, take appropriate action, and view detailed analytics within the dashboard. Bot Management also supports custom solutions via Workers and Logs.
This Enterprise product provides the most flexibility to customers by:
Generating a bot score of 1-99 for every request. Scores below 30 are commonly associated with bot traffic.</description></item></channel></rss>