<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Browser Isolation on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/</link><description>Recent content in Browser Isolation on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Isolation policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/isolation-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/isolation-policies/</guid><description>Isolation policiesWith Browser Isolation, you can define policies to dynamically isolate websites based on identity, security threats, or content.
&amp;#8203;​ Isolate When an HTTP policy applies the Isolate action, the user&amp;rsquo;s web browser is transparently served an HTML compatible remote browser client. Isolation policies can be applied to requests that include Accept: text/html*. This allows Browser Isolation policies to co-exist with API traffic.
The following example enables isolation for all web traffic:</description></item><item><title>Extensions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/extensions/</guid><description>ExtensionsBrowser Isolation supports running native Chromium Web Extensions in the remote browser.
This capability allows extending tools that require DOM access (such as password managers and ad blockers) to isolated pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Install an extension inside the remote browser &amp;#8203;​ Prerequisite: Isolate Chrome Web Store This step is not required when browsing via Clientless Web Isolation. You can access the Chrome Web Store at https://&amp;lt;authdomain&amp;gt;.cloudflareaccess.com/browser/https://chrome.google.com/webstore. Installing extensions requires Chrome Web Store isolation.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/accessibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/accessibility/</guid><description>AccessibilityBrowser Isolation has a built-in screen reader which enables people with visual impairments to browse isolated pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable or disable the screen reader &amp;#8203;​ Keyboard shortcut To turn on or off the built-in screen reader, press Ctrl Alt Z.
&amp;#8203;​ Drop-down menu To turn on or off the built-in screen reader, right-click on any isolated page and select Accessibility &amp;gt; Enable / Disable screen reader.</description></item><item><title>Browser Isolation with firewall</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/network-dependencies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/network-dependencies/</guid><description>Browser Isolation with firewallIf your organization uses a firewall or other policies to restrict Internet traffic, you may need to make a few changes to allow Browser Isolation to connect.
&amp;#8203;​ Remoting client Isolated pages are served by the remoting client. This client communicates to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network via HTTPS and WebRTC.
&amp;#8203;​ Remoting Client (Services) The remoting client provides static assets and API endpoints. For Browser Isolation to function, you must allow:</description></item><item><title>Known limitations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/known-limitations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/browser-isolation/known-limitations/</guid><description>Known limitationsBelow, you will find information regarding the current limitations for Browser Isolation.
&amp;#8203;​ Website compatibility Our Network Vector Rendering (NVR) technology allows us to deliver a secure remote computing experience without the bandwidth limitations of video streams. While we expect most websites to work perfectly, some browser features and web technologies are unsupported and will be implemented in the future:
Webcam and microphone support is unavailable. Websites that use WebGL may not function.</description></item></channel></rss>