<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/get-started/</guid><description>Get startedNetwork Error Logging is available to users on all plan types. To enable Network Error Logging:
Log in to your Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . Select Network and locate Network Error Logging Monitoring. Select the toggle to enable Network Error Logging. For more information, refer to Understanding Network Error Logging External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>How to</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/how-to/</guid><description>View ReportsUse NEL reports to view information such as:
Why a request failed The country a request failed from The last mile network a request failed from The Cloudflare data center the request was most likely meant for Log in to your Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . Click Analytics &amp;gt; Origin Reachability. Click a tab under Reachability summary to view specific information related to your Origin ASN, Origin, IP, or data center.</description></item><item><title>Reference</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-error-logging/reference/</guid><description>FailuresIf a user is able to connect to Cloudflare and the site they connect to has NEL enabled, Cloudflare passes back two headers to the browser indicating that they should report any network failures to an endpoint specified in the headers. The browser will operate as usual, and if something happens that prevents the browser from connecting to the site, the browser will log the failure as a report and send it to the endpoint.</description></item></channel></rss>