<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage rules in the dashboard on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/</link><description>Recent content in Manage rules in the dashboard on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create, edit, and delete rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/create-edit-delete-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/create-edit-delete-rules/</guid><description>Create, edit, and delete rulesA firewall rule has two main attributes: an expression and an action.
When an incoming HTTP request matches a firewall rule expression, Cloudflare performs the specified action. For more information, refer to Expressions and Actions.
ImportantFirewall rule expressions have a 4 KB limit (approximately 4,000 text characters). This limit applies whether you use the visual Expression Builder or edit your expression manually in the Expression Editor.</description></item><item><title>Edit rule expressions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/edit-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/edit-expressions/</guid><description>Edit rule expressionsIn the Cloudflare dashboard, there are two options for editing expressions:
Expression Builder: Allows you to create expressions using drop-down lists, emphasizing a visual approach to defining an expression. Expression Editor: A text-only interface that supports advanced features, such as grouping symbols and functions for transforming and validating values. In general, you can switch back and forth between the Expression Builder and the Expression Editor. However, the Expression Builder does not support nested expressions.</description></item><item><title>Preview rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rule-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rule-preview/</guid><description>Preview firewall rulesThe expression of a firewall rule can become quite complex. In this situation, you should test your firewall rule before deploying it to ensure that the rule will behave as expected.
Rule Preview helps you understand the potential impact of a firewall rule, by testing the rule against a sample drawn from the last 72 hours of traffic. Rule Preview is built into the firewall rules Expression Editor so that you can test a rule as you edit it.</description></item><item><title>Create a mTLS rule</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/create-mtls-rule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/create-mtls-rule/</guid><description>Create a mTLS ruleUse the Mutual TLS Rule interface in the Cloudflare dashboard to create an mTLS rule that requires requests to your API or web application to present a valid client certificate.</description></item></channel></rss>