<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deploy WARP on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/</link><description>Recent content in Deploy WARP on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manual deployment</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/manual-deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/manual-deployment/</guid><description>Manual deploymentIf you plan to direct your users to manually download and configure the WARP client, users will need to connect the client to your organization&amp;rsquo;s Cloudflare Zero Trust instance.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Install the Cloudflare root certificate on user devices. Install the WARP client on user devices. &amp;#8203;​ Log in from Windows and macOS Click on the Cloudflare logo in the menu bar. Click the gear icon. Navigate to Preferences &amp;gt; Account.</description></item><item><title>WARP with firewall</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/firewall/</guid><description>WARP with firewallIf your organization uses a firewall or other policies to restrict or intercept Internet traffic, you may need to exempt the following IP addresses and domains to allow the WARP client to connect.
&amp;#8203;​ Client orchestration API The WARP client talks with our edge via a standard HTTPS connection outside the tunnel for operations like registration or settings changes. To perform these operations, you must allow zero-trust-client.cloudflareclient.com which will lookup the following IP addresses:</description></item><item><title>WARP with legacy VPN</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/vpn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/deployment/vpn/</guid><description>WARP with legacy VPNWe understand that you may be required to run a legacy third-party VPN alongside the Cloudflare WARP client. Because the WARP client and third-party VPN both enforce firewall, routing, and DNS rules on your local device, the two products will compete with each other for control over network traffic.
For the most stable and consistent connection, we recommend using Cloudflare Tunnel to connect your private network or individual applications to our global edge network.</description></item></channel></rss>