<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extended DNS error codes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/extended-dns-error-codes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/extended-dns-error-codes/</guid><description>Extended DNS error codes Extended DNS Error Codes External link icon Open external link is a method to return additional information about the cause of DNS errors. As there are many reasons why a DNS query might fail, it became necessary to provide additional information on the exact cause of an error.
1.1.1.1 supports Extended DNS Error Codes. Below is a list of error codes 1.1.1.1 returns, what they mean, and steps you may want to take to resolve the issue.</description></item><item><title>Network operators</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/network-operators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/network-operators/</guid><description>Network operatorsNetwork operators, including Internet Service Providers (ISPs), device manufacturers, public WiFi networks, municipal broadband providers, and security scanning services can use 1.1.1.1 and 1.1.1.1 for Families in place of operating their own recursive DNS infrastructure.
Using 1.1.1.1 can improve performance for end-users due to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s extensive global network External link icon Open external link , as well as provide higher overall cache hit rates due to our regional caches.</description></item><item><title>Support for IPv6-only networks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/ipv6-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/infrastructure/ipv6-networks/</guid><description>Support for IPv6-only networksWhile network infrastructure is shifting towards IPv6-only networks, providers still need to support IPv4 addresses. Dual-stack networks are networks in which all nodes have both IPv4 and IPv6 connectivity capabilities, and can therefore understand both IPv4 and IPv6 packets.
1.1.1.1 supports DNS64, a mechanism that synthesizes AAAA records from A records when no AAAA records exist. DNS64 allows configuring a DNS resolver to synthesize IPv6 addresses from IPv4 answers.</description></item></channel></rss>