<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DNS on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/agentless/dns/</link><description>Recent content in DNS on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/agentless/dns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DNS over HTTPS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/agentless/dns/dns-over-https/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/agentless/dns/dns-over-https/</guid><description>Configure DNS over HTTPSWith Cloudflare Gateway, you can filter DNS over HTTPS (DoH) requests by DNS location or by user without needing to install the WARP client on your devices.
Location-based policies require that you send DNS requests to a location-specific DoH endpoint, while identity-based policies require that requests include a user-specific DoH token.
&amp;#8203;​ Filter DoH requests by location Location-based policies require that you send DNS requests to a unique DoH endpoint assigned to the location:</description></item><item><title>DNS over TLS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/agentless/dns/dns-over-tls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/agentless/dns/dns-over-tls/</guid><description>Configure DNS over TLSBy default, DNS is sent over a plaintext connection. DNS over TLS (DoT) is a standard for encrypting DNS queries to keep them secure and private. DoT uses the same security protocol, TLS, that HTTPS websites use to encrypt and authenticate communications.
Cloudflare supports DoT on standard port 853 and is compliant with RFC7858 External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain your DoT hostname Each Gateway DNS location has a unique DoT hostname.</description></item></channel></rss>