<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plans on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/</link><description>Recent content in Plans on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/free/</guid><description>Plans — FreeTo learn more about features and functionality, select a plan. Free Pro Business Bot Management for Enterprise &amp;#8203;​ Free features Plan name Bot Fight Mode Availability All Free customers Enablement Toggle in Firewall > Bots Type of bots detected Simple bots (from cloud ASNs) and headless browsers Actions Cloudflare issues a computationally expensive challenge Additional control Applied to all traffic across a domain &amp;#8203;​ Bot detection engines &amp;#8203;​ Heuristics The Heuristics engine processes all requests.</description></item><item><title>Pro</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/pro/</guid><description>Plans — ProTo learn more about features and functionality, select a plan. Free Pro Business Bot Management for Enterprise &amp;#8203;​ Pro features Plan name Super Bot Fight Mode Availability All Pro customers Enablement Toggle in Firewall > Bots Type of bots detected Simple bots and headless browsers Actions Customer chooses whether to allow, block, or challenge Analytics Limited analytics available in a Bot Report Additional control Applied to all traffic across a domain &amp;#8203;​ Bot detection engines &amp;#8203;​ Heuristics The Heuristics engine processes all requests.</description></item><item><title>Business</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/biz-and-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/biz-and-ent/</guid><description>Plans — Business and EnterpriseTo learn more about features and functionality, select a plan. Free Pro Business Bot Management for Enterprise &amp;#8203;​ Business features Plan name Super Bot Fight Mode Availability All Business customers and Enterprise customers without Bot Management* Enablement Toggle in Firewall > Bots Type of bots detected Simple bots, headless browsers, and many sophisticated bots Actions Customer chooses whether to allow, block, or challenge Analytics Dedicated Bot Analytics tool, available in the Firewall Additional control Applied to all traffic across a domain *When users purchase Bot Management for Enterprise, Cloudflare automatically replaces and disables other bot products to prevent overlap.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Bot Management</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/bm-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/plans/bm-subscription/</guid><description>Plans — Bot Management for EnterpriseTo learn more about features and functionality, select a plan. Free Pro Business Bot Management for Enterprise &amp;#8203;​ Bot Management for Enterprise Features Plan name Bot Management for Enterprise Availability Added to Enterprise plans by your account team Enablement Quick onboarding with help from our Solutions Engineering team Type of bots detected Simple and sophisticated bots, headless browsers, and domain-specific anomalies Actions Customer chooses from several options, including block, CAPTCHA challenge, and JS challenge Analytics Dedicated Bot Analytics tool, available in the Firewall Additional control Ability to restrict by path, IP address, and more.</description></item></channel></rss>