<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>/cdn-cgi/ endpoint</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cdn-cgi-endpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cdn-cgi-endpoint/</guid><description>/cdn-cgi/ endpointWhen you add a domain to Cloudflare, Cloudflare adds a /cdn-cgi/ endpoint (www.example.com/cdn-cgi/) to that domain.
This endpoint is managed and served by Cloudflare. It cannot be modified or customized. The endpoint is not used by every Cloudflare product, but you may find some products use the endpoint in its URL.
A few examples include (but are not limited to):
JavaScript detection used by Cloudflare bot products (example.com/cdn-cgi/challenge-platform/) Web analytics for a website proxied through Cloudflare (example.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare and Google Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/google-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/google-analytics/</guid><description>Using Google Analytics with CloudflareUsing Cloudflare does not affect Google Analytics (GA) tracking if it is added to the website in one of ways recommended by Google External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Standard GA setup Cloudflare proxies traffic to your origin web server, but the GA JavaScript code never actually sends traffic to your server. Instead, it executes directly in a user&amp;rsquo;s browser and does not interact with Cloudflare.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare Cookies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cloudflare-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cloudflare-cookies/</guid><description>Cloudflare CookiesCloudflare uses various cookies to maximize network resources, manage traffic, and protect our customers’ sites from malicious traffic.
&amp;#8203;​ Understanding the Cloudflare Cookies As defined in our Privacy Policy External link icon Open external link , the __cflb, __cf_bm, cf_ob_info and cf_use_ob, __cfwaitingroom, and __cfruid cookies are strictly necessary to provide the services requested by our customers.
As mentioned in our Privacy Policy, Cloudflare encourages our customers to disclose the use of these cookies to their end users and, in some jurisdictions, customers may be required by law to disclose these cookies to their end users.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare Ray ID</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cloudflare-ray-id/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cloudflare-ray-id/</guid><description>Cloudflare Ray IDA Cloudflare Ray ID is an identifier given to every request that goes through Cloudflare.
Ray IDs are particularly useful when evaluating Security Events for patterns or false positives or more generally understanding your application traffic.
Ray IDs are not guaranteed to be unique for every request. In some situations, different requests may have the same Ray ID. &amp;#8203;​ Look up Ray IDs &amp;#8203;​ Security events All customers can view Ray IDs and associated information — IP address, user agent, ASN, etc.</description></item><item><title>Content Security Policies (CSPs)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/content-security-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/content-security-policies/</guid><description>Content Security Policies (CSPs) and CloudflareA Content Security Policy (CSP) is an added layer of security that helps detect and mitigate certain types of attacks, including:
Content/code injection Cross-site scripting (XSS) Embedding malicious resources Malicious iframes (clickjacking) To learn more about configuring a CSP in general, refer to the Mozilla documentation External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Using a CSP with Cloudflare Cloudflare’s CDN is compatible with CSP.</description></item><item><title>HTTP request headers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/http-request-headers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/http-request-headers/</guid><description>HTTP request headersCloudflare passes all HTTP request headers to your origin web server and adds additional headers as specified below.
&amp;#8203;​ CF-Connecting-IP CF-Connecting-IP provides the client IP address connecting to Cloudflare to the origin web server. This header will only be sent on the traffic from Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge to your origin web server.
For guidance on logging your visitor’s original IP address, refer to Restoring original visitor IPs External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>Network ports</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/network-ports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/network-ports/</guid><description>Network portsLearn which network ports Cloudflare proxies by default and how to enable Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s proxy for additional ports.
&amp;#8203;​ Network ports compatible with Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s proxy By default, Cloudflare proxies traffic destined for the HTTP/HTTPS ports listed below.
HTTP ports supported by Cloudflare 80 8080 8880 2052 2082 2086 2095 HTTPS ports supported by Cloudflare 443 2053 2083 2087 2096 8443 Ports supported by Cloudflare, but with caching disabled 2052 2053 2082 2083 2086 2087 2095 2096 8880 8443 &amp;#8203;​ How to enable Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s proxy for additional ports If traffic for your domain is destined for a different port than the ones listed above, for example you have an SSH server that listens for incoming connections on port 22, either:</description></item><item><title>When does Cloudflare crawl my site?</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cloudflare-site-crawling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/reference/cloudflare-site-crawling/</guid><description>When does Cloudflare crawl my site?Cloudflare may crawl or make HTTP requests to your site to make sure its protected and performing properly.
&amp;#8203;​ Crawling situations &amp;#8203;​ Specific products Cloudflare will crawl your site when you have specific products enabled:
Always Online User-Agent: Mozilla/5.0 (compatible; CloudFlare-AlwaysOnline/1.0; +http://www.cloudflare.com/always-online) SSL/TLS recommender User-Agent: Cloudflare-SSLDetector This crawler ignores your robots.txt file unless there are rules explicitly targeting the user agent. Load balancing monitors User-Agent: Mozilla/5.</description></item></channel></rss>