<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DigiCert update on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/</link><description>Recent content in DigiCert update on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Universal certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/universal-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/universal-certificates/</guid><description>Changes to Universal certificatesCloudflare will stop using DigiCert as an issuing certificate authority (CA) for new Universal certificates. This will not affect existing Universal certificates.
This process will begin for Enterprise zones on October 18, 2022.
The maximum validity period for Universal certificates will also be decreased from 1 year to 90 days.
&amp;#8203;​ DCV changes You do not need to make any updates to the Domain Control Validation (DCV) for your zone.</description></item><item><title>Advanced certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/advanced-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/advanced-certificates/</guid><description>Advanced certificatesOn March 6, 2023, Cloudflare will stop using DigiCert as an issuing certificate authority (CA) for new advanced certificates. This will not affect existing custom hostname certificates.
On March 13, 2023, Cloudflare will stop using DigiCert as the CA for advanced certificate renewals. This will not affect existing advanced certificates, only their renewals.
&amp;#8203;​ Summary of changes This table provides a summary of the differences between DigiCert and Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s other CAs.</description></item><item><title>Custom hostnames</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/custom-hostname-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/reference/migration-guides/digicert-update/custom-hostname-certificates/</guid><description>Custom hostnamesOn January 23, 2023, Cloudflare will stop using DigiCert as an issuing certificate authority (CA) for new custom hostname certificates. This will not affect existing custom hostname certificates.
On January 31, 2023, Cloudflare will stop using DigiCert as the CA for custom hostname certificate renewals. This will not affect existing custom hostname certificates, but only certificate renewals.
&amp;#8203;​ Summary of changes This table provides a summary of the differences between DigiCert and our other CAs.</description></item></channel></rss>