<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account maintenance on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/</link><description>Recent content in Account maintenance on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Change password or email</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/change-password-or-email/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/change-password-or-email/</guid><description>Change password or email &amp;#8203;​ Change password To change your Cloudflare password:
Go to your Profile External link icon Open external link . Select your account. Select Authentication. On Password, select Change. Change your password and select Save. For added account security, consider changing your API tokens as well.
If your administrator has enabled Single sign-on (SSO), you cannot change your Authentication settings. &amp;#8203;​ Change email address To change the email address associated with your Cloudflare account:</description></item><item><title>Cancel Cloudflare subscriptions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/cancel-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/cancel-subscription/</guid><description>Cancel Cloudflare subscriptionsCancellations are not processed until the end of the billing period, so you can continue using the add-on or subscription until the new billing period begins. To avoid unwanted charges, start the cancellation process before the end of your billing period.
All billing period dates on invoices and the dashboard are in UTC/GMT timezone, not your local timezone. We recommend any downgrades or changes to subscriptions be made at least 24 hours before stated billing date to avoid any timezone confusion.</description></item><item><title>Change domain plan</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/change-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/change-plan/</guid><description>Change domain planOccasionally, you may want to upgrade or downgrade the plan associated with a specific Cloudflare domain.
&amp;#8203;​ Limitations If you decide to downgrade or remove a domain, Cloudflare does not issue refunds. Refer to our billing policy External link icon Open external link for more information.
Upgrades are processed immediately, but downgrades are not processed until the end of the billing period. When downgrading, you are allowed to continue using the higher plans&amp;rsquo; products until the new billing period begins.</description></item><item><title>Delete your Cloudflare account</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/delete-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/delete-account/</guid><description>Delete your Cloudflare accountThese steps do not apply to accounts under contract. Contact your Customer Success manager if you would like to delete a contract account.
&amp;#8203;​ Who can delete their account If your account uses Single-Sign On (SSO), your super administrator may need to delete your account on your behalf.
If your account does not use SSO, you can delete your account on your own.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before Cloudflare can cancel your account and delete your personal information, you will need to follow the process below for each domain associated with your Cloudflare account:</description></item><item><title>Update billing information</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/updating-billing-info/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/updating-billing-info/</guid><description>Update billing informationTo avoid potential disruptions in your Cloudflare services, make sure your billing information is current and accurate. It is also important to understand how Cloudflare plans and add-ons are priced External link icon Open external link .
If Cloudflare is unable to process your payment, review Troubleshooting failed payments External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Access payment methods To access your current payment methods (primary and backup):</description></item><item><title>Understand Cloudflare invoices</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/understand-invoices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/understand-invoices/</guid><description>Understand Cloudflare invoicesYou will receive an invoice in the Billing section of your Cloudflare account when you:
Change your Cloudflare plan type Upgrade or downgrade to or from a paid plan Add a new domain to a Cloudflare account Enable or renew a subscription or add-on service For any historical invoices not included in the Billing section, contact Cloudflare support External link icon Open external link .
Enterprise customers receive invoices directly from the Cloudflare accounting team.</description></item><item><title>Change Super Admininstrator</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/change-super-admin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-maintenance/change-super-admin/</guid><description>Change Super AdmininstratorIf you or someone in your organization leaves or loses access to email, you must change who is assigned the Super Administrator role. However, the process differs based on your plan type.
&amp;#8203;​ Enterprise customers Enterprise accounts can have multiple Super Administrators associated with their accounts.
First, add a member to your account and assign the Super Administrator role.
Then, if needed, remove the previous Super Administrator.</description></item></channel></rss>