<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Make API requests to 1.1.1.1 on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/encryption/dns-over-https/make-api-requests/</link><description>Recent content in Make API requests to 1.1.1.1 on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/encryption/dns-over-https/make-api-requests/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DNS Wireformat</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/encryption/dns-over-https/make-api-requests/dns-wireformat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/encryption/dns-over-https/make-api-requests/dns-wireformat/</guid><description>Using DNS WireformatCloudflare respects DNS wireformat as defined in RFC1035 External link icon Open external link .
To send queries using DNS wireformat, set the header accept: application/dns-message, or content-type: application/dns-message if using POST to signalize the media type of the query.
Queries using DNS wireformat can be sent using POST or GET.
&amp;#8203;​ Using POST When making requests using POST, the DNS query is included as the message body of the HTTP request, and the MIME type (see below) is included in the Content-Type request header.</description></item><item><title>Using JSON</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/encryption/dns-over-https/make-api-requests/dns-json/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/1.1.1.1/encryption/dns-over-https/make-api-requests/dns-json/</guid><description>Using JSONCloudflare&amp;rsquo;s DNS over HTTPS endpoint also supports JSON format for querying DNS data. For lack of an agreed upon JSON schema for DNS over HTTPS in the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF), Cloudflare has chosen to follow the same schema as Google&amp;rsquo;s DNS over HTTPS resolver.
JSON formatted queries are sent using a GET request. When making requests using GET, the DNS query is encoded into the URL. The client should include an HTTP Accept request header field with a MIME type of application/dns-json to indicate that the client is able to accept a JSON response from the DNS over HTTPS resolver.</description></item></channel></rss>