<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About drand on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/randomness-beacon/about/</link><description>Recent content in About drand on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/randomness-beacon/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Background</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/randomness-beacon/about/background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/randomness-beacon/about/background/</guid><description>BackgroundOver the years, a generation of public randomness (often referred to as common coins) has attracted interest from the cryptography research community. Many distributed systems, including various consensus mechanisms, anonymity networks such as Tor, or blockchain systems, assume access to such public randomness. However, it remained a major unsolved issue to generate public randomness in a distributed, scalable, and robust way. Currently, there is no service deployed to produce this type of randomness.</description></item><item><title>Future of drand</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/randomness-beacon/about/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/randomness-beacon/about/future/</guid><description>Future of drandAs of spring 2020, the drand network is production-ready and can now be considered foundational Internet infrastructure, much like DNS or BGP.
While the project has reached a mature state, we believe there are several ways for drand to continue to evolve.
We would like to continue to see reliable partners join the network; the more participants in the network, the stronger the guarantees.
We would like to investigate how to generate public randomness in a post-quantum secure way (like, through isogeny, lattice, and so on).</description></item></channel></rss>