<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Log Output Options</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-output-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-output-options/</guid><description>Log Output OptionsJobs in Logpush now have a new key output_options which replaces logpull_options and allows more flexible formatting.
Edge Logstream jobs do not support this yet.
&amp;#8203;​ Replacing logpull_options Previously, Logpush jobs could be customized by specifying the list of fields, sampling rate, and timestamp format in logpull_options as URL-encoded parameters. For example:
{ &amp;#34;id&amp;#34;: 146, &amp;#34;dataset&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;http_requests&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;enabled&amp;#34;: false, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;lt;DOMAIN_NAME&amp;gt;&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;logpull_options&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;fields=ClientIP,EdgeStartTimestamp,RayID&amp;amp;sample=0.1&amp;amp;timestamps=rfc3339&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;destination_conf&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;s3://&amp;lt;BUCKET_PATH&amp;gt;?region=us-west-2&amp;#34; } We have replaced this with output_options as it is used for both Logpull and Logpush.</description></item><item><title>Filters</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/filters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/filters/</guid><description>FiltersThe following table represents the comparison operators that are supported and example values. Filters are added as escaped JSON strings formatted as {&amp;quot;key&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;lt;field&amp;gt;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;operator&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;lt;comparison_operator&amp;gt;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;value&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;lt;value&amp;gt;&amp;quot;}.
Refer to the Log fields page for a list of fields related to each dataset.
Comparison operators define how values must relate to fields in the log line for an expression to return true.
Values represent the data associated with fields.
Name Operator Notation Supported Field Types English String Int Bool Array Object Example (operator in bold) Equal eq &amp;#x2705; &amp;#x2705; &amp;#x2705; &amp;#10060; &amp;#10060; {\"</description></item><item><title>Custom fields</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/custom-fields/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/custom-fields/</guid><description>Custom fieldsYou can configure custom fields — selected from the list of HTTP request headers, HTTP response headers, and cookies — to include in Logpush log entries of a zone. Once configured, these custom fields will be enabled for all the Logpush jobs in the zone that use the HTTP requests dataset and include the request headers, response headers, or cookie fields.
Custom fields can be enabled via API or the Cloudflare dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Pathing status</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/pathing-status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/pathing-status/</guid><description>Pathing status &amp;#8203;​ Understanding pathing Cloudflare issues the following Edge Pathing Statuses:
EdgePathingSrc (pathing source): The stage that made the routing decision. EdgePathingOp (pathing operation): The specific action or operation taken. EdgePathingStatus (pathing status): Additional information complementing the EdgePathingOp. &amp;#8203;​ EdgePathingSrc EdgePathingSrc refers to the system that last handled the request before an error occurred or the request was passed to the cache server. Typically, this will be the macro/reputation list.</description></item><item><title>Firewall fields</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/firewall-fields/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/firewall-fields/</guid><description>Firewall fieldsThe Firewall fields contain rules to block requests that contain specific types of content.
&amp;#8203;​ FirewallMatchesActions Value Action Description unknown Unknown Take no other action. allow Allow Bypass all subsequent rules. block Drop Block with an HTTP 403 response. challenge Challenge Drop Issue a CAPTCHA challenge. jschallenge Challenge Drop Issue a JS challenge. log Log Take no action other than logging the event. connectionClose Close Close connection. challengeSolved Allow Allow once CAPTCHA challenge solved.</description></item><item><title>WAF fields</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/waf-fields/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/waf-fields/</guid><description>WAF fieldsThe Web Application Firewall (WAF) contains rules managed by Cloudflare to block requests that contain malicious content.
&amp;#8203;​ WAF Action Value Action Description 0 Unknown Take no other action. 1 Allow Bypass all subsequent WAF rules. 2 Block Block with an HTTP 403 response. 3 Challenge Allow Issue a Managed Challenge. 4 Challenge Drop Unused. 5 Log Take no action other than logging the event. &amp;#8203;​ Deprecated fields for internal Cloudflare use The values of these fields are subject to change by Cloudflare at any time and are irrelevant for customer data analysis:</description></item><item><title>ClientRequestSource field</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/clientrequestsource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/clientrequestsource/</guid><description>ClientRequestSource fieldThe possible values for the ClientRequestSource field are the following:
Value Request source Description 0 unknown Should never happen. 1 eyeball A request from an end user. If you want to count requests made the Cloudflare Edge, the query should filter on requestSource=eyeball. 2 purge A request made by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s purge system. 3 alwaysOnline A request made by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Always Online crawler. 4 healthcheck A request made by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Health Check system.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/glossary/</guid><description>Glossary &amp;#8203;​ Categories of terms &amp;#8203;​ Requests &amp;#8203;​ Request A request is a message that is sent between a client, or web browser, to a server. Each request that has been processed through the Cloudflare network generates a record.
&amp;#8203;​ Origin requests An origin request is a type of request that is served from the origin server. The origin server is the server that contains the original version of your website.</description></item></channel></rss>