<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workers Analytics Engine (beta) on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/</link><description>Recent content in Workers Analytics Engine (beta) on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/get-started/</guid><description>Get started with Workers Analytics EngineThere are four steps to get started with Workers Analytics Engine:
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Enable Analytics Engine for your account Log into the Cloudflare dashboard. Navigate to the Workers page. Click Set up in the right hand side bar. Click Enable Analytics Engine &amp;#8203;​ 2. Configure your dataset and binding in Wrangler All data in Workers Analytics Engine is written to a dataset. A dataset is conceptually like a table in SQL: the rows and columns should have consistent meaning.</description></item><item><title>SQL API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/sql-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/sql-api/</guid><description>Workers Analytics Engine SQL APIThe Workers Analytics Engine SQL API is an HTTP API that allows executing SQL queries against your Workers Anaytics Engine datasets.
The API is hosted at https://api.cloudflare.com/client/v4/accounts/&amp;lt;account_id&amp;gt;/analytics_engine/sql.
&amp;#8203;​ Authentication Authentication is done via bearer token. An Authorization: Bearer &amp;lt;token&amp;gt; header must be supplied with every request to the API.
Use the dashboard to create a token with permssion to read analytics data on your account:</description></item><item><title>SQL Reference</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/sql-reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/sql-reference/</guid><description>Workers Analytics Engine SQL Reference &amp;#8203;​ SHOW TABLES statement SHOW TABLES can be used to list the tables on your account. The table name is the name you specified as dataset when configuring the workers binding (refer to Get started with Workers Analytics Engine, for more information). The table is automatically created when you write event data in your worker.
SHOW TABLES [FORMAT &amp;lt;format&amp;gt;] Refer to FORMAT clause for the available FORMAT options.</description></item><item><title>Querying from Grafana</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/grafana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/analytics-engine/grafana/</guid><description>Querying Workers Analytics Engine from GrafanaWorkers Analytics Engine is optimized for powering time series analytics that can be visualized using tools like Grafana. Every event written from the runtime is automatically populated with a timestamp field.
&amp;#8203;​ Grafana plugin setup We recommend the use of the Altinity plugin for Clickhouse External link icon Open external link for querying Workers Analytics Engine from Grafana.
Configure the plugin as follows:
URL: https://api.</description></item></channel></rss>