<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bots</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/bot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/bot/</guid><description>BotsA bot is a software application programmed to do certain tasks. Bots can be used for good (chatbots, search engine crawlers) or for evil (inventory hoarding, credential stuffing).
More informationFor more background, refer to What is a bot? External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Verified bots Cloudflare also maintains an internal list of Verified Bots that are associated with search engine optimization (SEO), website monitoring, and more. The method for allowing or blocking verified bots depends on your plan.</description></item><item><title>Bot scores</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/bot-score/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/bot-score/</guid><description>Bot scoresA bot score is a score from 1 to 99 that indicates how likely that request came from a bot. For example, a score of 1 means Cloudflare is quite certain the request was automated, while a score of 99 means Cloudflare is quite certain the request came from a human.
Bot scores are available to be used in Firewall fields and with Workers to customize application behavior. For more details, refer to Bot Management variables.</description></item><item><title>Challenge Solve Rate (CSR)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/challenge-solve-rate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/challenge-solve-rate/</guid><description>Challenge Solve Rate (CSR)The Challenge Solve Rate (CSR) is the percentage of issued challenges — Legacy CAPTCHA, JS Challenge, or Managed Challenge actions — that were solved. You can find the CSR of a rule by going to its corresponding dashboard page:
For firewall rules, go to Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Firewall rules. For custom rules, go to Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Custom rules. For rate limiting rules, go to Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Rate limiting rules.</description></item><item><title>Bot Tags</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/cloudflare-bot-tags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/cloudflare-bot-tags/</guid><description>Bot TagsBot Tags provide more detail about why Cloudflare assigned a bot score to a request.
Use these tags to learn more about your bot traffic and better inform security settings.
NoteBot tags are only available to Enterprise customers who have purchased Bot Management. &amp;#8203;​ Potential values Once you enable Bot Tags, you can see more information about bot requests, such as whether a request came from a verified bot (like Bing) or a category of verified bot (like SearchEngine).</description></item><item><title>Bot Feedback Loop</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/feedback-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/feedback-loop/</guid><description>Bot Feedback LoopThe Bot Feedback Loop is a way for customers to send Cloudflare direct feedback in the case of Bot Management potentially scoring a request incorrectly. When a customer submits a False Negative or a False Positive report, Cloudflare manually analyzes this data and uses it as a training dataset for our next Machine Learning model.
&amp;#8203;​ Availability Anyone who has access to Bot Analytics is able to submit feedback.</description></item><item><title>JA3 Fingerprint</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/ja3-fingerprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/concepts/ja3-fingerprint/</guid><description>JA3 FingerprintA JA3 Fingerprint External link icon Open external link helps you profile specific SSL/TLS clients across different destination IPs, Ports, and X509 certificates.
NoteJA3 Fingerprints are only available to Enterprise customers who have purchased Bot Management. &amp;#8203;​ Analytics To get more information about potential bot requests, use these JA3 Fingerprints in:
Bot Analytics Security Events and Security Analytics Analytics GraphQL API, specifically the HTTP Requests data set Logs &amp;#8203;​ Actions To adjust how your application responds to specific fingerprints, use them with:</description></item></channel></rss>