<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Secure Web Gateway on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/</link><description>Recent content in Secure Web Gateway on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Applications and app types</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/application-app-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/application-app-types/</guid><description>Applications and app typesGateway allows you to build DNS, Network, and HTTP policies based on applications and app types. This feature gives you more granular control over how web applications are used on your network.
&amp;#8203;​ Applications When you choose the Application selector in the DNS, Network, or HTTP policy builder, the Value drop-down menu will show all supported applications and their respective app types. Alternatively, you can use the Gateway API to fetch a list of applications, app types, and ID numbers.</description></item><item><title>Domain categories</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/domain-categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/domain-categories/</guid><description>Domain categoriesCloudflare Gateway allows you to block known and potential security risks on the public Internet, as well as specific categories of content. Domains are categorized by Cloudflare Radar.
You can block security risks and content categories by creating DNS or HTTP policies. Once you have configured your policies, you will be able to inspect network activity and the associated categories in your Gateway logs.
&amp;#8203;​ Security categories Category Definition Anonymizer Sites that allow users to surf the Internet anonymously.</description></item><item><title>Identity-based policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/identity-selectors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/identity-selectors/</guid><description>Identity-based policiesWith Cloudflare Zero Trust, you can create Secure Web Gateway policies that filter outbound traffic down to the user identity level. To do that, you can build DNS, HTTP or Network policies using a set of identity-based selectors. These selectors require you to deploy the Zero Trust WARP client in Gateway with WARP mode.
&amp;#8203;​ Identity-based selectors &amp;#8203;​ SAML Attributes Specify a value from the SAML Attribute Assertion.</description></item><item><title>Block page</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/configuring-block-page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/configuring-block-page/</guid><description>Configure block pageGateway responds to any blocked domain with 0.0.0.0, and does not return that blocked domain&amp;rsquo;s IP address. As a result, the browser will show a default error page, and users will not be able to reach that website. This may cause confusion and lead some users to think that their Internet is not working.
Configuring a custom block page on the Zero Trust dashboard helps avoid this confusion.</description></item><item><title>Order of enforcement</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/order-of-enforcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/order-of-enforcement/</guid><description>Order of enforcementWith Cloudflare Gateway, you can enable and configure any combination of DNS, network, and HTTP policies.
&amp;#8203;​ Priority between policy builders Gateway applies your policies in the following order:
DNS HTTP Network DNS policies are standalone. For example, if you block a site with a DNS policy but do not create a corresponding HTTP policy, users can still access the site if they know its IP address.</description></item><item><title>WARP session duration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/enforce-sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/enforce-sessions/</guid><description>Enforce WARP session durationCloudflare Zero Trust allows you to enforce session durations on Gateway Network and HTTP policies. Once a session expires, a user will be prompted to re-authenticate with the identity provider they used to enroll in the WARP client.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Ensure that traffic can reach your IdP and &amp;lt;your-team-name&amp;gt;.cloudflareaccess.com through WARP.
&amp;#8203;​ Configure session duration You can configure a WARP session for any Allow policy. To configure a session:</description></item><item><title>Lists</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/lists/</guid><description>ListsYour lists can include up to 5,000 entries for Enterprise subscriptions and 1,000 for Standard subscriptions. A CSV file containing a list of URLs or hostnames must be smaller than 2 MB. With Cloudflare Zero Trust, you can create lists of URLs, hostnames, or other entries to reference when creating Secure Web Gateway policies. This allows you to quickly create rules that match and take actions against several items at once.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated egress IPs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/egress-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/egress-policies/</guid><description>Dedicated egress IPsDedicated egress IPs are only available on Enterprise plans. When your users connect to the Internet through Cloudflare Gateway, by default their traffic is assigned a source IP address that is shared across all Cloudflare WARP users. Enterprise customers can purchase dedicated egress IPs to ensure that egress traffic from your organization is assigned a unique, static IP. These source IPs are dedicated to your account and can be used within allowlists on upstream services.</description></item></channel></rss>