<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Migration guides on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/</link><description>Recent content in Migration guides on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Migrating a Jekyll-based site from GitHub Pages</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-jekyll-from-github-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-jekyll-from-github-pages/</guid><description>Migrating a Jekyll-based site from GitHub PagesIn this tutorial, you will learn how to to migrate an existing GitHub Pages site using Jekyll External link icon Open external link to Cloudflare Pages. Jekyll is one of the most popular static site generators used with GitHub Pages, and migrating your GitHub Pages site to Cloudflare Pages will take a few short steps.
This tutorial will guide you through:
Adding the necessary dependencies used by GitHub Pages to your project configuration.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from Firebase</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-firebase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-firebase/</guid><description>Migrating from FirebaseIn this tutorial, you will learn how to migrate an existing Firebase application to Cloudflare Pages. You should already have an existing project deployed on Firebase that you would like to host on Cloudflare Pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Finding your build command and build directory To move your application to Cloudflare Pages, you will need to find your build command and build directory.
You will use these to tell Cloudflare Pages how to deploy your project.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from Netlify to Pages</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-netlify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-netlify/</guid><description>Migrating from Netlify to PagesIn this tutorial, you will learn how to migrate your Netlify application to Cloudflare Pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Finding your build command and build directory To move your application to Cloudflare Pages, find your build command and build directory. Cloudflare Pages will use this information to build and deploy your application.
In your Netlify Dashboard, find the project that you want to deploy. It should be configured to deploy from a GitHub repository.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from Vercel to Pages</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-vercel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-vercel/</guid><description>Migrating from Vercel to PagesIn this tutorial, you will learn how to deploy your Vercel application to Cloudflare Pages.
You should already have an existing project deployed on Vercel that you would like to host on Cloudflare Pages. Features such as Vercel&amp;rsquo;s serverless functions are currently not supported in Cloudflare Pages. &amp;#8203;​ Finding your build command and build directory To move your application to Cloudflare Pages, you will need to find your build command and build directory.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from Workers Sites to Pages</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-workers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/migrations/migrating-from-workers/</guid><description>Migrating from Workers Sites to PagesIn this tutorial, you will learn how to migrate an existing Cloudflare Workers Sites External link icon Open external link application to Cloudflare Pages.
As a prerequisite, you should have a Cloudflare Workers Sites project, created with Wrangler External link icon Open external link .
Cloudflare Pages provides built-in defaults for every aspect of serving your site. You can port custom behavior in your Worker — such as custom caching logic — to your Cloudflare Pages project using Functions.</description></item></channel></rss>