<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/</link><description>Recent content in Platform on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Branch build controls</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/branch-build-controls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/branch-build-controls/</guid><description>&amp;#8203;​ Branch build controls When connected to your git source, Pages allows you to control which environments and branches you would like to automatically build. By default, Pages will trigger a build any time you commit to either your production or preview environment. However, with branch build controls, you can configure automatic deployments to suit your preference on a per project basis.
&amp;#8203;​ Skip builds Without any configuration required, you can choose to skip a build and deployment on an adhoc basis.</description></item><item><title>Build configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/build-configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/build-configuration/</guid><description>Build configurationYou may tell Cloudflare Pages how your site needs to be built as well as where its output files will be located.
&amp;#8203;​ Build commands and directories You should provide a build command to tell Cloudflare Pages how to build your application. For projects not listed here, consider reading the tool&amp;rsquo;s documentation or framework, and submit a pull request to add it here.
Build directories indicates where your project&amp;rsquo;s build command outputs the built version of your Cloudflare Pages site.</description></item><item><title>Custom domains</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/custom-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/custom-domains/</guid><description>Custom domainsWhen deploying your Pages project, you may wish to point custom domains (or subdomains) to your site.
Purging the cacheIf Page Rules or other cache settings are used on your custom domain, that may lead to stale assets being served after a new build. You can resolve this by selecting Caching &amp;gt; Configuration &amp;gt; Purge Everything in the dashboard to ensure the latest build gets served. &amp;#8203;​ Add a custom domain To add a custom domain:</description></item><item><title>Debugging Pages</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/debugging-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/debugging-pages/</guid><description>Debugging PagesWhen setting up your Pages project, you may encounter various errors that prevent you from successfully deploying your site. This guide gives an overview of some common errors and solutions.
&amp;#8203;​ Check your build log You can review build errors in your Pages build log. To access your build log:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . In Account Home, go to Pages.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Hooks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/deploy-hooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/deploy-hooks/</guid><description>Deploy HooksWith Deploy Hooks, you can trigger deployments using event sources beyond commits in your source repository. Each event source may obtain its own unique URL, which will receive HTTP POST requests in order to initiate new deployments. This feature allows you to integrate Pages with new or existing workflows. For example, you may:
Automatically deploy new builds whenever content in a Headless CMS changes Implement a fully customized CI/CD pipeline, deploying only under desired conditions Schedule a CRON trigger to update your website on a fixed timeline To create a Deploy Hook:</description></item><item><title>Direct Uploads</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/direct-upload/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/direct-upload/</guid><description>Direct UploadsDirect Uploads enable you to upload your prebuilt assets to the Pages platform and deploy them to the Cloudflare edge network. This guide will instruct you how to upload your assets using Wrangler or the Drag and Drop method.
&amp;#8203;​ Upload methods After you have your prebuilt assets ready, there are two ways to begin uploading:
Wrangler. Drag and Drop. Within a Direct Uploads project, you can switch between creating deployments with either Wrangler or Drag and Drop.</description></item><item><title>Early Hints</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/early-hints/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/early-hints/</guid><description>Early HintsEarly Hints help the browser to load webpages faster. Early Hints is enabled automatically on all pages.dev domains. To enable Early Hints for your custom domains:
Log in to Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain. Go to Speed &amp;gt; Optimization. Turn on the Early Hints toggle. Early Hints automatically caches any preload External link icon Open external link and preconnect External link icon Open external link type Link headers External link icon Open external link to send as Early Hints to the browser.</description></item><item><title>Git integration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/git-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/git-integration/</guid><description>Git integrationCloudflare supports connecting Cloudflare Pages to your GitHub and GitLab repositories to look for new changes to your project.
&amp;#8203;​ Custom branches Suppose you have a custom Git workflow that uses specific branches to represent your project&amp;rsquo;s production build. In that case, you can specify a custom branch when creating (or managing an existing) project in the Pages dashboard by going to Settings &amp;gt; Builds &amp;amp; deployments and clicking the Configure Production deployments button.</description></item><item><title>Headers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/headers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/headers/</guid><description>Headers &amp;#8203;​ Attach a header To attach headers to Cloudflare Pages responses, create a _headers plain text file in the output folder of your project. It is usually the folder that contains the deploy-ready HTML files and assets generated by the build, such as favicons. Changes to headers will be updated to your website at build time. Make sure you commit and push the file to trigger a new build each time you update headers.</description></item><item><title>Known issues</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/known-issues/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/platform/known-issues/</guid><description>Known issuesHere are some known bugs and issues with Cloudflare Pages:
&amp;#8203;​ Builds and deployment GitHub and GitLab are currently the only supported platforms for automatic CI/CD builds. Direct uploads allow you to integrate your own build platform or upload from your local computer.
Monorepos or repositories with multiple codebases/applications currently cannot use the automatic GitHub/GitLab integration to build multiple sites from the same repository. However, Direct Uploads can be used to upload a monorepo as separate Pages projects from your own computer.</description></item></channel></rss>