<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/about/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WAF attack score</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/about/waf-attack-score/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/about/waf-attack-score/</guid><description>WAF attack scoreWAF attack score is a feature that complements WAF Managed Rules.
WAF&amp;rsquo;s managed rulesets contain rules that are continuously updated to better detect malicious payloads. They target specific patterns of established attack vectors and have a very low rate of false positives. However, managed rulesets are not optimized for attacks based on variations of the original signature introduced, for example, by fuzzing techniques.
WAF attack score allows you to identify these attack variations and their malicious payloads.</description></item><item><title>Uploaded content scanning</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/about/content-scanning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/about/content-scanning/</guid><description>Uploaded content scanningWAF content scanning will scan content being uploaded to your application.
ImportantThis feature is only available for select customers on an Enterprise plan. Contact your account team to get access.
At this stage, WAF content scanning API endpoints may change on short notice.
When enabled, content scanning attempts to detect content objects, such as uploaded files, and scans them for malicious signatures like malware. The scan results, along with additional metadata, are exposed as fields available in WAF custom rules, allowing you to implement fine-grained mitigation rules.</description></item></channel></rss>