<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Types of Interconnect</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/interconnect-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/interconnect-types/</guid><description>Types of interconnectCloudflare supports two types of network interconnect: Private network interconnect and virtual private network interconnect. The network interconnect is the link between your infrastructure and Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network.
&amp;#8203;​ Private network interconnect Private network interconnects (PNI) are available at any of our private peering facilities External link icon Open external link .
Choose a PNI if you are co-located with a Cloudflare data center. We also recommend a PNI if:</description></item><item><title>Route Leak Detection</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/route-leak-detection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/route-leak-detection/</guid><description>Route Leak DetectionRoute Leak Detection protects your routes on the Internet by notifying you when your traffic is routed somewhere it should not go, which could indicate a possible attack. Route Leak Detection also reduces the amount of time needed to mitigate leaks by providing you with timely notifications.
Cloudflare detects route leaks by using several sources of routing data to create a synthesis of how the Internet sees routes to BYOIP users.</description></item><item><title>Argo for Packets</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/argo-for-packets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/argo-for-packets/</guid><description>Argo for PacketsArgo for Packets provides IP layer network optimizations to supercharge your Cloudflare network services products like Magic Transit, Magic WAN, and Cloudflare for Offices External link icon Open external link .
Argo for Packets dynamically chooses the best possible path through Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network and looks at every path back from every Cloudflare data center back to your origin, down to the individual network path. Argo compares existing Layer 4 traffic and network analytics across all of these unique paths to determine the fastest, most available path.</description></item><item><title>Bidirectional Forwarding Detection</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/bfd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/about/bfd/</guid><description>Bidirectional Forwarding DetectionBidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) is a networking protocol that constantly monitors links and BGP sessions down to the second by sending a constant stream of traffic across the session.
If a small number of packets does not make it to the other side of the session, the session is considered down. This solution is useful for users who cannot tolerate any amount of packet loss during a session.</description></item></channel></rss>