<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enable Email Routing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/enable-email-routing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/enable-email-routing/</guid><description>Enable Email Routing ImportantEnabling Email Routing adds the appropriate MX records to the DNS settings of your zone in order for the service to work. You can change these MX records at any time. However, depending on how you configure them, Email Routing might stop working. Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain. Go to Email &amp;gt; Email Routing and select Get started.</description></item><item><title>Test Email Routing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/test-email-routing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/test-email-routing/</guid><description>&amp;#8203;​ Test your Email Routing configuration To test that your configuration is working properly, send an email to the custom address you set up in the dashboard. You should send your test email from a different address than the one you specified as the destination address. For example, if you set up your-name@gmail.com as the destination address, do not send your test email from that same Gmail account. Some email providers will discard what they interpret as an incoming duplicate email and will not show it in your inbox, making it seem like Email Routing is not working properly.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/email-routing-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/email-routing-analytics/</guid><description>Email Routing analyticsThe Overview page shows you a summary of your account. You can check details such as how many custom and destination addresses you have configured, as well as the status of your routing service.
&amp;#8203;​ Email Routing summary In Email Routing summary you can check metrics related the number of emails received, forwarded, dropped, and rejected. To filter this information by time interval, select the drop-down menu. You can choose preset periods between the previous 30 minutes and 30 days, as well as a custom date range.</description></item><item><title>Audit logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/audit-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/get-started/audit-logs/</guid><description>Email Routing audit logsAudit logs for Email Routing are available in the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . The following changes to Email Routing will be displayed:
Add/edit Rule Add address Address change status Enable/disable/unlock zone Refer to Review audit logs for more information.</description></item></channel></rss>