<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloudflare for SaaS on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/</link><description>Recent content in Cloudflare for SaaS on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Plans</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/plans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/plans/</guid><description>Plans — Cloudflare for SaaS Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability Yes Yes Yes Yes Hostnames included 100 100 100 100 Max hostnames 5000 5000 5000 Unlimited, but contact sales if using over 5000. CSR support No No No Yes Custom analytics Yes Yes Yes Yes Custom certificates No No No Yes Custom origin No No No Yes mTLS support No No No Yes Non-SNI support for SaaS zone No Yes Yes Yes Custom analytics No No No Yes WAF for SaaS WAF rules with current zone plan WAF rules with current zone plan WAF rules with current zone plan Create and apply custom firewall rulesets.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/hostname-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/hostname-analytics/</guid><description>AnalyticsYou can use custom hostname analytics for two general purposes: exploring how your customers use your product and sharing the benefits provided by Cloudflare with your customers.
These analytics include Site Analytics, Bot Analytics, Cache Analytics, Security Events, and any other datasets with the clientRequestHTTPHost field.
The plan of your Cloudflare for SaaS application determines the analytics available for your custom hostnames. &amp;#8203;​ Explore customer usage Use custom hostname analytics to help your organization with billing and infrastructure decisions, answering questions like:</description></item><item><title>API reference</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>