<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How we detect phish</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/how-we-detect-phish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/how-we-detect-phish/</guid><description>How we detect phishArea 1 uses a variety of factors to determine whether a given email message, a web domain or URL, or specific network traffic is part of a phishing campaign (marked with a Malicious disposition) or other common campaigns (for example, Spam).
These small pattern assessments are dynamic in nature and — in many cases — no single one in and of itself will determine the final verdict.</description></item><item><title>Dispositions and attributes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/dispositions-and-attributes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/dispositions-and-attributes/</guid><description>Dispositions and attributesArea 1 uses a variety of factors to determine whether a given email message, domain, URL, or packet is part of a phishing campaign. These small pattern assessments are dynamic in nature and — in many cases — no single pattern will determine the final verdict.
Based on these patterns, Area 1 may add X-Headers to each email message that passes through our system.
&amp;#8203;​ Dispositions Any traffic that flows through Area 1 is given a final Disposition, which represents our evaluation of that specific message.</description></item><item><title>Language support</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/language-support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/reference/language-support/</guid><description>Language support &amp;#8203;​ Email evaluation The scanning service and verdict engines used by Area 1 are language agnostic. We provide support for Double Byte Character sets (DBCS) and UTF-8, UTF-16, and UTF-32 encoding.
&amp;#8203;​ Dashboard The Area 1 email dashboard is localized to English and Japanese.
To update your language settings:
Log in to the Area 1 dashboard External link icon Open external link .
At the bottom of the page, select the language icon.</description></item></channel></rss>