<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tunnel administration on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Tunnel administration on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ansible</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/ansible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/ansible/</guid><description>Deploy Tunnels with Ansible and TerraformAnsible is a software tool that enables at scale management of infrastructure. Ansible is agentless — all it needs to function is the ability to SSH to the target and Python installed on the target.
Ansible works alongside Terraform to streamline the Cloudflare Tunnel setup process. In this guide, you will use Terraform to deploy an SSH server on Google Cloud and create a Cloudflare Tunnel that makes the server available over the Internet.</description></item><item><title>AWS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/aws/</guid><description>Deploy cloudflared in AWSThe purpose of this guide is to walk through some best practices for accessing private resources on AWS by deploying Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s lightweight connector, cloudflared.
We will walk through how to initialize a service on a Linux VM in AWS, and route to it from another VM running cloudflared. This deployment guide does not take into account routing beyond basic security groups and default VPCs.
Prerequisites Navigate to the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link and create a Cloudflare Zero Trust account.</description></item><item><title>Azure</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/azure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/azure/</guid><description>Deploy cloudflared in AzureThe purpose of this guide is to walk through some best practices for accessing private resources on Azure by deploying Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s lightweight connector, cloudflared.
We will walk through how to initialize a service on a Linux VM in Azure, and route to it from another VM running cloudflared. This deployment guide does not take into account routing beyond basic security groups and default VPCs.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Navigate to the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link and create a Cloudflare Zero Trust account.</description></item><item><title>Docker</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/docker/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GCP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/google-cloud-platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/google-cloud-platform/</guid><description>Deploy cloudflared in GCPThe purpose of this guide is to walk through some best practices for accessing private resources on Google Cloud Platform (GCP) by deploying Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s lightweight connector, cloudflared.
Prerequisites Navigate to the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link and create a Cloudflare Zero Trust account. Enroll an end-user device into your Cloudflare Zero Trust account. Create your environmentTo start, you will need to navigate to the Google Cloud Console and create a project.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/kubernetes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/kubernetes/</guid><description>Kubernetes Kubernetes External link icon Open external link is a container orchestration and management tool. Kubernetes is declarative, so you define the end state in a .yml file. A Kubernetes cluster has two components, the master, and the workers. The master is the control plane that the user interacts with to manage the containers. Worker nodes are where the containers are deployed and run. A Kubernetes cluster is connected internally through a private network.</description></item><item><title>Terraform</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/terraform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/deployment-guides/terraform/</guid><description>Deploy Tunnels with Terraform Terraform External link icon Open external link is an infrastructure as code software tool that allows you to deploy services from different providers using a standardized configuration syntax. When creating a Terraform configuration file, you define the final state of the configuration rather than the step-by-step procedure. This allows you to easily deploy, modify, and manage your Tunnels alongside your other infrastructure.
In this guide, you will use Terraform to deploy:</description></item></channel></rss>