<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage domains on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/</link><description>Recent content in Manage domains on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Move a domain between Cloudflare accounts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/move-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/move-domain/</guid><description>Move a domain between Cloudflare accountsYou will have to move or transfer domains from one Cloudflare account to another if you:
Manage a multi-user organization and need to segment domain access by user.
Receive a Cloudflare is already hosting under a different account error.
Lose access to your email address or Cloudflare account.
If you have two-factor authentication (2FA) External link icon Open external link enabled and access to backup codes, you can use those codes to access your Cloudflare account.</description></item><item><title>Remove a domain</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/remove-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/remove-domain/</guid><description>Remove a domain &amp;#8203;​ Before removing your domain If you experience website issues, we recommend temporarily pausing Cloudflare to evaluate your website&amp;rsquo;s performance.
If you need to re-add the domain in a different account, make sure the current settings have been saved. For example, you may Import and export DNS records.
&amp;#8203;​ Actions outside of Cloudflare When you remove a domain from Cloudflare, it also prevents your domain from using Cloudflare for DNS resolution.</description></item><item><title>Redirect one domain to another</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/redirect-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/redirect-domain/</guid><description>Redirect one domain to anotherIf you have an alias domain that only forwards traffic to another domain, you can set up redirects directly within Cloudflare.
Add your alias domain (for example, previous.com) to Cloudflare.
Make sure that your alias domain has a proxied DNS A or CNAME record that properly resolves DNS queries. You may also want to include a record for the www subdomain.
Type Name IPv4 address Proxy status A @ 192.</description></item><item><title>Pause Cloudflare</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/pause-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-domains/pause-cloudflare/</guid><description>Pause CloudflareTo troubleshoot your site, you can pause Cloudflare globally. This will send traffic directly to your origin web server instead of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s reverse proxy. Paused domains do not use Cloudflare services such as SSL or WAF.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain.
Within Overview, choose Advanced Actions &amp;gt; Pause Cloudflare on Site.
Pausing Cloudflare takes five minutes or less to complete.</description></item></channel></rss>