<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Features on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/</link><description>Recent content in Features on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Datasets (tables)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/data-sets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/data-sets/</guid><description>Datasets (tables)Cloudflare Analytics offers a range of datasets, including both general and product-specific ones. Datasets use a consistent naming scheme that explicitly identifies the type of data they return:
Domain - Each dataset is named after the field it describes and is associated with a set of nodes. Product-specific data nodes incorporate the name of the relevant product, for instance loadBalancingRequests* nodes.
Adaptive Sampling - Nodes that represent data acquired using adaptive sampling incorporate the Adaptive suffix.</description></item><item><title>Filtering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/filtering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/filtering/</guid><description>FilteringFilters constrain queries to a particular account or set of zones, requests by date, or those from a specific user agent, for example. Without filters, queries can suffer performance degradation, results can easily exceed supported bounds, and the data returned can be noisy.
&amp;#8203;​ Filter Structure The GraphQL filter is represented by the GraphQL Input Object External link icon Open external link , which exposes Boolean algebra on nodes.</description></item><item><title>Sorting</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/sorting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/sorting/</guid><description>SortingYou can specify the order of the query result elements using the orderBy argument. By default, the results are sorted by the primary key of a dataset (table). If you specify another field to sort on, the primary key is also used in the sorting key, allowing results to remain consistent for pagination.
The default order for an aggregated dataset is by the fields on which the aggregated data is grouped.</description></item><item><title>Pagination</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/pagination/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/pagination/</guid><description>PaginationPagination – breaking up your query results into smaller parts – can be done using limit, orderBy, and filtering parameters. The GraphQL Analytics API does not support cursors for pagination.
limit (integer) defines how many records to return. orderBy (string) defines the sort order for the data. &amp;#8203;​ Query pages without cursors Our examples assume that the date and clientCountryName relationships are unique.
&amp;#8203;​ Get the first n results of a query To limit results, add the limit parameter as an integer.</description></item><item><title>Nested Structures</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/nested-structures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/nested-structures/</guid><description>Nested StructuresTwo kinds of nested structures that behave in special ways are supported: arrays and maps. Fields of either of these types are arrays; when they are part part of query result, which is already an array of objects, they become nested arrays.
&amp;#8203;​ Arrays Arrays behave as a special kind of single value. There is no way to paginate through, filter, filter by, group, or group by the array.</description></item></channel></rss>