<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Account setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create account</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/create-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/create-account/</guid><description>Create a Cloudflare accountTo create a new Cloudflare account:
Go to the Sign up page External link icon Open external link . Enter your Email and Password. Click Create Account. Once you create your account, Cloudflare will automatically send an email to your address to verify that email address.
&amp;#8203;​ Best practices If you are creating an account for your team or a business, we recommend choosing an email alias or distribution list for your Email, such as cloudflare@example.</description></item><item><title>Verify email address</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/verify-email-address/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/verify-email-address/</guid><description>Verify email addressFor security reasons, Cloudflare attempts to verify the email address associated with your account. You cannot perform certain tasks within the Cloudflare dashboard - for example, adding a new member or updating your communication preferences - without verifying your email.
&amp;#8203;​ When creating your account When you first create an account, Cloudflare automatically sends a message to the email address you provided for your account.
To verify your email:</description></item><item><title>Manage account access</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/manage-account-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/manage-account-members/</guid><description>Manage account accessCustomers on all plans can share account access with other members. However, the roles available to your account depend on your plan.
&amp;#8203;​ Add account members To add a member to your account:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account (you must be logged in as a Super Administrator and have a verified email address).
Go to Manage Account &amp;gt; Members.</description></item><item><title>Create billing profile</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/create-billing-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/create-billing-profile/</guid><description>Create billing profileAfter you create a new account, you might want to create your billing profile.
&amp;#8203;​ Step 1 - Add primary payment method A primary payment method is required to process payment for Cloudflare products and services. We value your confidentiality and privacy - Cloudflare does not have access to your bank, credit card, pin, or PayPal account password details.
Customers in the Enterprise plan External link icon Open external link have additional payment options such as wire and ACH as well as yearly or quarterly billing.</description></item><item><title>Available roles</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/account-roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/account-setup/account-roles/</guid><description>Available rolesWhen you add a new member to your account, you need to choose a role for that member.
The exact roles available depend on your Cloudflare plan type.
All roles and permissions have access to your account Overview. &amp;#8203;​ Non-Enterprise roles If you have an account on a Free, Pro, or Business plan, users can have the following roles:
Super Administrator - All Privileges (only one allowed): Can edit any Cloudflare setting, make purchases, update billing, and manage memberships.</description></item></channel></rss>