<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/get-started/</guid><description>Get startedTo begin using Magic Network Monitoring, complete the list of tasks below. If you are an Enterprise customer, Cloudflare can significantly accelerate the timeline during active-attack scenarios.
If you are an Enterprise customer and would like to use Magic Network Monitoring and Magic Transit On Demand together, begin by configuring Magic Transit.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Verify NetFlow or SFlow capabilities Verify your routers are capable of exporting NetFlow or sFlow to an IP address on Cloudflare’s network.</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/rules/</guid><description>RulesMagic Network Monitoring rules will allow you to monitor the traffic volume destined for IP addresses or IP prefixes on your network. You can also receive alerts if the volume of traffic arriving at specific destinations exceeds a defined threshold.
If you are an Enterprise customer using Magic Transit On Demand, you can also configure Magic Network Monitoring rules to automatically activate Magic Transit if the rule’s threshold is exceeded.</description></item><item><title>Notifications</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/notifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/notifications/</guid><description>NotificationsYou can receive Magic Network Monitoring notifications via email, PagerDuty, or webhooks.
For more information on receiving notifications via PagerDuty or using webhooks, refer to Create a notification.
Log in to your Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select Notifications. From Notifications, click Add. Locate Magic Transit &amp;gt; Magic Network Monitoring: Volumetric Attack in the list and click Select to add a notification. Enter a name and description for the notification.</description></item><item><title>Magic Transit integration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/magic-transit-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/magic-transit-integration/</guid><description>Magic Transit integrationMagic Transit On Demand customers need to know when they should activate Magic Transit to mitigate DDoS attacks, and Magic Network Monitoring solves this problem by analyzing traffic flow from your data centers and detecting DDoS attacks.
If an attack is detected, you can choose to automatically activate IP advertisement and enable Magic Transit to protect the impacted IP prefixes from DDoS attacks. This feature is refer to as auto-advertisement, and you can enable it for individual Magic Network Monitoring rules.</description></item></channel></rss>