<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aruba EdgeConnect Enterprise</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/aruba-edgeconnect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/aruba-edgeconnect/</guid><description>Aruba EdgeConnect EnterpriseCloudflare partners with Aruba’s EdgeConnect SD-WAN solution to provide users with an integrated solution. The EdgeConnect appliances manage subnets associated with branch offices or retail locations. Anycast tunnels are set up between the EdgeConnect appliances and Cloudflare to securely route traffic.
This tutorial describes how to configure the EdgeConnect device for both east-west (branch to branch) and north-south (Internet-bound) use cases.
Note that north-south traffic routed through Cloudflare’s Secure Web Gateway is an optional add-on feature set and requires a Cloudflare Zero Trust account.</description></item><item><title>Cisco Viptela SD-WAN</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/viptela/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/viptela/</guid><description>Cisco Viptela SD-WANCloudflare partners with Cisco&amp;rsquo;s 8000v router SD-WAN solution to provide users with an integrated solution. The Viptela appliances (physical and virtual) manage subnets associated with branch offices and cloud instances. Anycast Tunnels are set up between these appliances and Cloudflare to securely route Internet-bound traffic. This tutorial describes how to configure the Cisco 8000v router in the SD-WAN mode for north-south (Internet-bound) use cases.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before setting up a connection between Cisco Viptela and Cloudflare, you must have:</description></item><item><title>Cisco IOS XE</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/cisco-ios-xe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/cisco-ios-xe/</guid><description>Cisco IOS XEThis tutorial contains a configuration example for setting up an IPsec tunnel between Cisco IOS XE and Cloudflare.
crypto ikev2 proposal default encryption aes-gcm-256 integrity sha512 sha384 sha256 sha1 group 14 19 20 ! crypto ikev2 keyring CLOUDFLARE_KEY peer CLOUDFLARE_1 address $cf_anycastIP_1 pre-shared-key $tunnel_passphrase peer CLOUDFLARE_2 address $cf_anycastIP_2 pre-shared-key $tunnel_passphrase ! crypto ipsec transform-set CF_TSET esp-gcm 256 ! crypto ipsec fragmentation after-encryption ! crypto ikev2 profile CLOUDFLARE_1 match identity remote address $cf_anycastIP_1 identity local fqdn $cf_tunnel_acc_id authentication remote pre-share authentication local pre-share keyring local CLOUDFLARE_KEY lifetime 86400 no config-exchange request !</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare Gateway</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/secure-web-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/secure-web-gateway/</guid><description>Connect to Cloudflare Gateway with Magic WANYou can route traffic through Magic WAN and Cloudflare Gateway to secure Internet browsing and SaaS application access from internal users and devices.
In this tutorial, you will learn how to configure the Anycast GRE or IPsec tunnel on-ramp to Magic WAN, which connects to Cloudflare Gateway, from enterprise site routers.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before you can configure the Anycast GRE or IPsec tunnel on-ramp to Magic WAN, the following items should already be completed:</description></item><item><title>Fortinet</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/fortinet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/fortinet/</guid><description>FortinetThis tutorial provides a configuration example for using FortiOS (ver 6.x) along with Magic WAN. You can choose to configure Magic WAN with Fortigate using Policy Based IPSec, Route Based IPSec, or GRE, and all three options are listed below.
&amp;#8203;​ IPsec – Route based configuration To ensure health checks work as expected, enable asymmetric routing for ICMP. Note that enabling asymmetric routing will affect FortiGate behavior. To learn more, refer to How FortiGate behaves when asymmetric routing is enabled External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>pfSense</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/pfsense/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/pfsense/</guid><description>pfSenseThis tutorial explains how to set up a policy-based or route-based IPsec VPN with a pfSense device.
&amp;#8203;​ (Policy-based only) LAN interface configuration From the pfSense WebGUI, select Interfaces &amp;gt; LAN. Choose an interface from the Available network ports list. Select Add. The General Configuration dialog displays. Note:You may need to adjust the MSS on the LAN interface. With the selected IPsec encryption ciphers, 1406 is the idle MSS as pfSense will subtract 40 from the value you specify.</description></item><item><title>strongSwan</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/strongswan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/strongswan/</guid><description>strongSwanThis tutorial contains a sample template of the ipsec.conf file for a working IPsec tunnel configuration established between a Linux machine running strongSwan and Cloudflare’s Magic service.
This ipsec.conf file is typically located in the /etc directory of the Linux machine.
&amp;#8203;​ Configuration parameters &amp;#8203;​ Phase 1 Encryption AES-CBC with 256-bit key length AES-GCM with 256-bit key length Integrity SHA-256 Diffie-Hellman group DH group 14 (2048-bit MODP group) PRF SHA-512 &amp;#8203;​ Phase 2 Encryption AES with 256-bit key length Integrity SHA-256 Diffie-Hellman group DH group 14 (2048-bit MODP group) &amp;#8203;​ Configuration template config setup charondebug=&amp;#34;all&amp;#34; uniqueids=yes conn %default ikelifetime=4h rekey=yes reauth=no keyexchange=ikev2 authby=secret dpdaction=restart closeaction=restart conn &amp;lt;tunnel_name&amp;gt; auto=start mark = 50 type=tunnel fragmentation=no leftauth=psk left=&amp;lt;IP_ADDR_OF_LINUX_UPLINK_TO_CF&amp;gt; leftid=&amp;lt;IPSEC_ID_STRING_IN_RESULT_OF_PSK_KEY-GEN_VIA_CF_API&amp;gt; leftsubnet=0.</description></item><item><title>VyOS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/vyos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/vyos/</guid><description>VyOSThis tutorial contains configuration information and a sample template for using a VyOS device with an IPsec configuration.
&amp;#8203;​ Notes vti &amp;lt;NAME_OF_VTI_INTERFACE — Specifies the virtual tunnel interface of the IPsec tunnel. esp-group &amp;lt;NAME_OF_ESP_GROUP&amp;gt; - Defines the ESP group for encrypted traffic defined by the tunnel or defines a particular ESP policy or profile. ike-group &amp;lt;NAME_OF_IKE_GROUP&amp;gt; - Defines IKE group to use for key exchanges or defines a particular IKE policy or profile.</description></item><item><title>WARP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/warp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-wan/tutorials/warp/</guid><description>WARP on-ramp to Magic WANUse WARP as an on-ramp to Magic WAN and route traffic from user devices with WARP installed to any network connected with Cloudflare Tunnel or Magic IP-layer tunnels (Anycast GRE External link icon Open external link , IPsec, or CNI).
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before you can begin using WARP as an on-ramp to Magic WAN, you must:
Set up your Zero Trust account. Contact your account team to enable the integration between WARP and Magic WAN.</description></item></channel></rss>