<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Additional options on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/</link><description>Recent content in Additional options on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Custom nameservers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/custom-nameservers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/custom-nameservers/</guid><description>Custom nameserversWith custom (or vanity) nameservers, a domain can use Cloudflare DNS without using the hostnames of Cloudflare-assigned nameservers. For instance, you can configure ns1.example.com and ns2.example.com as nameservers for example.com.
When using subdomain support, a parent and child zone cannot share the same nameserver names. &amp;#8203;​ Availability Cloudflare domains on Business or Enterprise plans can set Custom Nameservers at Cloudflare:
Enterprise plans: Create account-level nameservers via the API Create zone-level nameservers via the dashboard or API Business plans: Create account-level nameservers via the API (after contacting Cloudflare Support External link icon Open external link ) Create zone-level nameservers via the dashboard or API &amp;#8203;​ Restrictions For both account-level and zone-level custom nameservers, you have to configure at least two custom nameservers and no more than five.</description></item><item><title>DNSSEC</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/dnssec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/dnssec/</guid><description>DNSSECDNS Security Extensions (DNSSEC) adds an extra layer of authentication to DNS, ensuring requests are not routed to a spoofed domain.
For additional background on DNSSEC, visit the Cloudflare Learning Center External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Disable DNSSEC If you are onboarding an existing domain to Cloudflare, make sure DNSSEC is disabled at your registrar (where you purchased your domain name). Otherwise, your domain will experience connectivity errors when you change your nameservers.</description></item><item><title>Analytics and logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/analytics/</guid><description>Analytics and logsWhen you use Cloudflare DNS, you can access data about DNS queries through a variety of sources.
&amp;#8203;​ Analytics DNS analytics allow you to evaluate aggregate data about DNS queries to your zone.
For a quick summary, view your DNS analytics in the dashboard:
Log into the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Select your zone. Go to Analytics &amp;gt; DNS. For more detailed metrics, you can use the Cloudflare API.</description></item><item><title>CNAME flattening</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/cname-flattening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/cname-flattening/</guid><description>CNAME flatteningCNAME flattening speeds up CNAME resolution and allows you to use a CNAME record at your root/apex domain (example.com).
This functionality is also what allows you to use a root custom domain with a Cloudflare Pages site. &amp;#8203;​ How it works With CNAME flattening, Cloudflare finds the IP address that a CNAME points to. This process could involve a single lookup or multiple (if your CNAME points to another CNAME).</description></item><item><title>Reverse zones and PTR records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/reverse-zones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/additional-options/reverse-zones/</guid><description>Reverse zones and PTR recordsEnterprise customers who control their own IP prefix(es) can set up reverse zones with PTR records to allow reverse DNS lookups.
&amp;#8203;​ PTR records PTR records specify the allowed hosts for a given IP address. They are the opposite of A records External link icon Open external link and used for reverse DNS lookups.
Historically, PTR records prevented outbound SMTP servers from being blocked by spam filters.</description></item></channel></rss>