<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Add web applications on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/</link><description>Recent content in Add web applications on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SaaS applications</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/saas-apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/saas-apps/</guid><description>Add a SaaS application to AccessCloudflare Access allows you to add an additional authentication layer to your SaaS applications. When you integrate a SaaS application with Access, users log in using your existing identity providers and are only granted access if they pass your Access policies.
This page provides generic instructions for setting up a SaaS application on the Zero Trust dashboard.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Get SaaS application URLs Obtain the following URLs from your SaaS application account:</description></item><item><title>Self-hosted applications</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/self-hosted-apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/self-hosted-apps/</guid><description>Self-hosted applicationsBefore you start
Add a website to Cloudflare Change your domain nameservers to Cloudflare Cloudflare Access allows you to securely publish internal tools and applications to the Internet, by providing an authentication layer using your existing identity providers to control who has access to your applications.
Make sure you create Access policies before connecting your application to Cloudflare. To connect your origin to Cloudflare, you can use Cloudflare Tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare dashboard SSO application</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/dash-sso-apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/configure-apps/dash-sso-apps/</guid><description>Cloudflare dashboard SSO applicationBy adding a Dashboard SSO application to your Cloudflare Zero Trust account, you can enforce single sign-on (SSO) to the Cloudflare dashboard with the identity provider (IdP) of your choice.
Once you have configured SSO, every user that wants to login with Dashboard SSO will need to exist as a member in your Cloudflare account and IdP. If there is no Cloudflare member account for this user, the request will not forward the authentication phase to the IdP.</description></item></channel></rss>