<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/get-started/</guid><description>Get started with Cloudflare Stream Before you get started:You must first create a Cloudflare account and create an API token to begin using Stream. Upload your first video Start your first live stream &amp;#8203;​ Upload your first video &amp;#8203;​ Step 1: Upload an example video from a public URL You can upload videos directly from the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link or using the API.
To use the API, replace the API_TOKEN and ACCOUNT_ID values with your credentials in the example below.</description></item><item><title>WebRTC (beta)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/webrtc-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/webrtc-beta/</guid><description>WebRTC Beta Sub-second latency live streaming (using WHIP) and playback (using WHEP) to unlimited concurrent viewers.
WebRTC is ideal for when you need live video to playback in near real-time, such as:
When the outcome of a live event is time-sensitive (live sports, financial news) When viewers interact with the live stream (live Q&amp;amp;A, auctions, etc.) When you want your end users to be able to easily go live or create their own video content, from a web browser or native app WebRTC streaming is currently in beta, and we&amp;rsquo;d love to hear what you think.</description></item><item><title>Stream API Reference</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog &amp;#8203;​ 2022-12-08 &amp;#8203;​ Faster mp4 downloads of live recordings Generating MP4 downloads of live stream recordings is now significantly faster. For more, refer to the docs.
&amp;#8203;​ 2022-11-22 &amp;#8203;​ VP9 support for WebRTC live streams (beta) Cloudflare Stream now supports VP9 External link icon Open external link when streaming using WebRTC (WHIP), currently in beta.
&amp;#8203;​ 2022-11-08 &amp;#8203;​ Reduced time to start WebRTC streaming and playback with Trickle ICE Cloudflare Stream&amp;rsquo;s WHIP External link icon Open external link and WHEP External link icon Open external link implementations now support Trickle ICE External link icon Open external link , reducing the time it takes to initialize WebRTC connections, and increasing compatibility with WHIP and WHEP clients.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/faq/</guid><description>Frequently asked questions about Cloudflare Stream Stream Stream Live &amp;#8203;​ Stream &amp;#8203;​ What formats and quality levels are delivered through Cloudflare Stream? Cloudflare decides on which bitrate, resolution, and codec is best for you. We deliver all videos to industry standard H264 codec. We use a few different adaptive streaming levels from 360p to 1080p to ensure smooth streaming for your audience watching on different devices and bandwidth constraints.</description></item></channel></rss>