<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Account setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage account members</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/manage-account-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/manage-account-members/</guid><description>Manage account membersIf your account is a Super Admin, you have the ability to add, edit, and delete users and - if those users lose their two-factor authentication (2FA) device - reset their 2FA.
&amp;#8203;​ Add user To add a user:
Log in to the Area 1 dashboard External link icon Open external link . Go to Settings (the gear icon). Go to Users and Actions. Select Add User. Enter their information, as well as their Permission level.</description></item><item><title>Escalation contacts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/escalation-contacts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/escalation-contacts/</guid><description>Escalation contactsWhenever Area 1 finds an exceptional phishing threat or Email Service irregularity behavior (compromised email servers at a partner or vendor, wire fraud tactics, and more), we try to reach out to our customers.
You can enable these special notifications through an opt-in process:
Log in to the Area 1 dashboard External link icon Open external link . Go to Settings (the gear icon). Go to Subscriptions &amp;gt; Escalation Contacts.</description></item><item><title>Manage parent permissions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/manage-parent-permissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/manage-parent-permissions/</guid><description>Manage parent permissionsWhen you set up Area 1 through a partner, that partner&amp;rsquo;s account is the parent account to your child account.
Each child account can set the level of access allowed to their account from the parent. You may want to update this setting if you are receiving troubleshooting support from your parent account.
To update parent permissions:
Log in to the Area 1 dashboard External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>SSO integration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/sso/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/sso/</guid><description> SSO integrationIn addition to standard logins (username, password, and two-factor authentication (2FA) codes), Area 1 offers support for SAML based single sign-on (SSO) logins to your dashboard.
For more details on setup, refer to the following resources:
Generic SSO guide (PDF) Okta SSO guide (PDF) Azure AD SSO guide (PDF) Cloudflare Access for SaaS</description></item><item><title>Permissions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/permissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/account-setup/permissions/</guid><description>PermissionsWhen you create a user, the available options for permissions depend on whether your account is a parent account or a child account.
&amp;#8203;​ Parent accounts Parent accounts are treated as containers with no services provisioned. User accounts created at the parent level will allow them to access any child account.
These accounts are only required for administrators who manage multiple accounts, most commonly associated with our partners.
Parent users can have one of the following roles:</description></item></channel></rss>