<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Understanding Cloudflare Web Analytics on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/</link><description>Recent content in Understanding Cloudflare Web Analytics on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Core Web Vitals</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/core-web-vitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/core-web-vitals/</guid><description>Core Web Vitals Core Web Vitals External link icon Open external link are high-level metrics designed by Google to capture the user experience. Three core Web Vitals metrics are measured: Largest Contentful Paint, First Input Delay, and Cumulative Layout Shift. Each of these metrics is automatically assigned a rating of Good, Needs Improvement, or Poor based on the industry standard methodology and testing designed by Google. Page load time statistics are supplemented by First Paint and First Contentful Paint.</description></item><item><title>Data origin and collection</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/data-origin-and-collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/data-origin-and-collection/</guid><description>Data origin and collectionWeb Analytics relies on the performance.getEntriesByType('navigation') object to collect metrics about page load performance. If Navigation Timing Level 2 is not supported, then performance.timing (Level 1) External link icon Open external link is used.
Refer to the W3C Processing Model External link icon Open external link for a visual depiction of the sequence of timing events for web page loads.
&amp;#8203;​ Data collection and reporting Web Analytics collects the minimum amount of information - timing metrics - to show customers how their websites perform.</description></item><item><title>Dimensions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/dimensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/dimensions/</guid><description>DimensionsDimensions are the labels used to describe different types of metrics or data. For example, Referer is the data collected from external links referring visits to a page, while Browser shows which browsers accessed your website.
Below you will find a list of the different dimensions you can use to filter Web Analytics:
Country: The visitor&amp;rsquo;s country. Host: The domain of the site&amp;rsquo;s URL. Path: The links within your site referring visits to a page.</description></item><item><title>High-level metrics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/high-level-metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/high-level-metrics/</guid><description>High-level metrics Visits - A page view that originated from a different website or direct link. Cloudflare checks where the HTTP referer does not match the hostname. One visit can consist of multiple page views. Page views - A successful HTTP response with a content-type of HTML. Page load time - The total amount of time required to load the page. Core Web Vitals External link icon Open external link - Higher-level metrics designed by Google to capture the user experience more completely.</description></item><item><title>Page load time summary</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/page-load-time-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/page-load-time-summary/</guid><description>Page load time summaryPage load time summary gives you an overview of how long your web page takes to load, broken down by area. To access Page load time:
Go to Web Analytics External link icon Open external link from your account home page, and choose a website. Select Page load time. Below is a list of all the components you can inspect:
Page load: The total amount of time required to load the page.</description></item><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/web-analytics/understanding-web-analytics/limits/</guid><description>LimitsCloudflare limits the number of sites for which you can track web analytics, as well as the number of rules allowed for each plan type. Refer to the following tables for more information.
&amp;#8203;​ Site limits Cloudflare limits the number of sites for which you can track web analytics when they are not proxied by Cloudflare.
Site type Limit Not proxied through Cloudflare 10 Proxied through Cloudflare No limit &amp;#8203;​ Rules limits Cloudflare limits the number of Web Analytics rules you can have by plan type.</description></item></channel></rss>