<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network policies on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/network-policies/</link><description>Recent content in Network policies on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/network-policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/network-policies/common-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/network-policies/common-policies/</guid><description>Common network policiesThe following policies are commonly used to secure network traffic.
&amp;#8203;​ Block content categories Block content categories which go against your organization’s acceptable use policy.
Selector Operator Value Action Content categories in Adult Themes, Gambling Block &amp;#8203;​ Block applications Block content categories which go against your organization’s acceptable use policy.
Selector Operator Value Action Application in Netflix Block After 7 days, view your Shadow IT analytics and block additional applications based on what your users are accessing.</description></item><item><title>SSH proxy and command logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/network-policies/ssh-logging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/network-policies/ssh-logging/</guid><description>Configure SSH proxy and command logsCloudflare Zero Trust supports SSH proxying and command logging using Secure Web Gateway and the WARP client.
You can create network policies to manage and monitor SSH access to your applications. When a device connects to your origin server over SSH, a session log will be generated showing which user connected, the session duration, and optionally a full replay of all commands run during the session.</description></item></channel></rss>