<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Migrating from reCAPTCHA</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/migrating-from-recaptcha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/migrating-from-recaptcha/</guid><description>Migrating from reCAPTCHACustomers using reCAPTCHA today can switch seamlessly to Cloudflare Turnstile. Follow the step-by-step guide below to assist with the upgrade process.
To complete the migration, you must obtain the sitekey and secret key.
&amp;#8203;​ Client-side integration Update the client-side integration inserting the Turnstile script snippet in your HTML&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; element: &amp;lt;script src=&amp;#34;https://challenges.cloudflare.com/turnstile/v0/api.js?compat=recaptcha&amp;#34; async defer&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Locate the grecaptcha.render() calls and replace the sitekey with your Turnstile sitekey. &amp;#8203;​ Server-side integration Update the server-side integration by replacing the siteverify URL.</description></item><item><title>Client-side rendering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/client-side-rendering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/client-side-rendering/</guid><description>Client-side renderYou can initialize and customize the Turnstile widget on your web page via implicit or explicit rendering.
&amp;#8203;​ Implicitly render the Turnstile widget The HTML is scanned for elements that have a cf-turnstile class name:
&amp;lt;div class=&amp;#34;cf-turnstile&amp;#34; data-sitekey=&amp;#34;yourSitekey&amp;#34; data-callback=&amp;#34;javascriptCallback&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt; Once a challenge has been solved, a token is passed to the success callback. This token must be validated against our siteverify endpoint. A token can only be validated once and cannot be consumed twice.</description></item><item><title>Server-side validation</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/server-side-validation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/turnstile/get-started/server-side-validation/</guid><description>Server-side validationCustomers must call the siteverify endpoint to validate the Turnstile widget response from their website’s backend. The widget response must only be considered valid once it has been verified by the siteverify endpoint. The presence of a response alone is not enough to verify it as it does not protect from replay or forgery attacks. In some cases, Turnstile may purposely create invalid responses that are rejected by the siteverify API.</description></item></channel></rss>