<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Client certificates on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/</link><description>Recent content in Client certificates on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a client certificate</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/create-a-client-certificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/create-a-client-certificate/</guid><description>Create a client certificateTo create a client certificate in the Cloudflare dashboard:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and application.
Navigate to SSL &amp;gt; Client Certificates.
Click Create Certificate.
ImportantYou can only use API Shield with a certificate authority (CA) that is fully managed by Cloudflare. Cloudflare generates a unique CA for each account.
If you need to use certificates issued by another CA, use Cloudflare Access to upload your own CA.</description></item><item><title>Configure your mobile app or IoT device</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/configure-your-mobile-app-or-iot-device/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/configure-your-mobile-app-or-iot-device/</guid><description>Configure your mobile app or IoT deviceThis tutorial demonstrates how to configure your Internet-of-things (IoT) device and mobile application to use client certificates with API Shield™.
&amp;#8203;​ Scenario details This walkthrough uses the example of a device that captures temperature readings and transmits them by sending a POST request to a Cloudflare-protected API. A mobile application built in Swift for iOS retrieves those readings and displays them.
To keep this example simple, the API is implemented as a Cloudflare Worker (borrowing code from the To-Do List tutorial on building a jamstack app).</description></item><item><title>Enable mTLS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/enable-mtls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/enable-mtls/</guid><description>Enable mTLSTo enable mutual Transport Layer Security (mTLS) for a host from the Cloudflare dashboard:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and application. Navigate to SSL &amp;gt; Client Certificates. To enable mTLS for a host, click the Edit link in the Hosts section of the Client Certificates card. Enter the name of a host in your current application and press Enter.</description></item><item><title>Revoke a client certificate</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/revoke-client-certificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/revoke-client-certificate/</guid><description>Revoke a client certificateYou can revoke a client certificate you previously generated.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and application. Navigate to SSL &amp;gt; Client Certificates. Click the certificate you want to revoke. Click Revoke and confirm the operation. ImportantAfter revoking a certificate, you must update any mTLS rules that check for the presence of a client certificate so that they block all requests that include a revoked certificate.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/client-certificates/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Troubleshooting client certificatesIf your query returns an error even after configuring and embedding a client SSL certificate, check the following settings.
&amp;#8203;​ Check SSL/TLS handshake On your terminal, use the following command to check whether an SSL/TLS connection can be established successfully between the client and the API endpoint.
$ curl -v --cert /path/to/certificate.pem --key /path/to/key.pem https://your-api-endpoint.com If the SSL/TLS handshake cannot be completed, check whether the certificate and the private key are correct.</description></item></channel></rss>