<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Troubleshooting on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/troubleshooting/</link><description>Recent content in Troubleshooting on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nameservers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/troubleshooting/nameservers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/troubleshooting/nameservers/</guid><description>NameserversIf you see unexpected results when changing your nameservers, review the following troubleshooting questions.
&amp;#8203;​ Is a DS record present at your registrar? You need to remove any pre-Cloudflare DS records at your registrar to update your authoritative nameservers. This will disable DNSSEC and allow Cloudflare to resolve your domain name.
You can then re-enable DNSSEC in Cloudflare and at your registrar after you have changed your nameservers.
&amp;#8203;​ Do the nameservers at your registrar exactly match the values provided by Cloudflare?</description></item><item><title>DNS_PROBE_FINISHED_NXDOMAIN</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/troubleshooting/dns-probe-finished-nxdomain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/troubleshooting/dns-probe-finished-nxdomain/</guid><description>DNS_PROBE_FINISHED_NXDOMAINIf you or your visitors experience DNS_PROBE_FINISHED_NXDOMAIN errors after you activate your domain on Cloudflare, review your DNS records in Cloudflare.
If your domain is added to Cloudflare by a hosting partner, manage your DNS records via the hosting partner. &amp;#8203;​ Background DNS_PROBE_FINISHED means that the DNS request for a resource timed out and NXDOMAIN stands for non-existent domain. Together, these messages mean that the DNS query for a specific resource could not locate an associated domain.</description></item></channel></rss>