<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alerts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/reference/alerts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/reference/alerts/</guid><description>WAF alertsThe WAF provides two types of alerts that inform you of any spikes in security events:
Security Events Alert: Alerts about spikes across all services that generate log entries in Security Events. Advanced Security Events Alert: Similar to Security Events Alert with support for additional filtering options. For details on alert types and their availability, refer to Alert types.
To receive WAF alerts, you must configure a notification. Notifications help you stay up to date with your Cloudflare account through email, PagerDuty, or webhooks, depending on your Cloudflare plan.</description></item><item><title>Phases</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/reference/phases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/reference/phases/</guid><description>WAF phasesThe Web Application Firewall provides the following phases where you can create rulesets and rules:
http_request_firewall_custom http_ratelimit http_request_firewall_managed These phases exist both at the account level and at the zone level. Considering the available phases and the two different levels, rules will be evaluated in the following order:
WAF feature Scope Phase Ruleset kind Location in the dashboard Custom rulesets
Account http_request_firewall_custom custom (create)root (deploy) Account Home &amp;gt; Application Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Custom rulesets Custom rules Zone http_request_firewall_custom zone Your zone &amp;gt; Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Custom rules Rate limiting rules Account http_ratelimit root Account Home &amp;gt; Application Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Rate limiting rulesets Rate limiting rules Zone http_ratelimit zone Your zone &amp;gt; Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Rate limiting rules WAF Managed Rules Account http_request_firewall_managed root Account Home &amp;gt; Application Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Managed rulesets WAF Managed Rules Zone http_request_firewall_managed zone Your zone &amp;gt; Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Managed rules To learn more about phases, refer to Phases in the Ruleset Engine documentation.</description></item></channel></rss>