<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authentication on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/</link><description>Recent content in Authentication on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure an Analytics API token</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/api-token-auth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/api-token-auth/</guid><description>Configure an Analytics API tokenCloudflare recommends API tokens as the preferred authentication method with Cloudflare APIs. This article walks through creating API tokens for authentication to the GraphQL Analytics API.
For more details on API tokens and the full range of supported options, refer to Creating API tokens.
To create an API token for authentication to the GraphQL Analytics API, use this workflow:
Access the Create API Token page Configure a custom API token Review and create your API token Copy and test your API token &amp;#8203;​ Access the Create API Token page To access the Create Custom Token page, follow these steps:</description></item><item><title>Authenticate with a Cloudflare API key</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/api-key-auth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/api-key-auth/</guid><description>Authenticate with a Cloudflare API keyAPI keys are unique to each Cloudflare user and used only for authentication. An API key does not authorize access to accounts or zones. To ensure that the GraphQL Analytics API authenticates your queries, retrieve your Cloudflare Global API Key.
Learn how to retrieve your API Key in the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . Learn how to retrieve your API Key using the Cloudflare API.</description></item><item><title>Configure GraphQL client endpoint and HTTP headers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/graphql-client-headers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/getting-started/authentication/graphql-client-headers/</guid><description>Configure GraphQL client endpoint and HTTP headers Launch GraphiQL External link icon Open external link . Click Edit HTTP Headers. The Edit HTTP Headers window appears. Click Add Header. Enter X-AUTH-EMAIL in the Header name field and your email address registered with Cloudflare in the Header value field, and click Save. To configure authentication, click Add Header. You can use Cloudflare Analytics API token authentication (recommended) or Cloudflare API key authentication.</description></item></channel></rss>