<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WARP on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/</link><description>Recent content in WARP on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First-time setup</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/set-up-warp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/set-up-warp/</guid><description>Set up WARP for your organizationThis is a high-level, step-by-step walkthrough on how to get started with WARP in your organization. From downloading the client to sending the first queries to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge, here is a guide on how to do it for the first time.
&amp;#8203;​ Gateway with WARP (default) This mode enables our complete suite of device security features.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Create a Cloudflare Zero Trust account. The Cloudflare Zero Trust dashboard will be your go-to place to check device connectivity data, as well as create Secure Web Gateway and Zero Trust policies for your organization.</description></item><item><title>Download WARP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/download-warp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/download-warp/</guid><description>Download WARPYou can download the WARP client from the Zero Trust dashboard. To do that, navigate to Settings &amp;gt; Devices and scroll down to Download the WARP client.
Alternatively, download the client from one of the following links after checking requirements:
&amp;#8203;​ Windows OS Ver Windows 8.1, Windows 10, Windows 11 OS Type 64bit only .NET Framework Min version 4.7.2 or later HD Space 184MB Memory 3MB Network Types WIFI or LAN Windows Release Builds External link icon Open external link Windows Beta Builds External link icon Open external link &amp;#8203;​ macOS OS Ver Mojave, Catalina, Big Sur, Monterey, Ventura OS Type 64bit only HD Space 75MB Memory 35MB Network Types WIFI or LAN macOS Release Builds External link icon Open external link macOS Beta Builds External link icon Open external link &amp;#8203;​ Linux OS Ver CentOS 8, RHEL 8, Ubuntu 16.</description></item><item><title>WARP settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/warp-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/warp-settings/</guid><description>WARP settingsWARP settings define the WARP client modes and permissions available to end users. Admins can configure these settings on the Zero Trust dashboard under Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client.
Managed deploymentsIf you are deploying WARP with device management software, we recommend only supplying organization in your deployment parameters and managing all other settings via the dashboard. Any settings you configure on the dashboard will be overridden by the local policy deployed by your management software.</description></item><item><title>Known limitations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/known-limitations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/known-limitations/</guid><description>Known limitationsBelow, you will find information on devices, software, and configurations that are incompatible with Cloudflare WARP.
&amp;#8203;​ Windows Server The WARP client does not run on Windows Server. Refer to the downloads page for a list of supported operating systems.
&amp;#8203;​ Windows Subsystem for Linux 2 The WARP client does not run on Windows Subsystem for Linux 2 (WSL2). To use WARP, fall back to Windows Subsystem for Linux 1 (WSL1).</description></item><item><title>Remove WARP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/remove-warp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/remove-warp/</guid><description>Remove WARPTo uninstall the WARP client and the Cloudflare certificate from your device:
&amp;#8203;​ Windows Go to Windows Settings (Windows Key + I). Select Apps. Select App &amp;amp; Features. Scroll to find the Cloudflare WARP application and select Uninstall. WARP is now removed from your device.
&amp;#8203;​ macOS We include an uninstall script as part of the macOS package that you originally used.
To find and run the uninstall script, run the following commands:</description></item></channel></rss>