<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CNI Setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/</link><description>Recent content in CNI Setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scope your configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/scope-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/scope-config/</guid><description>Scope your configurationCloudflare engages with your organization in an initial kickoff call to confirm the scope and timeline for the CNI setup. To prepare for the initial kickoff call, have the configuration data for the type of cross-connect you want to use with CNI ready to provide to your Customer Success Manager.
&amp;#8203;​ Private network interconnect (PNI) To set up a PNI connection, provide the following information:
Colocation facility where you want to connect.</description></item><item><title>Configure the cross-connect</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/configure-cross-connect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/configure-cross-connect/</guid><description>Configure the network cross-connectThe Cloudflare Infrastructure uses your information to configure the cross-connect, but the configuration process varies slightly for physical and virtual links. This process can take one to two weeks and can take longer depending on the provider. Your Customer Success Manager will remain in contact with you to ensure your cross-connect is on track.
&amp;#8203;​ Physical links To configure the network cross-connect for physical links, Cloudflare generates a Letter of Authorization (LOA)/service key and sends it to you.</description></item><item><title>Configure BGP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/configure-bgp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/set-up-cni/configure-bgp/</guid><description>Configure the BGP sessionAfter establishing your connection, the next steps include provisioning the Generic Route Encapsulation (GRE) IPs and configuring the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) peering information. This process takes approximately one week.
&amp;#8203;​ Provision the IP Cloudflare sends a set of IPs that you assign to your connection before Cloudflare establishes the BGP connection. The set of IPs will look similar to the example below.
Cloudflare v4: 192.0.2.10/31 Acme v4: 192.</description></item></channel></rss>