<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Encryption modes on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/</link><description>Recent content in Encryption modes on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Off (no encryption)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/off/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/off/</guid><description>Off - SSL/TLS encryption modesSetting your encryption mode to Off (not recommended) redirects any HTTPS request to plaintext HTTP.
flowchart LR accTitle: No SSL/TLS Encryption accDescr: With an encryption mode of Off, your application does not encrypt traffic between the visitor and Cloudflare or between Cloudflare and your server. A[Browser] &lt;--Unencrypted--> B((Cloudflare))&lt;--Unencrypted--> C[(Origin server)] &amp;#8203;​ Use when Cloudflare does not recommend setting your encryption mode to Off.
&amp;#8203;​ Required setup There is no required setup for this option.</description></item><item><title>Flexible</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/flexible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/flexible/</guid><description>Flexible - SSL/TLS encryption modesSetting your encryption mode to Flexible makes your site partially secure. Cloudflare allows HTTPS connections between your visitor and Cloudflare, but all connections between Cloudflare and your origin are made through HTTP. As a result, an SSL certificate is not required on your origin.
flowchart LR accTitle: Flexible SSL/TLS Encryption accDescr: With an encryption mode of Flexible, your application encrypts traffic between the visitor and Cloudflare, but not between Cloudflare and your server.</description></item><item><title>Full</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/full/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/full/</guid><description>Full - SSL/TLS encryption modesWhen you set your encryption mode to Full, Cloudflare allows HTTPS connections between your visitor and Cloudflare and makes connections to the origin using the scheme requested by the visitor. If your visitor uses http, then Cloudflare connects to the origin using plaintext HTTP and vice versa.
flowchart LR accTitle: Full SSL/TLS Encryption accDescr: With an encryption mode of Full, your application encrypts traffic going to and coming from Cloudflare but does not validate your origin certificate.</description></item><item><title>Full (strict)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/full-strict/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/full-strict/</guid><description>Full (strict) - SSL/TLS encryption modesWhen you set your encryption mode to Full (strict), Cloudflare does everything in Full mode but also enforces more stringent requirements for origin certificates.
flowchart LR accTitle: Full - Strict SSL/TLS Encryption accDescr: With an encryption mode of Full (strict), your application encrypts traffic going to and coming from Cloudflare. A[Browser] &lt;--Encrypted--> B((Cloudflare))&lt;--Encrypted--> C[("Origin server (verified) &amp;#9989;")] &amp;#8203;​ Use when For the best security, choose Full (strict) mode whenever possible (unless you are an Enterprise customer).</description></item><item><title>Strict (SSL-Only Origin Pull)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/ssl-only-origin-pull/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/ssl-modes/ssl-only-origin-pull/</guid><description>Strict (SSL-Only Origin Pull) - SSL/TLS encryption modesThis method is only available for Enterprise zones. Connections to the origin will always be made using SSL/TLS, regardless of the scheme requested by the visitor.
The certificate presented by the origin will be validated the same as with Full (strict) mode.
flowchart LR accTitle: Strict (SSL-Only Origin Pull) SSL/TLS Encryption accDescr: With an encryption mode of Strict (SSL-Only Origin Pull), all connections to the origin will always be made using SSL/TLS.</description></item></channel></rss>