<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Make API calls</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/make-api-calls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/make-api-calls/</guid><description>Make API callsOnce you create your API token, all API requests are authorized in the same way. Cloudflare uses the RFC standard External link icon Open external link Authorization: Bearer &amp;lt;API_TOKEN&amp;gt; interface. An example request is shown below.
$ curl &amp;#34;https://api.cloudflare.com/client/v4/zones/&amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt;&amp;#34; \ -H &amp;#34;Authorization: Bearer YQSn-xWAQiiEh9qM58wZNnyQS7FUdoqGIUAbrh7T&amp;#34; Never send or store your API token secret in plaintext. Also be sure not to check it into code repositories, especially public ones.</description></item><item><title>Create tokens via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/create-via-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/create-via-api/</guid><description>Create API tokens via the APIGenerate new API tokens on the fly via the API. Before you can do this, you must create an API token in the Cloudflare dashboard that can create subsequent tokens.
&amp;#8203;​ Generating the initial token Before you can create tokens via the API, you need to generate the initial token via the Cloudflare dashboard.
From the API Tokens management screen External link icon Open external link , select Create Token.</description></item><item><title>Restrict tokens</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/restrict-tokens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/restrict-tokens/</guid><description>Restrict token useAPI tokens can be restricted at runtime in two ways:
Client IP address range filtering Time To Live (TTL) constraints &amp;#8203;​ Client IP address range filtering Client IP address restrictions control which IP addresses can make API requests with this token. By default, if no filtering is applied, all IP addresses can use the token. Once an Is in rule is applied, the token can only be used from the defined IP addresses.</description></item><item><title>Roll tokens</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/roll-token/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/api/how-to/roll-token/</guid><description>Roll API tokenIf your token is lost or compromised, you can either create a new token or roll your token to generate a new secret. Rolling your API token into a new one will invalidate the previous token, but the access and permissions will be the same as the previous API token.
To roll your API token:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and go to My Profile &amp;gt; API Tokens.</description></item></channel></rss>