<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configure a rule with the Skip action on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/custom-rules/skip/</link><description>Recent content in Configure a rule with the Skip action on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/custom-rules/skip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>API examples</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/custom-rules/skip/api-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/custom-rules/skip/api-examples/</guid><description>API examples of custom rules with the Skip actionUse the Rulesets API to configure custom rules via API.
The skip action supports different skip options, according to the security features or products that you wish to skip.
The following sections provide examples for the different skip rule scenarios available for custom rules.
Take the following into account regarding the provided examples:
The &amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt; value is the ID of the zone where you want to add the rule.</description></item><item><title>Skip options</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/custom-rules/skip/options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/custom-rules/skip/options/</guid><description>Available skip optionsThe available skip options in custom rules are the following:
Skip the remaining custom rules (current ruleset)
Dashboard option: All remaining custom rules. API action parameter: ruleset. Skips the remaining rules in the current ruleset. Skip phases
Dashboard options: All rate limiting rules and All managed rules.
API action parameter: phases.
Skips the execution of one or more phases. Based on the phases you can skip, this option effectively allows you to skip rate limiting rules and/or WAF Managed Rules.</description></item></channel></rss>