<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Framework guides on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Framework guides on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy a Blazor Site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-blazor-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-blazor-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Blazor site Blazor External link icon Open external link is an SPA framework that can use C# code, rather than JavaScript in the browser. In this guide, you will build a site using Blazor, and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Install .NET Blazor uses C#, so you will need to install the .NET SDK External link icon Open external link by grabbing the newest installation from the .</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Brunch site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-brunch-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-brunch-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Brunch site Brunch External link icon Open external link is a fast front-end web application build tool with simple declarative configuration and seamless incremental compilation for rapid development.
&amp;#8203;​ Install Brunch To begin, install Brunch:
$ npm install -g brunch &amp;#8203;​ Create a Brunch project Brunch maintains a library of community-provided skeletons External link icon Open external link to offer you a boilerplate for your project. Run Brunch&amp;rsquo;s recommended es6 skeleton with the brunch new command:</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Docusaurus site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-docusaurus-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-docusaurus-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Docusaurus site Docusaurus External link icon Open external link is a static site generator. It builds a single-page application with fast client-side navigation, leveraging the full power of React to make your site interactive. It provides out-of-the-box documentation features but can be used to create any kind of site such as a personal website, a product site, a blog, or marketing landing pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Install Docusaurus To begin, with Node.</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Gatsby site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-gatsby-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-gatsby-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Gatsby site Gatsby External link icon Open external link is an open-source React framework for creating websites and apps. In this guide, you will create a new Gatsby application and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages. You will be using the gatsby CLI to create a new Gatsby site.
&amp;#8203;​ Installing Gatsby Install the gatsby CLI by running the following command in your terminal:
$ npm install -g gatsby-cli &amp;#8203;​ Creating a new project With Gatsby installed, you can create a new project using gatsby new.</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Gridsome site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-gridsome-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-gridsome-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Gridsome site Gridsome External link icon Open external link is a Vue.js powered Jamstack framework for building static generated websites and applications that are fast by default. In this guide, you will create a new Gridsome project and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages. You will use the @gridsome/cli External link icon Open external link , a command line tool for creating new Gridsome projects.
&amp;#8203;​ Install Gridsome Install the @gridsome/cli by running the following command in your terminal:</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Hexo site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-hexo-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-hexo-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Hexo site Hexo External link icon Open external link is a tool for generating static websites, powered by Node.js. Hexo&amp;rsquo;s benefits include speed, simplicity, and flexibility, allowing it to render Markdown files into static web pages via Node.js.
In this guide, you will create a new Hexo application and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages. You will use the hexo CLI to create a new Hexo site.
&amp;#8203;​ Installing Hexo First, install the Hexo CLI with npm or yarn by running either of the following commands in your terminal:</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Honojs site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-honojs-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-honojs-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Honojs site Hono External link icon Open external link is a small, simple, and ultrafast web framework for Cloudflare Pages and Workers, Deno, and Bun. In this guide, you will create a new Honojs application and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a new project Create a new project by running the following commands in your terminal:
$ mkdir my-hono-app $ cd my-hono-app $ npm init -y # Make sure Hono is installed $ npm install hono # Install the required dependencies # ESBuild is needed to bundle the hono app code # npm-run-all enables us to run multiple npm commands at once $ npm install --save-dev wrangler esbuild npm-run-all Open your project and create a src/server.</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Hugo site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-hugo-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-hugo-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Hugo site Hugo External link icon Open external link is a tool for generating static sites, written in Go. It is incredibly fast and has great high-level, flexible primitives for managing your content using Markdown and JSON.
In this guide, you will create a new Hugo application and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages. You will use the hugo CLI to create a new Hugo site.
&amp;#8203;​ Before you continue All of the framework guides assume you already have a fundamental understanding of Git External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Jekyll site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-jekyll-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-jekyll-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Jekyll site Jekyll External link icon Open external link is an open-source framework for creating websites, based around Markdown with Liquid templates. In this guide, you will create a new Jekyll application and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages. You use the jekyll CLI to create a new Jekyll site.
If you have an existing Jekyll site on GitHub Pages, refer to the Jekyll migration guide. &amp;#8203;​ Installing Jekyll Jekyll is written in Ruby, meaning that you will need a functioning Ruby installation, like rbenv, to install Jekyll.</description></item><item><title>Deploy a Next.js site</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-nextjs-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/pages/framework-guides/deploy-a-nextjs-site/</guid><description>Deploy a Next.js site Next.js External link icon Open external link is an open-source React framework for creating websites and apps. In this guide, you will create a new Next.js application and deploy it using Cloudflare Pages.
&amp;#8203;​ Consider if you need the Edge Runtime Cloudflare Pages supports full-stack Next.js projects which use the Edge Runtime External link icon Open external link or any projects which can be statically exported External link icon Open external link .</description></item></channel></rss>