<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tunnel use cases on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/</link><description>Recent content in Tunnel use cases on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SSH</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/ssh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/ssh/</guid><description>Connect with SSH through Cloudflare TunnelThe Secure Shell Protocol (SSH) enables users to remotely access devices through the command line. With Cloudflare Zero Trust, you can make your SSH server available over the Internet without the risk of opening inbound ports on the server.
Cloudflare Zero Trust offers two solutions to provide secure access to SSH servers:
Private subnet routing with Cloudflare WARP to Tunnel Public hostname routing with cloudflared access &amp;#8203;​ Set up an SSH server in GCP This example walks through how to set up an SSH server on a Google Cloud Platform (GCP) virtual machine (VM), but you can use any machine that supports SSH connections.</description></item><item><title>RDP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/rdp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/rdp/</guid><description>Connect to Remote Desktop through Cloudflare TunnelThe Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) provides a graphical interface for users to connect to a computer remotely. RDP is most commonly used to facilitate simple remote access to machines or workstations which users cannot physically access. However, this also makes RDP connections the frequent subject of attacks, since a misconfiguration can inadvertently allow unauthorized access to the machine.
With Cloudflare Zero Trust, you can enjoy the convenience of making your RDP server available over the Internet without the risk of opening any inbound ports on your local server.</description></item><item><title>Kubectl</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/kubectl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/kubectl/</guid><description/></item><item><title>SMB</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/smb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/use_cases/smb/</guid><description>Access an SMB drive through Cloudflare TunnelThe Server Message Block (SMB) protocol allows users to read, write, and access shared resources on a network. Due to security risks, firewalls and ISPs usually block public connections to an SMB file share. With Cloudflare Tunnel, you can provide secure and simple SMB access to users outside of your network.
Cloudflare Zero Trust offers two solutions for connecting to SMB servers:
Private subnet routing with Cloudflare WARP to Tunnel Public hostname routing with cloudflared access &amp;#8203;​ Set up an SMB server on Linux While SMB was developed for Microsoft Windows, Samba provides SMB connectivity from UNIX-like and BSD systems.</description></item></channel></rss>