<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Origin Rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/</link><description>Recent content in Origin Rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a rule in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/create-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/create-dashboard/</guid><description>Create an Origin Rule in the dashboard Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain. Go to Rules &amp;gt; Origin Rules. Select Create origin rule. Enter a descriptive name for the rule in Rule name. Under When incoming requests match, define the rule expression. Under Set origin parameters, define the Origin Rule settings you wish to change for requests matching the rule expression.</description></item><item><title>Create a rule via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/create-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/create-api/</guid><description>Create an Origin Rule via APIUse the Rulesets API to create Origin Rules via API. Define the route configuration in the action_parameters field.
When creating an Origin Rule via API, make sure you:
Set the rule action to route. Define the parameters in the action_parameters field according to the type of origin override. Deploy the rule to the http_request_origin phase at the zone level. Follow this workflow to create an Origin Rule for a given zone via API:</description></item><item><title>Terraform example</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/terraform-example/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/terraform-example/</guid><description>Terraform exampleThe following example defines a single Origin Rule for a zone using Terraform. The rule overrides the Host header, the resolved hostname, and the destination port of API requests.
# Change origin for API requests resource &amp;#34;cloudflare_ruleset&amp;#34; &amp;#34;http_origin_example&amp;#34; { zone_id = &amp;#34;&amp;lt;ZONE_ID&amp;gt;&amp;#34; name = &amp;#34;Change origin&amp;#34; description = &amp;#34;&amp;#34; kind = &amp;#34;zone&amp;#34; phase = &amp;#34;http_request_origin&amp;#34; rules { action = &amp;#34;route&amp;#34; action_parameters { host_header = &amp;#34;example.net&amp;#34; origin { host = &amp;#34;example.</description></item><item><title>Available settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/features/</guid><description>Available settingsThe following sections describe the available settings in Origin Rules.
&amp;#8203;​ Host header Allows you to rewrite the HTTP Host header of incoming requests.
A common use case for this functionality is when your content is hosted on a third-party server that only accepts Host headers with their own server names. In this situation, you must update the Host HTTP header in incoming requests from Host: example.com to Host: thirdpartyserver.</description></item><item><title>API parameter reference</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/parameters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/parameters/</guid><description>API parameter referenceCreate different overrides by including different action parameters in the action_parameters field:
Override type What to include Host header override host_header parameter SNI override sni object DNS record override / Destination port override origin object The same Origin Rule can have different types of overrides. Refer to Configuring several overrides in the same rule for a syntax example. &amp;#8203;​ Host header override parameters The full syntax of the action_parameters field for overriding the HTTP Host header is the following:</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/origin-rules/faq/</guid><description>FAQBelow you will find answers to the most commonly asked questions regarding Origin Rules.
&amp;#8203;​ What happens if I use both an Origin Rule and a Page Rule to perform a Host header/DNS record override? In this situation the Origin Rule parameters will override the Page Rule External link icon Open external link parameters. Consider the following example scenarios:
A Page Rule defines a Host header override, but not a resolve override (or DNS record override).</description></item></channel></rss>