<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced topics on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/advanced-topics/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced topics on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/advanced-topics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Import Cloudflare resources</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/advanced-topics/import-cloudflare-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/advanced-topics/import-cloudflare-resources/</guid><description>Import Cloudflare resourcesAn important point to understand about Terraform is that it can only manage configuration it created or was explicitly told about after the fact. The reason for this limitation is that Terraform expects to be authoritative for the resources it manages. It relies on two types of files to understand what resources it controls and what state they are in. Terraform determines when and how to make changes from the following:</description></item><item><title>Provider customization</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/advanced-topics/provider-customization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/advanced-topics/provider-customization/</guid><description>Provider customizationTerraform communicates with cloud and edge provider APIs such as Cloudflare through modules known as providers. These providers are installed automatically when you run terraform init in a directory that has a .tf file containing a provider.
Typically, the only required parameters to the provider are those required to authenticate. However, you may want to customize the provider to your needs. The following section covers some optional settings External link icon Open external link that you can pass to the Cloudflare Terraform provider.</description></item></channel></rss>