<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aggregation intervals</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/aggregation-intervals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/aggregation-intervals/</guid><description>Aggregation intervalsAggregation intervals allow you to return data in a specified interval (or frequency). If no interval is defined, data will be returned in the default aggregation interval (or frequency). As a general principle, the longer the date range, the bigger the aggregation interval.
For example, when requesting one day of data, the default aggregation interval is 15 minutes. When requesting more than one month of data, the default is one day.</description></item><item><title>Bot classes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/bot-classes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/bot-classes/</guid><description> Bot classesA bot class in Radar is a grouping of bot scores.
Scores between 1 to 29 are classified as bot traffic. Scores equal or above 30 are classified as non-bot/human traffic.
Class Description Likely automated Bot scores of 1 through 29. Likely human Bot scores of 30 through 99.</description></item><item><title>Confidence levels</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/confidence-levels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/confidence-levels/</guid><description>Confidence levelsThe result.meta.confidenceInfo.level in the response provides an indication of how much confidence Cloudflare has in the data. Confidence levels can be affected either by internal issues affecting data quality or by not having a lot of data for a given location (like Antarctica) or Autonomous System (AS).
Level Description 1 There is not enough data in this time range and/or for this location or Autonomous System. Data also exhibits an erratic pattern, possibly due to the reasons previously mentioned.</description></item><item><title>Normalization methods</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/normalization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/radar/concepts/normalization/</guid><description>Normalization methodsCloudflare Radar does not normally return raw values. Instead, values are returned as percentages or normalized using min-max.
Refer to the result.meta.normalization property in the response to check which post-processing method was applied to the raw values, if any.
&amp;#8203;​ Method Method Description PERCENTAGE Values represent percentages. PERCENTAGE_CHANGE Values represent a percentage change External link icon Open external link from a baseline period. MIN_MAX Values have been normalized using min-max External link icon Open external link .</description></item></channel></rss>