<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1 – Initialize Terraform</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/initialize-terraform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/initialize-terraform/</guid><description>Introduction to Terraform initThis tutorial shows you how to get started with Terraform. The tutorial uses an example scenario where you have a web server for your domain, accessible on 203.0.113.10, and you just signed up your domain (example.com) on Cloudflare to manage everything in Terraform.
Before you begin, ensure you have installed Terraform. You will also need to create an API Token with permissions to edit resources for this tutorial.</description></item><item><title>2 – Track your history</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/track-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/track-history/</guid><description>Track your historyIn the Initialize Terraform tutorial, you created and applied some basic Cloudflare configuration. Terraform applied this configuration to your zone because you provided your API token at the top of the cloudflare.tf file that has access to this zone.
$ head -n13 cloudflare.tf | tail -n3 provider &amp;#34;cloudflare&amp;#34; { api_token = &amp;#34;your-api-token&amp;#34; } In this tutorial, you will store your configuration in GitHub where it can be tracked, peer-reviewed, and rolled back to as needed.</description></item><item><title>3 – Configure HTTPS settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/configure-https-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/configure-https-settings/</guid><description>Configure HTTPS settingsAfter proxying a basic website through Cloudflare, you can use Terraform to adjust zone settings. In this tutorial, you will configure some optional HTTPS settings and then push the updated configuration to GitHub for posterity.
You will use a new Git branch for the changes and then merge it into the master branch before applying. On a team, you might consider using this step as an opportunity for others to review your change before merging and deploying it.</description></item><item><title>4 – Improve performance</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/use-load-balancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/use-load-balancing/</guid><description>Improve performance and reliabilityIn this tutorial, you will add a second origin for some basic round robining, and then use the Cloudflare Load Balancing product to fail traffic over as needed. You will also enhance your load balancing configuration through the use of &amp;ldquo;geo steering&amp;rdquo; to serve results from an origin server that is geographically closest to your end users.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Add another DNS record for www To get started, add a DNS record for a second web server, located in Asia.</description></item><item><title>5 – Add exceptions with Page Rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/add-page-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/add-page-rules/</guid><description>Add exceptions with Page RulesIn the Configure HTTPS settings tutorial, you configured zone settings that apply to all of example.com. In this tutorial, you will add an exception to these settings using Page Rules External link icon Open external link .
Specifically, you will increase the security level for a URL known to be expensive to render and cannot be cached: https://www.example.com/expensive-db-call. Additionally, you will add a redirect from the previous URL used to host this page.</description></item><item><title>6 – Revert configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/revert-configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/terraform/tutorial/revert-configuration/</guid><description>Revert configurationSometimes, you may have to roll back configuration changes. For example, you might want to run performance tests on a new configuration or maybe you mistyped an IP address and brought your entire site down.
To revert your configuration, check out the desired branch and ask Terraform to move your Cloudflare settings back in time. If you accidentally brought your site down, consider establishing a good strategy for peer reviewing pull requests rather than merging directly to master as done in the tutorials for brevity.</description></item></channel></rss>