<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Loss Prevention on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/data-loss-prevention/</link><description>Recent content in Data Loss Prevention on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/data-loss-prevention/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Predefined DLP Profiles</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/data-loss-prevention/predefined-profiles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/data-loss-prevention/predefined-profiles/</guid><description>Predefined DLP ProfilesCloudflare Zero Trust provides predefined DLP Profiles for common types of sensitive data. A DLP Profile is a collection of regular expressions (also known as detection entries) that Gateway will match on when scanning your HTTP traffic. Some detection entries include built-in validation checks to increase detection granularity.
&amp;#8203;​ Financial information Credit card numbers begin with a six or eight-digit Issuer Identification Number (IIN) and are followed by up to 23 additional digits.</description></item><item><title>Log the payload of matched rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/data-loss-prevention/payload-logging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/data-loss-prevention/payload-logging/</guid><description>Log the payload of matched rulesData Loss Prevention allows you to log the data that triggered a specific DLP policy. This data is stored in the portion of the HTTP request known as the payload. Payload logging is especially useful when diagnosing the behavior of DLP rules. Since the values that triggered a rule may contain sensitive data, they are encrypted with a customer-provided public key so that only you can examine them later.</description></item></channel></rss>