<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/</link><description>Recent content in Setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure rules and addresses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/email-routing-addresses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/email-routing-addresses/</guid><description>Configure rules and addressesAn email rule is a pair of a custom email address and a destination address, or a custom email address with an Email Worker. This allows you to route emails to your preferred inbox, or apply logic through Email Workers before deciding what should happen to your emails. You can have multiple custom addresses, to route email from specific providers to specific mail inboxes.
&amp;#8203;​ Custom addresses Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/email-routing-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/email-routing-dns-records/</guid><description>DNS recordsYou can check the status of your DNS records in the Settings section of Email Routing. This section also allows you to troubleshoot any potential problems you might have with DNS records.
&amp;#8203;​ Email DNS records Check the status of your account&amp;rsquo;s DNS records in the Email DNS records card:
Email DNS records configured - DNS records are properly configured. Email DNS records misconfigured - There is a problem with your accounts DNS records.</description></item><item><title>Disable Email Routing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/disable-email-routing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-routing/setup/disable-email-routing/</guid><description>Disable Email RoutingEmail Routing provides two options for disabling the service:
Delete and Disable: This option will immediately disable Email Routing and remove its MX records. Your custom email addresses will stop working, and your email will not be routed to its final destination. Unlock and keep DNS records: (Advanced) This option is recommended if you plan to migrate to another provider. It allows you to add new MX records before disabling the service.</description></item></channel></rss>