<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/</link><description>Recent content in Platform on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/pricing/</guid><description>PricingR2 charges based on the total volume of data stored, along with two classes of operations on that data:
Class A operations which are more expensive and tend to mutate state. Class B operations which tend to read existing state. There are no charges for egress bandwidth.
All included usage is on a monthly basis.
&amp;#8203;​ R2 pricing Free Paid - Rates Storage 10 GB / month $0.015 / GB-month Class A Operations 1 million requests / month $4.</description></item><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/limits/</guid><description>LimitsWe want to encourage you to build any application you can dream up, and realize that doesn&amp;rsquo;t always fit within our limits.
To increase any of our limits, please fill out our form! External link icon Open external link &amp;#8203;​ Rate limiting on managed public buckets through r2.dev Managed public bucket access through an r2.dev subdomain is not intended for production usage, and has a rate limit applied to it.</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/platform/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog &amp;#8203;​ 2022-12-07 Fix CORS preflight requests for the S3 API, which allows using the S3 SDK in the browser. Passing a range header to the get operation in the R2 bindings API should now work as expected. &amp;#8203;​ 2022-11-30 Requests with the header x-amz-acl: public-read are no longer rejected. Fixed issues with wildcard CORS rules and presigned URLs. Fixed an issue where ListObjects would time out during delimited listing of unicode-normalized keys.</description></item></channel></rss>