<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/</link><description>Recent content in Installation on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Preparing the environment</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/preparing-environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/preparing-environment/</guid><description>Preparing the environmentThere are no dependencies to install Railgun. The only external requirement is a Memcached instance for Railgun to use as a cache backend. However, you should ensure that the latest CA certificate bundle is installed for your operating system as it will be used to connect securely back to Cloudflare during activation. CentOS, Red Hat, Debian, and Ubuntu users should make sure that the ca-certificates package is installed and up-to-date via yum or apt.</description></item><item><title>Installation overview</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/installation-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/installation-overview/</guid><description>Installation overview &amp;#8203;​ Package Repository Railgun is available only for 64-bit systems. The best way of installing Railgun is via the Package Repository External link icon Open external link . Run the commands mentioned on the Package Repository page in order to set this up. Debian, CentOS, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, and Amazon Linux users may use the Railgun binary package repository. Ubuntu and Debian users will be automatically subscribed to the apt repo after installing one of the packages linked below.</description></item><item><title>Configuration and activation</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/configuration-activation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/set-up/configuration-activation/</guid><description>Configuration and activationRailgun is configured in /etc/railgun/railgun.conf (GNU/Linux). The most important directives are wan.port, which specifies the port Railgun listens on, and memcached.servers, a space separated list of host:port Memcached instances for Railgun to utilize. It is also possible to specify the full path to a single socket file for Memcached. Using a socket file is recommended for best performance if your Memcached does not require network communication. Make sure at least one Memcached instance is defined.</description></item></channel></rss>