<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/analytics/</guid><description>AnalyticsCloudflare measures the following metrics for every connection.
Metric Name Example Unit count Count of total events 1000 Count bytesIngress Sum of ingress bytes 1000 Sum bytesEgress Sum of egress bytes 1000 Sum durationAvg Average connection duration 1.0 Time in milliseconds durationMedian Median connection duration 1.0 Time in milliseconds duration90th 90th percentile connection duration 1.0 Time in milliseconds duration99th 99th percentile connection duration 1.0 Time in milliseconds &amp;#8203;​ Additional dimensions You can divide your analytics further by the following dimensions.</description></item><item><title>Configuration options</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/configuration-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/configuration-options/</guid><description>Configuration optionsSpectrum is a global TCP and UDP proxy running on Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge nodes. It does not terminate the connection. Instead it passes through the packets to the backend server.
Some of these features require an Enterprise plan. If you would like to upgrade, contact your account team. &amp;#8203;​ Application type The application type determines the protocol by which data travels from the edge to your origin. Select TCP/UDP if you want to proxy directly to the origin.</description></item><item><title>Event logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/logs/</guid><description>Event logsSpectrum logs the entire lifecycle of every client that connects through it. These event logs are available through Logpush as a separate category (dataset type spectrum_events); they are not part of HTTP log events.
For each connection, Spectrum logs a connect event and either a disconnect or error event. Details on status codes can be found below.
&amp;#8203;​ Configuring Logpush Spectrum log events can be configured through the dashboard or API, depending on your preferred destination.</description></item><item><title>Limitations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/limitations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/limitations/</guid><description>LimitationsThe following limitations apply to different protocols supported by Spectrum.
&amp;#8203;​ UDP At the moment, Cloudflare does not support packet fragmentation for UDP packets. If packets are fragmented, they will be dropped at Cloudflare’s edge.
&amp;#8203;​ Minecraft Minecraft Java Edition is supported but Minecraft Bedrock Edition is not supported.</description></item><item><title>Settings by plan</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/settings-by-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/settings-by-plan/</guid><description>Settings by planCertain fields in Spectrum request and response bodies require an Enterprise plan. To upgrade your plan, contact your account team.
Spectrum properties requiring an Enterprise plan:
Name Type Description Example origin_dns object Method and parameters used to discover the origin server address via DNS. Valid record types are A, AAAA, SRV and empty(both A and AAA).
A request must contain either an &amp;ldquo;origin_dns&amp;rdquo; parameter or an &amp;ldquo;origin_direct&amp;rdquo; parameter.</description></item><item><title>Simple Proxy Protocol Header</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/simple-proxy-protocol-header/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/reference/simple-proxy-protocol-header/</guid><description>Simple Proxy Protocol HeaderThe client source IP and port is encoded in a fixed-length, 38-octet long header and prepended to the payload of each proxied UDP datagram in the format described below.
0 1 2 3 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0 1 +-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+ | Magic Number | | +-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+ + | | + + | | + Client Address + | | + +-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+ | | | +-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+ + | | + + | | + Proxy Address + | | + +-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+ | | Client Port | +-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+ | Proxy Port | Payload.</description></item></channel></rss>