<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ethereum-gateway/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ethereum-gateway/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethereum network</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ethereum-gateway/concepts/ethereum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ethereum-gateway/concepts/ethereum/</guid><description>Ethereum networkThe Ethereum network is a distributed consensus platform that allows users to write and compute smart contracts in a distributed manner. Smart contracts are essentially Turing complete programs that are available at a unique address of the network. When the smart contract is run as part of a transaction, the result and the current state of the contract are stored in a verifiable consensus that is agreed upon by the entire network of nodes.</description></item><item><title>Node types</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ethereum-gateway/concepts/node-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ethereum-gateway/concepts/node-types/</guid><description>Types of Ethereum NodesThere are three widely known Ethereum nodes that are used: Full nodes, Archive nodes, and Light nodes.
&amp;#8203;​ Full nodes Full nodes store all the blockchain’s data and participate in block validation. Validating the blockchain includes keeping track of new blocks and computing and maintaining state changes. Full nodes, once fully synced with the network, can query all Ethereum blockchain data.
&amp;#8203;​ Light nodes A light node is much smaller than a full node and does not participate in block validation in the same way.</description></item></channel></rss>