<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Always Online</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/always-online/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/always-online/</guid><description>Always OnlineCloudflare’s Always Online feature is now integrated with the Internet Archive External link icon Open external link so that visitors can access a portion of your website even when your origin server is unreachable and a Cloudflare-cached version is unavailable. When your origin is unreachable, Always Online checks Cloudflare’s cache for a stale or expired version of your website. If a version does not exist, Cloudflare goes to the Internet Archive to fetch and serve static portions of your website.</description></item><item><title>Cache Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-analytics/</guid><description>Cache AnalyticsUse Cache Analytics to improve site performance or reduce origin web server traffic. Cache Analytics helps determine if resources are missing from cache, expired, or ineligible for caching. Cache Analytics includes filter by hostname, list of top URLs that miss cache, and a query of up to three days of data.
First, determine whether to focus on Requests or Data Transfer. The default view is Requests, which helps with understanding performance because every cache miss degrades the speed of content delivery.</description></item><item><title>Cache Deception Armor</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-deception-armor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-deception-armor/</guid><description>Cache Deception ArmorBefore learning about Cache Deception Armor, you should first understand how Web Cache Deception attacks work.
&amp;#8203;​ Web Cache Deception attacks Web Cache Deceptions attacks occur when an attacker tricks a user into clicking a link in the format of http://www.example.com/newsfeed/foo.jpg, when http://www.example.com/newsfeed is the location of a dynamic script that returns different content for different users.
This scenario becomes problematic when your website is configured to be flexible about what kinds of paths it can handle.</description></item><item><title>Cache keys</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-keys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-keys/</guid><description>Cache KeysA Cache Key is an identifier that Cloudflare uses for a file in our cache, and the Cache Key Template defines the identifier for a given HTTP request. For example, consider the following HTTP request on a TLS connection:
GET /logo.jpg HTTP/1.1 Host: www.cloudflare.com User-Agent: Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_14_6) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/77.0.3865.90 Safari/537.36 Accept: image/jpg As we can see from the example, the default cache key includes:</description></item><item><title>Cache Reserve (beta)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-reserve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-reserve/</guid><description>Cache Reserve Beta Cache Reserve is a large, persistent data store implemented on top of R2 External link icon Open external link . By pushing a single button in the dashboard, your website’s cacheable content will be written to Cache Reserve. In the same way that Tiered Cache External link icon Open external link builds a hierarchy of caches between your visitors and your origin, Cache Reserve serves as the ultimate upper-tier cache that will reserve storage space for your assets for as long as you want.</description></item><item><title>Cache Rules (beta)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cache-rules/</guid><description>Cache Rules Beta Use Cache Rules to customize cache properties of your HTTP requests. For example, create a rule to specify how long to cache a resource in the Cloudflare edge network.
&amp;#8203;​ Availability The following table describes Cache Rules availability per plan.
Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability Yes Yes Yes Yes Number of rules 10 25 50 125 &amp;#8203;​ Order and priority Cache rules are unique, unlike Page Rules.</description></item><item><title>CDN-Cache-Control</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cdn-cache-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cdn-cache-control/</guid><description>CDN-Cache-ControlCDN-Cache-Control is a response header field set on the origin to separately control the behavior of CDN caches from other intermediaries that might handle a response. You can set the CDN-Cache-Control or Cloudflare-CDN-Cache-Control response header using the same directives used with the Cache-Control.
&amp;#8203;​ Header precedence You have several options available to determine how CDN-Cache-Control directives interact with Cache-Control directives.
An origin can:
Return the CDN-Cache-Control response header which Cloudflare evaluates to make caching decisions.</description></item><item><title>Crawler Hints</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/crawler-hints/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/crawler-hints/</guid><description>Crawler HintsCrawler Hints aims to increase the proportion of relevant crawls and limit crawls that do not find fresh content to reduce the need for repeated crawls.
&amp;#8203;​ Background Search engines and similar services operate massive networks of bots that crawl the Internet to identify the content most relevant to a user query. Content on the web is always changing though, and search engine crawlers must continually wander the Internet and guess how frequently they should check a site for content updates.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/cors/</guid><description>Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS)A cross-origin request is a request for website resources external to the origin. For example, a.example.com attempts to serve resources from b.secondexample.com. CORS instructs the browser to determine if a cross-origin request, such as an image or JavaScript from b.secondexample.com, is allowed by a.example.com. The browser does not load resources that are disallowed by CORS.
Cloudflare supports CORS by:
Identifying cached assets based on the Host Header, Origin Header, URL path, and query.</description></item><item><title>Default cache behavior</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/default-cache-behavior/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cache/about/default-cache-behavior/</guid><description>Default Cache BehaviorCloudflare respects the origin web server’s cache headers in the following order unless an Edge Cache TTL page rule overrides the headers.
Cloudflare does not cache the resource when: The Cache-Control header is set to private, no-store, no-cache, or max-age=0. The Set-Cookie header exists. Cloudflare does cache the resource when: The Cache-Control header is set to public and max-age is greater than 0. Note that Cloudflare does cache the resource even if there is no Cache-Control header based on status codes.</description></item></channel></rss>