<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guide</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/get-started/</guid><description>Get started guideCloudflare Queues is a flexible messaging queue that allows you to queue messages for asynchronous processing. By following this guide, you will create your first queue, a Worker to publish messages to that queue, and a consumer Worker to consume messages from that queue.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisite: Create a Cloudflare account In order to use Queues, you need a Cloudflare account. If you already have an account, skip this step.</description></item><item><title>JavaScript APIs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/javascript-apis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/javascript-apis/</guid><description>JavaScript APIsCloudflare Queues is integrated with Cloudflare Workers. To send and receive messages, you must use a Worker.
A Worker that can send messages to a Queue is a producer Worker, while a Worker that can receive messages from a Queue is a consumer Worker. It is possible for the same Worker to be a producer and consumer, if desired.
In the future, we expect to support other APIs, such as HTTP endpoints to send or receive messages.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/configuration/</guid><description>ConfigurationCloudflare Queues can be configured using Wrangler, the command-line interface for Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Developer Platform, which includes Workers, R2, and other developer products.
Each Worker has a wrangler.toml configuration file that specifies environment variables, triggers, and resources, such as a Queue. Use the options below to configure your Queue.
Below are options for Queues, refer to the Wrangler documentation for a full reference of wrangler.toml. &amp;#8203;​ Producer These options should be used when a Worker wants to send messages to a Queue.</description></item><item><title>Limits</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/limits/</guid><description>LimitsMany of these limits will increase during the Public Beta of Queues. If you have questions about a certain limit, please reach out. Feature Limit Queues 10 per account Maximum message size 128 KB Maximum message retries 100 Maximum batch size 100 messages Maximum batch wait time 30 seconds Maximum message throughput 1 100 messages per second Maximum retention period 4 days (96 hours) 1 This is a limit that we will increase, and aspire to effectively eliminate in the future.</description></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/pricing/</guid><description>PricingCloudflare Queues requires the Workers Paid plan to use, but does not increase your monthly subscription cost. Cloudflare Queues charges for the total number of operations against each of your queues during a given month.
An operation is counted for each 64 KB of data that is written, read, or deleted. Messages larger than 64 KB are charged as if they were multiple messages: for example, a 65 KB message and a 127 KB message would both incur two operation charges when written, read, or deleted.</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog &amp;#8203;​ 2022-12-12 &amp;#8203;​ Increased per-account limits Queues now allows developers to create up to 100 queues per account, up from the initial beta limit of 10 per account. This limit will continue to increase over time.
&amp;#8203;​ 2022-12-13 &amp;#8203;​ sendBatch support The JavaScript API for Queue producers now includes a sendBatch method which supports sending up to 100 messages at a time.</description></item></channel></rss>