<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/about/</guid><description>AboutOne of the major advantages of using Cloudflare is that cacheable content (such as images, JavaScript, CSS, and HTML) is both cached by Cloudflare and delivered from our data centers around the world. Because Cloudflare has data centers covering the entire globe, cached content gets delivered quickly to web surfers wherever they are (and overcomes latency problems).
But only about 66% of content is cacheable. The other 34% must be obtained from the real origin web server.</description></item><item><title>License agreement</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/license-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/license-agreement/</guid><description>LicenseSERVICES AGREEMENT
Your installation of this software is symbol of your signature indicating that you accept the terms of this Services Agreement (this “Agreement”). This Agreement is a legal agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity) and CloudFlare Inc. for the services being provided to you by CloudFlare or its authorized representative (the “Services”), including any computer software and any associated media, printed materials, and “online” or electronic documentation provided in connection with the Services (the “Software” and together with the Services are hereinafter collectively referred to as the “Solution”).</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog* Apr 23 2018 Cloudflare Inc &amp;lt;help@cloudflare.com&amp;gt; - 5.3.3 - Uses go 1.10.1 * Mar 12 2018 Cloudflare Inc &amp;lt;help@cloudflare.com&amp;gt; - 5.3.2 - Passthrough URIs with invalid percent encoding * Nov 28 2017 Cloudflare Inc &amp;lt;help@cloudflare.com&amp;gt; - 5.3.1 - Fix IPv6 connections sometimes going to the wrong port * Nov 8 2016 CloudFlare Inc &amp;lt;help@cloudflare.com&amp;gt; - 5.3.0 - Improve rg-listener.conf format and help text - Standardise error codes for origin failures - Return HTTP 527 for communication errors between sender and listener - Set railgun user agent if none is specified by client - Add Memcached as package dependency * Dec 16 2015 CloudFlare Inc &amp;lt;help@cloudflare.</description></item><item><title>API reference</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>