<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Methods on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/</link><description>Recent content in Methods on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TXT</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/txt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/txt/</guid><description>TXT DCV methodTXT record validation requires the creation of a TXT record in the hostname&amp;rsquo;s authoritative DNS. &amp;#8203;​ Zone setups &amp;#8203;​ Full zones Certificates on full zones - whether using a wildcard hostname or not - will be automatically renewed and validated without any action from you. Cloudflare can complete DCV on your behalf by serving the TXT DCV tokens. &amp;#8203;​ Partial zones For partial zones1, the process depends on whether the certificate uses a wildcard hostname.</description></item><item><title>Email</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/email/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/email/</guid><description>Email DCV methodEmail based validation will send an approval email to the contacts listed for a given domain in WHOIS, along with the following addresses: admin@, administrator@, hostmaster@, postmaster@, and webmaster@. With the upcoming change to certificates issued by DigiCert, email DCV will soon be unsupported. &amp;#8203;​ Limitations Based on your chosen Certificate Authority, you may not be able to use email verification with advanced certificates.
Selecting Let’s Encrypt as a CA limits a certificate to a TXT Certificate validation method, 90 days for the Certificate Validity Period, two host entries (one for the zone name and one for the subdomain wildcard of the zone name, such as example.</description></item><item><title>HTTP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/http/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/changing-dcv-method/methods/http/</guid><description>HTTP DCV methodWhen you choose HTTP DCV, Cloudflare automatically adds a verification HTTP token to your domain.
Only use this method if your domain can tolerate a few minutes of downtime.
&amp;#8203;​ Limitations HTTP DCV is only available for proxied domains.
HTTP DCV validation also does not work for wildcard certificates or certificates with multiple SANs.
If you want to use wildcard certificates or pre-validate your certificate — either to avoid downtime or prevent any issuance errors — use TXT validation.</description></item></channel></rss>