<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business email compromise (BEC) on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/enhanced-detections/business-email-compromise/</link><description>Recent content in Business email compromise (BEC) on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/enhanced-detections/business-email-compromise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Office 365 directory integration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/enhanced-detections/business-email-compromise/o365-directory-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/enhanced-detections/business-email-compromise/o365-directory-guide/</guid><description>Office 365 directory integrationCloudflare Area 1 can integrate with Office 365 to retrieve user and group information. This can be used to enforce the Business Email Compromise configuration to prevent user impersonation.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Authorize Area 1 with Office 365 for Directory Access You need to authorize Cloudflare Area 1 to make connections into your Office 365 tenant External link icon Open external link to retrieve your directory details. The account used to authorize will require the Privileged authentication admin and Privileged role admin roles.</description></item><item><title>Google Workspaces directory integration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/enhanced-detections/business-email-compromise/gworkspaces-directory-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/email-security/email-configuration/enhanced-detections/business-email-compromise/gworkspaces-directory-guide/</guid><description>Gmail directory integrationCloudflare Area 1 can integrate with Google to retrieve user and group information. This can be used to enforce the Business Email Compromise configuration to prevent user impersonation.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Create a service account in Google for Area 1 Directory Integration You need to authorize Cloudflare Area 1 to make connections into your Google tenant to retrieve your directory details. Cloudflare recommends that you create a service account for this purpose.</description></item></channel></rss>