<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analytics on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/</link><description>Recent content in Analytics on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Network Discovery</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/private-network-discovery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/private-network-discovery/</guid><description>Private Network DiscoveryThe Private Network Discovery report gives you visibility over the users and applications that live on you private network. This information enables you to create identity and device-driven Zero Trust policies in Cloudflare Zero Trust, so that you can have control over the security of your private network.
On the Private Network Discovery report, you can gather information on what applications are accessed in your private network and who accessed it.</description></item><item><title>Shadow IT Discovery</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/access/</guid><description>Shadow IT DiscoveryThe Zero Trust Shadow IT Discovery page gives you visibility over which SaaS applications your end users are visiting. This information enables you to create the appropriate Zero Trust or Secure Web Gateway policies in Cloudflare Zero Trust, so that you can have control over the security of your users and data.
On the Shadow IT Discovery page, you can gather information on the application status and application type of the applications visited by your users.</description></item><item><title>Gateway Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/gateway/</guid><description>Gateway AnalyticsTo see the top Allowed and Blocked requests across all of your DNS locations, navigate to Analytics &amp;gt; Gateway. You can filter the data by selecting a specific location and/or time.
Requests — This chart shows an overview of the number of requests made by end users within the time period you specify. It shows a breakdown of requests based on the decision Gateway took (either Allowed or Blocked).</description></item><item><title>User logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/users/</guid><description>User logsCloudflare Zero Trust allows you to consult a comprehensive list of users who have authenticated to Cloudflare Zero Trust. For each user that logged in, you can see their name, their email address, and whether they’re actively utilizing a seat in both Access and Gateway.
To see your user list, navigate to My Team &amp;gt; Users.
&amp;#8203;​ Revoke user sessions Clicking the Revoke button next to a user will terminate all currently active sessions for that user, and revoke access to all their connected devices.</description></item></channel></rss>