<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BYOIP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/byoip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/byoip/</guid><description>BYOIPWhen creating a Spectrum application, Cloudflare normally assigns an arbitrary IP from Cloudflare’s IP pool to your application. If you want to be explicit in your network setup or use your own IP addresses, BYOIP with Spectrum allows you to do just that.
BYOIP stands for Bring Your Own IP. If you own an IP prefix you can migrate it to Cloudflare. After migration, Cloudflare broadcasts your IP prefix and traffic is routed to the global Cloudflare network.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare Load Balancer</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/load-balancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/load-balancer/</guid><description>Cloudflare Load BalancerYou can configure Spectrum and Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Load Balancing to provide TCP healthchecks, failover, and traffic steering to bring resiliency to your Spectrum applications. To prevent issues with DNS resolution for a Spectrum application, do not use the same Spectrum hostname as a current Load Balancing hostname.
NoteThis feature requires an Enterprise plan. If you would like to upgrade, contact your account team. &amp;#8203;​ TCP health checks You can configure Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Load Balancer to probe any TCP port for an accepted connection, which is in addition to HTTP and HTTPS probing capabilities.</description></item><item><title>DDoS Protection for Spectrum</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/ddos-for-spectrum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/ddos-for-spectrum/</guid><description>DDoS Protection for SpectrumSpectrum provides DDoS Protection at layers 3-4 of the OSI model External link icon Open external link , that is against TCP and UDP based DDoS attacks.
Spectrum works as a layer 4 reverse proxy, therefore a proper TCP connection must be first established before traffic is proxied to the origin. This moves any impact of SYN or SYN-ACK reflection attacks to the Cloudflare edge. Additionally, by using Spectrum in front of your application, your origin IP is concealed — preventing attackers from targeting your origin server directly.</description></item><item><title>FTP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/ftp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/ftp/</guid><description>FTPEnabling Spectrum for FTP is not straightforward due to the implementation of the protocol. This guide gives an overview of the intricacies of FTP and under which circumstances you can enable Spectrum for your FTP service.
This feature requires an Enterprise plan. If you would like to upgrade, contact your account team. &amp;#8203;​ How FTP Operates FTP leverages two different sockets, one for issuing commands and the other for actual data transfer.</description></item><item><title>Static IP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/static-ip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/spectrum/about/static-ip/</guid><description>Static IPWhen you create a Spectrum application, you are assigned an IP. These IPs are normally dynamic, meaning that they will change over time. But, for instance, if you want to set up Firewall rules for specific IPs, you may want to use static IPs. A static IP, like a physical street address can tell other computers or servers on the Internet where a specific computer is located or connected.</description></item></channel></rss>