<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Basic tasks on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/</link><description>Recent content in Basic tasks on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Find zone and account IDs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/find-account-and-zone-ids/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/find-account-and-zone-ids/</guid><description>Find zone and account IDsOnce you set up a new account and add your domain to Cloudflare, you may need access to your zone and account IDs for API operations.
To find your zone and account IDs:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain.
On the Overview page (the landing page for your domain), find the API section.</description></item><item><title>Manage subdomains</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-subdomains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/manage-subdomains/</guid><description>Manage subdomainsOnce you have added your domain to Cloudflare and updated your nameservers, you also might want to set up a subdomain.
Most subdomains serve a specific purpose within the overall context of your website. For example, blog.example.com might be your blog, support.example.com could be your customer help portal, and store.example.com would be your e-commerce site.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a subdomain If you have already added a subdomain at your host, create a corresponding DNS A or CNAME record for that subdomain (blog, store).</description></item><item><title>Interacting with Cloudflare</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/interact-with-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/interact-with-cloudflare/</guid><description>How to interact with CloudflareOnce you set up an account, you have several ways to interact with Cloudflare.
&amp;#8203;​ Without code If you prefer working without code, you can manage your account and domain settings through the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link .
If your domain was added to Cloudflare by a hosting partner, manage your DNS records via the hosting partner. &amp;#8203;​ With code For those who prefer to interact with Cloudflare programmatically, you can use several methods:</description></item><item><title>Access Cloudflare resources</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/access-cloudflare-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/access-cloudflare-resources/</guid><description>Access Cloudflare resourcesAs you get started with Cloudflare, you may want to take advantage of the following resources.
&amp;#8203;​ Documentation Resource Description Product docs Read product how-to guides and developer quickstarts. Support Knowledgebase External link icon Open external link . Find common troubleshooting guides and — if included in your plan — contact Support External link icon Open external link . Learning center External link icon Open external link Get resources on cyber security and how the Internet works.</description></item><item><title>Access compliance documentation</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/access-compliance-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/access-compliance-docs/</guid><description>Access compliance documentationSuper Administrators can access common compliance documentation — for topics like PCI, SOC 2, ISO, and more — through the Cloudflare dashboard.
To access compliance documentation:
Log into the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account where you are a Super Administrator. Go to Support &amp;gt; Compliance Documents. If you have not accessed this page before, read the confidentiality statement and click I Agree.</description></item><item><title>Test speed</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/test-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/test-speed/</guid><description>Test speedCloudflare offers several tools to test the speed of your website, as well as the speed of your Internet connection.
&amp;#8203;​ Test website speed &amp;#8203;​ Using Cloudflare Once your domain is active on Cloudflare, you can run speed tests within the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link .
This speed test will provide information about critical loading times, performance with and without Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s proxy, and recommended optimizations.</description></item><item><title>Use Cloudflare without changing nameservers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/cloudflare-without-changing-nameservers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/basic-tasks/cloudflare-without-changing-nameservers/</guid><description> Use Cloudflare without changing nameserversIf you cannot change your domain nameservers, you can still use Cloudflare on your website by:
Activating Cloudflare through a certified hosting partner External link icon Open external link . Using a partial zone setup.</description></item></channel></rss>