<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet Content Provider (ICP)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/concepts/icp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/concepts/icp/</guid><description>Internet Content Provider (ICP)Internet Content Provider (ICP) is a licensing regime instated by the Telecommunications Regulations of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China (中华人民共和国电信条例), promulgated in September 2000.
Under ICP, all websites with their own domain name that operate inside China must obtain a license, whether hosted on a server in mainland China or provided to visitors from China via a CDN). Licenses are issued at the provincial level.
Local government requires that all domains have valid ICP licenses to onboard Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s China Network.</description></item><item><title>China Authoritative DNS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/concepts/china-dns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/china-network/concepts/china-dns/</guid><description>China Authoritative DNSCloudflare is able to deploy DNS service in mainland China to improve the Time to First Byte (TTFB) performance. With this deployment, the DNS query will be resolved in mainland China instead of global DNS servers.
&amp;#8203;​ When to use Before you enable China Authoritative DNS, you should confirm that over 90% of the traffic is coming from China. After you enable China Authoritative DNS, all the global DNS requests will be routed to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s servers in China.</description></item></channel></rss>