<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tenant structure</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/structure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/structure/</guid><description>Tenant structureCloudflare helps Channel and Alliance partners manage their and their customers&amp;rsquo; accounts through a Tenant structure.
&amp;#8203;​ Tenants and Tenant admins A Tenant is a special type of Cloudflare account that contains other accounts and resources. Once you sign a partner agreement with Cloudflare, we create a special Tenant account and then add your user to that account as a Tenant admin. Cloudflare can add multiple users as Tenant admins upon request.</description></item><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/get-started/</guid><description>Get startedHaving access to Cloudflare’s provisioning capabilities allows you to more easily create and manage Cloudflare accounts. The following steps will get you started on making API calls to provision accounts, users, and services.
&amp;#8203;​ Before you begin &amp;#8203;​ Channel and Alliance partner account setup Before using the Tenant API, you need to create an account, verify your email address, and add your billing information.
After you sign your partner agreement with Cloudflare, Cloudflare will add certain entitlements to your account that allow you to provision and manage custom accounts.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/tenant/glossary/</guid><description>GlossaryThe following terms are used throughout the Tenant API docs. For more details on how these concepts interact with each other, refer to Tenant structure.
&amp;#8203;​ Tenant A Tenant is a special type of Cloudflare account that contains other accounts and resources. &amp;#8203;​ Tenant admin Once you sign a partner agreement with Cloudflare, we create a special Tenant account and then add your user to that account as a Tenant admin.</description></item></channel></rss>