<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HTTP DDoS Attack Protection on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/</link><description>Recent content in HTTP DDoS Attack Protection on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/configure-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/configure-dashboard/</guid><description>Configure HTTP DDoS Attack Protection in the dashboardYou can customize the action and sensitivity of the rules in the HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset in the following ways:
Configure all the rules in the ruleset Configure one or more rules Tag and rule configurations have greater priority than ruleset configurations.
For more information on the available parameters and allowed values, refer to Managed ruleset parameters.
Important note for API usersThe API allows you to specify a custom rule expression so that a configuration (or override) only applies to a subset of incoming requests.</description></item><item><title>Configure via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/configure-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/configure-api/</guid><description>Configure HTTP DDoS Attack Protection via APIConfigure the HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset by defining overrides using the Rulesets API.
Each zone has the HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset enabled by default. This means that you do not need to deploy the managed ruleset to the ddos_l7 phase ruleset explicitly. You only have to create a rule in the phase ruleset to deploy the managed ruleset if you need to configure overrides.</description></item><item><title>Rule categories</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/rule-categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/rule-categories/</guid><description>Rule categoriesRules in the HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset belong to the following categories (also known as tags):
Name Description botnets Rules for requests from known botnets, with very high accuracy and low risk of false positives. It is recommended that you keep these rules enabled. unusual-requests Rules for requests with suspicious characteristics that are not usually seen in legitimate traffic. advanced Rules related to features available to Advanced DDoS Protection customers, such as Adaptive DDoS Protection.</description></item><item><title>Parameters</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/override-parameters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/http/override-parameters/</guid><description>Ruleset parametersConfigure the HTTP DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset to change the action applied to a given attack or modify the sensitivity level of the detection mechanism. You can configure the managed ruleset in the Cloudflare dashboard or define overrides via Rulesets API.
The available parameters are the following:
Action Sensitivity Level &amp;#8203;​ Action API property name: &amp;quot;action&amp;quot;.
The action that will be performed for requests that match specific rules of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s DDoS mitigation services.</description></item></channel></rss>