<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Logpush</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/about/</guid><description>LogpushLogpush delivers logs in less than one minute with batches of no more than 100,000 records per file. This limit may be raised in the future. There is no minimum batch size, and Logpush may deliver files more than one time per minute.
Prior to mid-2020, Logpush sent logs once every five minutes (referred to as Logpush v1). The change to more frequent log pushing allows Cloudflare to deliver information to you as close to real time as possible in smaller files.</description></item><item><title>Edge Log Delivery</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/edge-log-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/edge-log-delivery/</guid><description>Edge Log DeliveryEdge Log Delivery allows customers to send logs directly from Cloudflare’s edge to their destination of choice. Logs are delivered in under 10 seconds. Compared to Logpush, Edge Log Delivery sends logs with lower latency, more frequently and in smaller batches.
For Data Localization Suite External link icon Open external link customers, Edge Log Delivery can be configured to deliver logs directly to your destination without first flowing through either of our US or EU core data centers.</description></item><item><title>Instant Logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/instant-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/instant-logs/</guid><description>Instant LogsInstant Logs allows Cloudflare customers to access a live stream of the traffic for their domain from the Cloudflare dashboard or from a command-line interface (CLI). Seeing data in real time allows you to investigate an attack, troubleshoot, debug or test out changes made to your network. Instant Logs is lightweight, simple to use and does not require any additional setup.
&amp;#8203;​ Availability Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability No No Yes Yes &amp;#8203;​ Instant Logs on the Cloudflare dashboard Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>R2 Log Retrieval</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/r2-log-retrieval/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/r2-log-retrieval/</guid><description>R2 Log RetrievalCloudflare’s Log Retrieval API allows you to query logs from R2 by providing a time range. This functionality is available in beta via the API documented here.
&amp;#8203;​ Before getting started Set up a Logpush to R2 job. Create an R2 access key with at least R2 read permissions. Ensure that you have Logshare read permissions. Alternatively, create a Cloudflare API token with the following permissions: Account scope Logs read permissions &amp;#8203;​ Authentication The following headers are required for all API calls:</description></item></channel></rss>