<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sourcing Kit (beta) on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/</link><description>Recent content in Sourcing Kit (beta) on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enable Sourcing Kit</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/enable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/enable/</guid><description>Enable Sourcing KitEnabling Sourcing Kit will set it up with the necessary information to start importing images from your Amazon S3 account.
&amp;#8203;​ Create your first import job Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account. Go to Images &amp;gt; Sourcing Kit. Select Import images to create an import job. In Source name give your source an appropriate name. In Amazon S3 bucket information enter the S3&amp;rsquo;s bucket name where your images are stored.</description></item><item><title>Edit sources</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/edit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/edit/</guid><description>Edit source detailsThe Sourcing Kit main page has a list of all the import jobs and sources you have defined. This is where you can edit details for your sources or abort running import jobs.
&amp;#8203;​ Source details You can learn more about your sources by selecting the Sources tab on the Sourcing Kit dashboard. Use this option to rename or delete your sources.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account.</description></item><item><title>Credentials</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/credentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/sourcing-kit/credentials/</guid><description>Amazon S3 credentialsTo migrate images from Amazon S3, Sourcing Kit requires access permissions to your bucket. While you can use any AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) user credentials with the correct permissions to create a Sourcing Kit source, Cloudflare recommends that you create a user with a narrow set of permissions.
To create the correct Sourcing Kit permissions:
Log in to your AWS IAM account.
Create a policy with the following format (replace &amp;lt;BUCKET_NAME&amp;gt; with the bucket you want to grant access to):</description></item></channel></rss>