<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/analytics/</guid><description>Magic Firewall Analytics &amp;#8203;​ GraphQL Analytics Use the GraphQL Analytics API to view data for requests passing through Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network. For more information about using the GraphQL Analytics API and getting started, refer to GraphQL Analytics API.</description></item><item><title>List types</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/list-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/list-types/</guid><description>List types &amp;#8203;​ Threat intelligence Cloudflare sees approximately 39 million HTTP requests each second and blocks 126 billion cyber threats each day. Cloudflare uses that data to detect malicious actors on the Internet and turns that information into a list of known malicious IP addresses. Cloudflare also integrates with a number of third-party vendors to augment the coverage.
The threat intelligence feed categories include Malware, Anonymizer, and Botnet Command-and-Control centers.</description></item><item><title>Traffic types</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/traffic-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/traffic-types/</guid><description>Traffic typesMagic Firewall enables you to allow or block traffic on a variety of packet characteristics, such as source and destination IP, source and destination port, protocol, packet length, and bit field match.
Magic Firewall supports layers three and four — network and transport — protocols such as TCP, UDP, and ICMP. Any type of layer three or four protocols can go through Magic Firewall and then be matched on those protocols.</description></item><item><title>IDS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/ids/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/ids/</guid><description>Intrusion Detection Systems (IDS)Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Intrusion Detection System (IDS) is an Advanced Magic Firewall feature you can use to actively monitor for a wide range of known threat signatures in your traffic. An IDS expands the security coverage of a firewall to analyze traffic against a broader threat database, detecting a variety of sophisticated attacks such as ransomware, data exfiltration, and network scanning based on signatures or “fingerprints” in network traffic.</description></item><item><title>Ruleset logic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/ruleset-logic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-firewall/about/ruleset-logic/</guid><description>Magic Firewall ruleset logicMagic Firewall rules are performed after Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s DDoS mitigations have been applied. The two systems are independent, and therefore, permitting traffic inside Magic Firewall does not allow it within our DDoS mitigations. Traffic can still be blocked by DDoS mitigations that are applied first in the flow through Cloudflare’s systems.
By default, Magic Firewall permits all traffic until explicitly blocked by a rule. If no rules are configured, all traffic is permitted after Cloudflare’s DDoS mitigations have been applied.</description></item></channel></rss>