<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analytics integrations on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/</link><description>Recent content in Analytics integrations on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Datadog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/datadog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/datadog/</guid><description>DatadogThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare metrics using the Cloudflare Integration tile for Datadog External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Overview Before viewing the Cloudflare dashboard in Datadog, note that this integration:
Is available to all Cloudflare customer plans (Free, Pro, Business and Enterprise) Is based on the Cloudflare Analytics API Provides Cloudflare web traffic and DNS metrics only Does not feature data coming from request logs stored in Cloudflare Logs &amp;#8203;​ Task 1 - Install the Cloudflare App To install the Cloudflare App for Datadog:</description></item><item><title>Elastic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/elastic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/elastic/</guid><description>ElasticThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare Logs External link icon Open external link using Elastic and Kibana.
&amp;#8203;​ Overview If you have not used Cloudflare Logs before, refer to the Logs documentation for more details. Contact your Cloudflare Customer Account Team to enable logs for your account.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before sending your Cloudflare log data to Elastic, make sure that you:
Have an existing Elastic instance (versions 6.x and 7.</description></item><item><title>Google Cloud</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/google-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/google-cloud/</guid><description>Google Cloud &amp;#8203;​ Overview This tutorial covers how to configure certain Google Cloud Platform (GCP) components so that you can analyze your Cloudflare Logs data.
Before proceeding, you need to enable Cloudflare Logpush in Google Cloud Storage to ensure your log data is available for analyzing.
The components we&amp;rsquo;ll use in this tutorial include:
Google Cloud Function to import logs from Google Cloud Storage to Google BigQuery Google BigQuery to make log data available to the reporting engine, and Google Data Studio to run interactive reports The following diagram depicts how data flows from Cloudflare Logs through the different components of the Google Cloud Platform discussed in this tutorial.</description></item><item><title>Graylog</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/graylog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/graylog/</guid><description>GraylogThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare Logs External link icon Open external link using Graylog External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Overview If you haven&amp;rsquo;t used Cloudflare Logs before, visit our Logs documentation for more details. Contact your Cloudflare Customer Account Team to enable logs for your account.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before sending your Cloudflare log data to Graylog, make sure that you:
Have an existing Graylog installation.</description></item><item><title>Looker</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/looker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/looker/</guid><description>LookerThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare Logs External link icon Open external link using the Cloudflare Log Analytics for Looker External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Overview If you have not used Cloudflare Logs before, refer to the Logs documentation for more details. Contact your Cloudflare Customer Account Team to enable logs for your account.
This tutorial uses Cloudflare Logpush to send logs to Google Cloud Storage Bucket and Cloud Function and then import them into Google Big Query.</description></item><item><title>New Relic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/new-relic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/new-relic/</guid><description>New RelicThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare metrics using the New Relic One Cloudflare Quickstart External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before sending your Cloudflare log data to New Relic, make sure that you:
Have a Cloudflare Enterprise account with Cloudflare Logs enabled. Have a New Relic account. Configure Logpush to New Relic. &amp;#8203;​ Task 1 - Install the Cloudflare Network Logs quickstart Log in to New Relic.</description></item><item><title>Splunk</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/splunk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/splunk/</guid><description>SplunkThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare Logs External link icon Open external link using the Cloudflare App for Splunk External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before sending your Cloudflare log data to Splunk, ensure that you:
Have an existing Splunk Enterprise or Cloud account Have a Cloudflare Enterprise account Consult the Splunk documentation External link icon Open external link for the Cloudflare App &amp;#8203;​ Task 1 - Install and Configure the Cloudflare App for Splunk To install the Cloudflare App for Splunk External link icon Open external link :</description></item><item><title>Sumo Logic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/sumo-logic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/data-products/analytics-integrations/sumo-logic/</guid><description>Sumo LogicThis tutorial explains how to analyze Cloudflare Logs External link icon Open external link using the Cloudflare App for Sumo Logic External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Overview If you have not used Cloudflare Logs before, refer to the Logs documentation for more details. Contact your Cloudflare Customer Account Team to enable logs for your account.
This tutorial describes how to use Cloudflare Logpush to send logs to AWS S3 and the AWS S3 source collector External link icon Open external link to get logs into Sumo Logic.</description></item></channel></rss>