<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Custom load balancing rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/</link><description>Recent content in Custom load balancing rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create custom rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/create-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/create-rules/</guid><description>Create custom rulesCreate and manage Load Balancing rules in the Custom Rules page, which is part of the Create/Edit Load Balancer workflow found in Traffic in the dashboard.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Understand whether Cloudflare proxies your traffic: Depending on the nature of your traffic, you may have access to different fields for your load balancing rules. For more details, see Supported fields and expressions. &amp;#8203;​ Workflow Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select an account and application.</description></item><item><title>Expressions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/expressions/</guid><description>Load Balancing expressionsLoad Balancing rules use two kinds of expressions:
Simple expressions compare a value from an HTTP request to a value defined in the expression. A simple expression is identified by the presence of a comparison operator (equals or less than, for example).
Compound expressions combine two or more simple expressions into a single expression. Compound expression contains a logical operator (and, or, for example). With compound expressions you can tailor rules to specific use cases with a high degree of accuracy and precision.</description></item><item><title>Actions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/actions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/actions/</guid><description>Load Balancing actionsAdd actions to customize how your load balancer responds to certain HTTP requests.
Each load balancing rule includes one or more actions.
&amp;#8203;​ Supported Actions This table lists the actions available for Load Balancing rules. For a walkthrough, refer to Create Load Balancing rules.
Action Options Description Fixed response N/A Respond to the request with an HTTP status code and an optional message. Override Session affinity Set the session affinity for the request.</description></item><item><title>Supported fields and operators</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-balancing-rules/reference/</guid><description>Supported fields and operatorsThe fields available for load balancing rules depend on whether Cloudflare proxies the traffic going through your load balancer.
If you use the wrong set of fields, you might see unexpected behavior from load balancing rules. For best results, use the fields associated with your traffic&amp;rsquo;s proxy status.
Field Set Section in Expression Builder Description Fields supported regardless of proxy BOTH The values that are always accessible regardless of whether the load balancer is proxied or not.</description></item></channel></rss>