<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamic advertisement</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/dynamic-advertisement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/dynamic-advertisement/</guid><description>Dynamic advertisementTo ensure smooth operation in general and simplify the advertisement process during an attack scenario, refer to dynamic advertisement best practices. To configure BGP advertisement at the Cloudflare edge, use the Cloudflare API or use the IP Prefixes page from your Cloudflare Account Home.
When using the API, you can authorize a call with your email and API key or create a service token for this purpose. A successful API response indicates the service registered the request.</description></item><item><title>Internet Routing Registry</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/irr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/irr/</guid><description>Internet Routing RegistryThe Internet Routing Registry (IRR) External link icon Open external link is a globally distributed database of routing information. The IRR contains announced routes and routing policies in a common format, and network operators use this information to configure their backbone routers.
The IRR consists of many individual routing registries External link icon Open external link , and some are managed by regional entities, such as APNIC, ARIN, and RIPE.</description></item><item><title>Letter of Authorization</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/loa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/loa/</guid><description>Letter of Authorization (LOA)A letter of authorization (LOA) is a document that authorizes Cloudflare to announce a prefix(es) on behalf of another entity. The LOA is required by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s transit providers so they can accept the routes Cloudflare advertises on behalf of another entity.
The letter must contain both the prefixes you are authorizing Cloudflare to announce and which ASN they will be announced under. Cloudflare can announce a prefix under your ASN or you are welcome to use Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s ASN.</description></item><item><title>Prefix delegations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/prefix-delegations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/byoip/about/prefix-delegations/</guid><description>Prefix delegationsBYOIP supports prefix delegations, which occur when a prefix owner account (Account A) allows another account (Account B) to use part or all of their prefix.
The effect of a delegation depends on the service used with the prefix. Currently BYOIP + CDN and BYOIP + Spectrum support prefix delegations.
&amp;#8203;​ CDN CDN delegations only have an effect if you are using SSL for SaaS in addition to BYOIP + CDN.</description></item></channel></rss>