<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API and Terraform on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/</link><description>Recent content in API and Terraform on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access API examples</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/rule-api-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/rule-api-examples/</guid><description>Access API examplesAccess users can create policies, including individual rule blocks inside of group or policy bodies. For example, this policy allows all Cloudflare email account users to reach the application with the exception of one account:
{ &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;allow cloudflare employees&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;decision&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;allow&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;include&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;email_domain&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;domain&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;cloudflare.com&amp;#34; } } ], &amp;#34;exclude&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;email&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;email&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;notthisperson@cloudflare.com&amp;#34; } } ], &amp;#34;require&amp;#34;: [] } &amp;#8203;​ Example rule configurations These are commonly used rule configurations.</description></item><item><title>Scoped API tokens</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/scoped-api-tokens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/scoped-api-tokens/</guid><description>Scoped API tokensThe administrators managing policies and groups in Cloudflare Access might be different from the users responsible for configuring firewall rules or other Cloudflare for Infrastructure settings. Cloudflare Access supports scoped API tokens External link icon Open external link so that team members and automated systems can manage settings specific to Access without having permission to modify other configurations in Cloudflare.
&amp;#8203;​ Creating a scoped API token In the Cloudflare for Infrastructure External link icon Open external link dashboard, click the user icon in the top right and navigate to &amp;ldquo;My Profile&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Terraform</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/access-with-terraform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/api-terraform/access-with-terraform/</guid><description>Terraform Requirements Terraform External link icon Open external link installed on your machine The Cloudflare provider External link icon Open external link properly configured Terraform External link icon Open external link is a tool for building, changing, and versioning infrastructure, and provides components and documentation for building Cloudflare resources External link icon Open external link . Listed below are examples to help you get started with building Access with Terraform.</description></item></channel></rss>