<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analytics on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/</link><description>Recent content in Analytics on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GraphQL Analytics API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/fetching-bulk-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/fetching-bulk-analytics/</guid><description>GraphQL Analytics APIStream provides analytics about both live video and video uploaded to Stream, via the GraphQL API described below, as well as in the Stream dashboard External link icon Open external link .
The Stream Analytics API uses the Cloudflare GraphQL Analytics API, which can be used across many Cloudflare products. For more about GraphQL, rate limits, filters, and sorting, refer to the Cloudflare GraphQL Analytics API docs.</description></item><item><title>Get live viewer counts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/live-viewer-count/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/live-viewer-count/</guid><description> Live viewer counts for third party playersThe Stream player has full support for live viewer counts by default. To get the viewer count for live videos for use with third party players, make a GET request to the /views endpoint.
https://customer-&amp;lt;CODE&amp;gt;.cloudflarestream.com/&amp;lt;INPUT_ID&amp;gt;/views Below is a response for a live video with several active viewers:
{ &amp;#34;liveViewers&amp;#34;: 113 }</description></item><item><title>Fetch per-video analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/fetching-per-video-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/getting-analytics/fetching-per-video-analytics/</guid><description>Fetch per-video analytics (deprecated) This API is deprecated and will be removed on Feb 1, 2023The Stream GraphQL Analytics API provides the same functionality, with additional filters and metrics, as well as the ability to fetch data about mutliple videos in a single API request. Queries are faster, more reliable, and built on a shared analytics system that you can use across many Cloudflare products. Cloudflare measures the following metrics for every video play:</description></item></channel></rss>