<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloudflare Notifications on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/</link><description>Recent content in Cloudflare Notifications on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notification History</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/notification-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/notification-history/</guid><description>Notification HistoryNotification History is a log of notifications that have been sent to your account via the Notifications service. Information contained in Notification History includes the notification itself, when the notification was sent, and who the notification was sent to.
&amp;#8203;​ How to access Notification History Currently, customers can access Notification History via the Cloudflare API. Using GET, customers can retrieve a list of history records for notifications sent to an account.</description></item><item><title>Available Notifications</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/notification-available/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/notifications/notification-available/</guid><description>Available NotificationsAvailable Notifications depend on your Cloudflare plan. Cloudflare offers a variety of Notifications for our products and services, such as Billing, Denial-of-Service protection, Magic Transit, and SSL/TLS.
Depending on your plan, you will also be able to configure webhooks (which allow you to connect your account with external services such as Slack and Google Chat) and PagerDuty to receive Cloudflare Notifications.
&amp;#8203;​ Actions available on receiving a Notification Each Notification carries different types of information about the status of your Cloudflare account, or the type of action you can take.</description></item><item><title>API reference</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>