<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Discovery on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/discovery/</link><description>Recent content in Discovery on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/discovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introspection</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/discovery/introspection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/discovery/introspection/</guid><description>IntrospectionCloudflare GraphQL API has a dynamic schema and exposes more than 70 datasets across zone and account scopes. We constantly expand the list and replace existing ones with more capable alternatives.
To tackle the schema question, GraphQL provides an introspection External link icon Open external link mechanism. It is part of the GraphQL specification and allows you to explore the graph of the datasets and fields.
The introspection results provide an overview of ALL available nodes and fields, their descriptions and deprecation status.</description></item><item><title>Settings node</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/discovery/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/features/discovery/settings/</guid><description>Settings nodeCloudflare GraphQL API exposes more than 70 datasets to its customers. These datasets represent different Cloudflare products with very different data shapes; thus, each has its configuration of limits.
Although we allow access to ALL plans for the essential datasets (like httpRequestsAdaptiveGroups, firewallEventsAdaptive, etc), users on larger plans benefit from an extended set of datasets and wider query limits.
In addition to introspection, users can use the Settings node that is available for both zones and accounts scopes.</description></item></channel></rss>