<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Migration guides on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Migration guides on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTTP Requests by Colo Groups to HTTP Requests by Adaptive Groups</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/graphql-api-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/graphql-api-analytics/</guid><description>HTTP Requests by Colo Groups to HTTP Requests by Adaptive GroupsThis guide shares considerations when migrating from the deprecated httpRequests1mByColoGroups and httpRequests1dByColoGroups GraphQL API nodes to the httpRequestsAdaptiveGroups GraphQL API node.
For example, if you wanted to see which five data centers had the most number of requests, the total number of those requests, and the total amount of data transfer, in the past you used the httpRequests1mByColoGroups GraphQL API node as in the following example:</description></item><item><title>Zone Analytics to GraphQL Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/zone-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/zone-analytics/</guid><description>Zone Analytics to GraphQL AnalyticsThe Zone Analytics API allows you to get request data by zone. It offers optional since and until parameters to specify the request time period and a continuous parameter to indicate whether the time period should be moved backward to find a period with completely aggregated data.
For example, here is a sample curl call to get data for a two minute period:
curl -s -H &amp;#34;X-Auth-Email: &amp;lt;REDACTED&amp;gt;&amp;#34; -H &amp;#34;X-Auth-Key: &amp;lt;REDACTED&amp;gt;&amp;#34; -X GET &amp;#34;https://api.</description></item><item><title>Zone Analytics Colos Endpoint to GraphQL Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/zone-analytics-colos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/analytics/graphql-api/migration-guides/zone-analytics-colos/</guid><description>Zone Analytics Colos Endpoint to GraphQL AnalyticsThis guide shows how you might migrate from the deprecated (and soon to be sunset) zone analytics API to the GraphQL API. It provides an example for a plausible use-case of the colos endpoint, then shows how that use-case is translated to the GraphQL API. It also explores features of the GraphQL API that make it more powerful than the API it replaces.</description></item></channel></rss>