<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add a third-party tool</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/add-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/add-tool/</guid><description>Add a third-party toolYou can add new third-party tools and load them into your website through the Cloudflare dashboard. If the tool you are adding needs to start actions different from the default Pageview trigger, it is recommended that you create the triggers you need first.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain. Select Zaraz &amp;gt; Tools Configuration &amp;gt; Third-party tools.</description></item><item><title>Create a trigger</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/create-trigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/create-trigger/</guid><description>Create a triggerTriggers define the conditions under which a tool will start an action. Since a tool must have actions in order to work, and actions must have triggers, it is important to set up your website&amp;rsquo;s triggers correctly. A trigger can be made out of one or more Rules. Zaraz supports multiple types of Trigger Rules.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>Create an action</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/create-actions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/create-actions/</guid><description>Create a third-party tool actionTools on Zaraz must have actions configured in order to do something. Every action has triggers assigned to it. When the conditions of the triggers are met, the action will start. An action can be anything the tool can do - sending analytics information, showing a widget, adding a script and much more.
To start using actions, first create a trigger to determine when this action will start.</description></item><item><title>Create a variable</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/create-variables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/create-variables/</guid><description>Create a variableVariables are reusable blocks of information. They allow you to have one source of data you can reuse across tools and triggers in the dashboard. You can then update this data in a single place.
For example, instead of typing a specific user ID in multiple fields, you can create a variable with that information instead. If there is a change and you have to update the user ID, you just need to update the variable and the change will be reflected across the dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Additional fields</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/additional-fields/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/additional-fields/</guid><description>Additional fieldsAlmost all tools in the Tools Library require that you enter information in more than one field to be properly configured. Beyond these required default fields, some tools let you add additional fields.
If we take Universal Google Analytics as an example, a default field would be your GA Property ID (the Google Analytics account ID), and an example of an additional field would be a Custom Dimension (like Custom Dimension 1).</description></item><item><title>Edit tools and actions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/edit-tools-and-actions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/edit-tools-and-actions/</guid><description>Edit tools and actions Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain. Go to Zaraz &amp;gt; Tools. Under Third-party tools, locate your tool and select Edit. On this page you will be able to edit settings related to the tool, add actions, and edit existing ones. To edit an existing action, select its name.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable or disable a tool Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>Edit triggers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/edit-triggers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/edit-triggers/</guid><description>Edit a trigger Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain. Go to Zaraz &amp;gt; Tools Configuration. Under Triggers, locate your trigger and select Edit. You can edit every field related to the trigger, as well as add new trigger rules.
&amp;#8203;​ Delete a trigger Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>Edit variables</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/edit-variables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/get-started/edit-variables/</guid><description>Edit a variable Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain. Go to Zaraz &amp;gt; Tools Configuration &amp;gt; Variables. Locate the variable you want to edit, and select Edit to make your changes. Select Save to save your edits. &amp;#8203;​ Delete a variable ImportantYou cannot delete a variable being used in tools or triggers. Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item></channel></rss>