<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Peering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/peering-with-content-providers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/peering-with-content-providers/</guid><description>PeeringIf you are running an IPFS node that serves many requests - like a public HTTP gateway - you may be able to speed up queries by maintaining long-lived connections to nodes that provide a large volume of data.
This process is known as Peering and you can tell IPFS to prioritize Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s peers by editing the Peering configuration in your IPFS config file.
{ &amp;#34;Peering&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;Peers&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;ID&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;QmcFf2FH3CEgTNHeMRGhN7HNHU1EXAxoEk6EFuSyXCsvRE&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Addrs&amp;#34;: [ &amp;#34;/dnsaddr/node-1.</description></item><item><title>Using IPFS with your website</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/updating-for-ipfs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/updating-for-ipfs/</guid><description>Using IPFS with your websiteThough it is not required, it is strongly recommended that websites hosted on IPFS use only relative links, unless linking to a different domain. This is because data can be accessed in many different (but ultimately equivalent) ways:
From your custom domain: https://ipfs.tech/index.html From a gateway: https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipns/ipfs.tech/index.html By immutable hash: https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipfs/QmNksJqvwHzNtAtYZVqFZFfdCVciY4ojTU2oFZQSFG9U7B/index.html Using only relative links within a web application supports all of these at once, and gives the most flexibility to the user.</description></item><item><title>Automated deployments</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/automated-deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/ipfs-gateway/reference/automated-deployment/</guid><description>Automated deploymentsStatic sites are easy to deploy automatically. The code of the site is usually kept in a Git repository and deployed by pushing the latest commit to a repository that&amp;rsquo;s connected to a Continuous Integration service like Travis CI External link icon Open external link , or by pushing to a repository directly on the server and activating a post-receive hook. Either way, the production version of the site is built and then copied into the serving path of an Apache or NGINX instance.</description></item></channel></rss>