<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FAQ on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/</link><description>Recent content in FAQ on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting started with Cloudflare Zero Trust</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-getting-started-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-getting-started-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Getting started with Cloudflare Zero Trust &amp;#8203;​ How do I sign up for Cloudflare Zero Trust? You can sign up today at this link External link icon Open external link . Follow the onboarding steps, choose a team name and a payment plan, and start protecting your network in just a few minutes.
&amp;#8203;​ What&amp;rsquo;s a team domain/team name? Your team domain is a unique subdomain assigned to your Cloudflare account; for example, &amp;lt;your-team-name&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title>General</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-general-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-general-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
General &amp;#8203;​ What is the difference between Cloudflare Gateway and 1.1.1.1? 1.1.1.1 does not block any DNS query. When a browser requests for example.com, 1.1.1.1 simply looks up the answer either in cache or by performing a full recursive DNS query.
Cloudflare Gateway&amp;rsquo;s DNS resolver introduces security into this flow. Instead of allowing all DNS queries, Gateway first checks the hostname being queried against the intelligence Cloudflare has about threats on the Internet.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-authentication-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-authentication-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Identity &amp;#8203;​ Can Access work with multiple identity providers at the same time? Yes. Your team can simultaneously use multiple providers, reducing friction when working with partners or contractors. Get started by adding your preferred identity providers as login methods on the Zero Trust dashboard. Then, when securing a new application behind Access, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to choose which providers you want your users to log in with to reach that application.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-troubleshooting/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Troubleshooting &amp;#8203;​ I tried to register the WARP client with my Zero Trust domain but received the following error messages: Authentication Expired and Registration error. Please try again later. When a user logs into an organization, WARP will open a web page so the user can sign in via Cloudflare Access. Access then generates a JSON Web Token (JWT) that is passed from the web page to the WARP client to authenticate the device.</description></item><item><title>Tunnels</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/cloudflare-tunnels-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/cloudflare-tunnels-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Tunnels &amp;#8203;​ ​Can I create a Tunnel for an apex domain? Yes. With Named Tunnels External link icon Open external link you can create a CNAME at the apex that points to the named tunnel.
&amp;#8203;​ ​Does Cloudflare Tunnel support Websockets? Yes. Cloudflare Tunnel has full support for Websockets.
&amp;#8203;​ ​Does Cloudflare Tunnel support gRPC? Yes. Cloudflare Tunnel supports gRPC for services within a private network. Public hostname deployments are not supported at this time.</description></item><item><title>Policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-policies-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-policies-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Policies &amp;#8203;​ What is the order of policy enforcement? Gateway and Access policies generally trigger from top to bottom based on their position in the policy table in the UI. Exceptions include Bypass and Service Auth policies, which Access evaluates first. Similarly, for Gateway HTTP policies, Do Not Inspect and Isolate policies take precedence over all Allow or Block policies. To learn more about order of enforcement, refer to our documentation for Access policies and Gateway policies.</description></item><item><title>Devices</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-devices-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/faq/teams-devices-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Devices &amp;#8203;​ Why is my device not connecting to a closer Cloudflare data center? As our Network Map External link icon Open external link shows, we have locations all over the globe. However, in the Advanced Connection stats of our application, you may notice that the data center (colo) you are connecting to isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily the one physically closest to your location. This can be due to a number of reasons:</description></item></channel></rss>