<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workers API on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/</link><description>Recent content in Workers API on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use R2 from Workers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/workers-api-usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/workers-api-usage/</guid><description>Use R2 from Workers &amp;#8203;​ 1. Install Wrangler This guide is tailored to Wrangler 2. If you are still using Wrangler 1, refer to the Migrate from Wrangler 1 guide. To create your R2 bucket, install Wrangler, the Workers CLI.
To install wrangler External link icon Open external link , ensure you have npm installed External link icon Open external link . Use a Node version manager like Volta External link icon Open external link or nvm External link icon Open external link to avoid permission issues or to easily change Node.</description></item><item><title>Use the R2 multipart API from Workers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/workers-multipart-usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/workers-multipart-usage/</guid><description>Use the R2 multipart API from WorkersBy following this guide, you will create a Worker through which your applications can perform multipart uploads. This example worker could serve as a basis for your own use case where you can add authentication to the worker, or even add extra validation logic when uploading each part. This guide also contains an example Python application that uploads files to this worker.
This guide assumes you have set up the R2 binding for your Worker.</description></item><item><title>Workers API Reference</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/workers-api-reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/workers-api/workers-api-reference/</guid><description>R2The in-Worker R2 API is accessed by binding an R2 bucket to a Worker. The Worker you write can expose external access to buckets via a route or manipulate R2 objects internally.
The R2 API includes some extensions and semantic differences from the S3 API. If you need S3 compatibility, consider using the S3-compatible API.
&amp;#8203;​ Concepts R2 organizes the data you store, called objects, into containers, called buckets. Buckets are the fundamental unit of performance, scaling, and access within R2.</description></item></channel></rss>