<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tunnel availability and failover</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/deploy-cloudflared-replicas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/deploy-cloudflared-replicas/</guid><description>Tunnel availability and failoverOur lightweight and open-source connector, cloudflared External link icon Open external link , was built to be highly available without any additional configuration requirements. When you run a tunnel, cloudflared establishes four outbound-only connections between the origin server and the Cloudflare network. These four connections are made to four different servers spread across at least two distinct data centers. This model ensures high availability and mitigates the risk of individual connection failures.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel permissions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-permissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-permissions/</guid><description>Tunnel permissionsNew! Set up and manage your Cloudflare Tunnel environment on the Zero Trust dashboard. You will be able to install cloudflared as a service, create and run tunnels, and get an overview of your active and inactive connectors.
Refer to these instructions for a step-by-step walkthrough of the UI.
Cloudflare Tunnel requires two files:
An account certificate (the cert.pem) A tunnel credentials file (&amp;lt;TUNNEL-UUID&amp;gt;.json) for each tunnel The account certificate (cert.</description></item><item><title>Useful terms</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-useful-terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-useful-terms/</guid><description>Useful termsNew! Set up and manage your Cloudflare Tunnel environment on the Zero Trust dashboard. You will be able to install cloudflared as a service, create and run tunnels, and get an overview of your active and inactive connectors.
Refer to these instructions for a step-by-step walkthrough of the UI.
Review terminology for tunnels setup locally through the CLI.
&amp;#8203;​ Tunnel A tunnel is a secure, outbound-only pathway you can establish between your origin and the Cloudflare global network.</description></item><item><title>Downloads</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/installation/</guid><description>DownloadsNew! Set up and manage your Cloudflare Tunnel environment on the Zero Trust dashboard. You will be able to install cloudflared as a service, create and run tunnels, and get an overview of your active and inactive connectors.
Refer to these instructions for a step-by-step walkthrough of the UI.
Cloudflare Tunnel requires the installation of a lightweight server-side daemon, cloudflared, to connect your infrastructure to Cloudflare. cloudflared is an open source project External link icon Open external link maintained by Cloudflare.</description></item><item><title>GitHub</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>