<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Common tasks on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/</link><description>Recent content in Common tasks on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monitor scripts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/monitor-scripts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/monitor-scripts/</guid><description>Monitor scripts on your siteOnce you have activated Page Shield, review the Active Scripts dashboard to see which active scripts are running on your domain.
If you see unexpected scripts on the dashboard, check them for signs of malicious activity.
The All Reported Scripts dashboard displays all the scripts, including infrequent or inactive scripts, reported in the last 30 days. After 30 days without any report, Page Shield will delete information about a previously reported script, and the script will no longer appear in any of the dashboards.</description></item><item><title>Monitor connections</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/monitor-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/monitor-connections/</guid><description>Monitor connections made by scripts on your sitePage Shield&amp;rsquo;s connection monitor helps you identify data exfiltration attacks such as MageCart, which rely on sending data from the browser to an unknown third-party endpoint.
Only available to customers on a Business or Enterprise plan. Use the Active Connections dashboard to review the connections made by scripts on your domain during the last seven days. If you see unexpected connections on the dashboard, check them for signs of malicious activity.</description></item><item><title>Configure alerts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/configure-alerts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/configure-alerts/</guid><description>Configure Page Shield alertsOnce you have activated Page Shield, you can set up multiple alerts for your domain.
Cloudflare sends alerts at regular intervals, so you might experience a delay between adding a new script and receiving an alert.
Only available to customers on a Business or Enterprise plan. To set up alerts:
Go to Security &amp;gt; Page Shield. Click Configure Alerts. Select an alert type. Fill in the required information and click Create.</description></item><item><title>Review malicious scripts and connections</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/review-malicious-scripts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/review-malicious-scripts/</guid><description>Review malicious scripts and connectionsIn the list of scripts and connections displayed in Page Shield&amp;rsquo;s dashboards, scripts and connections considered malicious appear at the top of the list, so that you can quickly identify those items, review them, and take action.
Only available to Enterprise customers with a paid add-on. &amp;#8203;​ Review malicious scripts To review the scripts considered malicious:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>Review changed scripts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/review-changed-scripts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/page-shield/use-dashboard/review-changed-scripts/</guid><description>Review changed scriptsPage Shield analyzes the JavaScript dependencies in the pages of your domain over time.
You can configure a notification for code change alerts to receive a daily notification about changed scripts in your domain.
Available as a paid add-on for customers on an Enterprise plan. When you receive such a notification:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item></channel></rss>