<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Routers on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/</link><description>Recent content in Routers on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supported routers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/supported-routers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/supported-routers/</guid><description>Supported routersThe majority of enterprise grade routers are capable of exporting NetFlow or sFlow, and popular router brands that support either NetFlow or sFlow are listed below.
Relatively few consumer grade routers are capable of exporting NetFlow or sFlow. If you are a network hobbyist, business, or other organization, and your router options are limited, you can view the list of open source and affordable options below.
Note:These lists are not exhaustive, and we encourage you to check your router’s specification sheet to confirm your router is capable of exporting NetFlow or sFlow.</description></item><item><title>Recommended sampling rate</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/recommended-sampling-rate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/recommended-sampling-rate/</guid><description>Recommended sampling rateNetFlow or sFlow data is created by sampling the traffic that passes through your router. Lower sampling rates increase network flow data accuracy but require more router memory and CPU when the data is generated. Additionally, network flow data accuracy is maintained if customer select a higher sampling rate but also receive a larger amount of traffic.
The table below gives general recommendations for sampling rates depending on your traffic volume.</description></item><item><title>Netflow/IPFIX configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/netflow-ipfix-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/netflow-ipfix-config/</guid><description>Netflow/IPFIX configurationMagic Network Monitoring supports the NetFlow v5, NetFlow v9, and IPFIX network flow data formats.
Log in to your router&amp;rsquo;s configuration application.
Open your router&amp;rsquo;s NetFlow configuration menu.
Set up your router&amp;rsquo;s Flow Exporter configuration with the following values:
Flow exporter
Destination IP address: 162.159.65.1 Destination Port: 2055 Transport Protocol: UDP Set up your router&amp;rsquo;s Flow Record configuration with the following values:
Flow Record
match ipv4 protocol match ipv4 source address match ipv4 destination address match transport source-port match transport destination-port match interface input Confirm your router&amp;rsquo;s Netflow template.</description></item><item><title>sFlow/jFlow configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/sflow-jflow-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/magic-network-monitoring/routers/sflow-jflow-config/</guid><description> sFlow/jFlow configuration Log in to your router&amp;rsquo;s configuration application.
Open your router&amp;rsquo;s sFlow configuration menu.
Set up your router&amp;rsquo;s sFlow Exporter configuration with the following values:
sFlow Exporter
Destination IP address: 162.159.65.1 Destination Port: 6343 Transport Protocol: UDP</description></item></channel></rss>