<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FAQ on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/</link><description>Recent content in FAQ on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/general-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/general-faq/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
General FAQ &amp;#8203;​ Once a request has passed through the Cloudflare network, how soon are the logs available? When using Logpush, logs are pushed in batches as soon as possible. For example, if you receive a file at 10:10, the file consists of logs that were processed before 10:10.
When using Logpull, logs become available in approximately one to five minutes. Cloudflare requires that calls to the Logpull API to be for time periods of at least one minute in the past.</description></item><item><title>Logpush</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/logpush/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/logpush/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Logpush &amp;#8203;​ What happens if my cloud storage destination is temporarily unavailable? Logpush is designed to retry in case of errors. If your destination is temporarily unavailable, Logpush will retry around five times over five minutes. However, note that this number and time are just approximations. If Cloudflare persistently receives errors from your destination, and cannot keep up with incoming batches, Logpush will eventually drop logs. If the errors continue for a prolonged period of time, Logpush will assume that the destination is permanently unavailable and disable your push job.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/logpull-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/logpull-api/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Logpull API &amp;#8203;​ How long are logs retained? Cloudflare makes logs available for at least three days and up to seven days. If you need your logs for a longer time period, download and store them locally.
&amp;#8203;​ I am asking for logs for the time window of 16:10-16:13. However, the timestamps in the logs show requests that are before this time period. Why does that happen?</description></item><item><title>Common calculations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/common-calculations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/common-calculations/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Common calculations &amp;#8203;​ How can I calculate bytes served by the origin from Cloudflare Logs? The best way to calculate bytes served by the origin is to use the CacheResponseBytes field in Cloudflare Logs, and to filter only requests that come from the origin. Make sure to filter out OriginResponseStatus values 0 and 304, which indicate a revalidated response.
&amp;#8203;​ How do I calculate bandwidth usage for my zone?</description></item><item><title>Instant Logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/instant-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/faq/instant-logs/</guid><description>❮ Back to FAQ
Instant Logs &amp;#8203;​ I am getting an HTTP 301 when attempting to connect to my WebSocket. What can I do? Make sure you are using the wss:// protocol when connecting to your WebSocket.
&amp;#8203;​ I am getting an HTTP 429. What can I do? Connection requests are rate limited. Try your request again after waiting a few minutes.
&amp;#8203;​ Why am I not receiving data? First, double-check if you have a filter defined.</description></item></channel></rss>