<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Runtime APIs on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/</link><description>Recent content in Runtime APIs on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>addEventListener</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/add-event-listener/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/add-event-listener/</guid><description>addEventListener &amp;#8203;​ Background The addEventListener function defines triggers for a Worker script to execute. There are currently two types of event listeners - &amp;quot;fetch&amp;quot; listeners which are sent a FetchEvent and &amp;quot;scheduled&amp;quot; listeners which are sent a ScheduledEvent.
&amp;#8203;​ Syntax addEventListener(type, listener) void
If multiple &amp;quot;fetch&amp;quot; listeners are registered, when one does not call event.respondWith(), the runtime delivers the event to the next registered listener. A &amp;quot;fetch&amp;quot; listener and a &amp;quot;scheduled&amp;quot; listener can be registered in the same script.</description></item><item><title>Cache</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/cache/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/cache/</guid><description>Cache &amp;#8203;​ Background The Cache API External link icon Open external link allows fine grained control of reading and writing from the Cloudflare edge network External link icon Open external link cache.
The Cache API is available globally but the contents of the cache do not replicate outside of the originating data center. A GET /users response can be cached in the originating data center, but will not exist in another data center unless it has been explicitly created.</description></item><item><title>Durable Objects</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/durable-objects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/durable-objects/</guid><description>Durable ObjectsDurable Objects are available to anyone with a Workers paid subscription. You can enable them for your account in the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link by navigating to “Workers” and opting in to pricing.
&amp;#8203;​ Background Durable Objects provide low-latency coordination and consistent storage for the Workers platform. A given namespace can support essentially unlimited Durable Objects, with each Object having access to a transactionally consistent key-value storage API.</description></item><item><title>Encoding</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/encoding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/encoding/</guid><description>Encoding &amp;#8203;​ TextEncoder &amp;#8203;​ Background The TextEncoder takes a stream of code points as input and emits a stream of bytes. Encoding types passed to the constructor are ignored and a UTF-8 TextEncoder is created.
TextEncoder() External link icon Open external link returns a newly constructed TextEncoder that generates a byte stream with UTF-8 encoding. TextEncoder takes no parameters and throws no exceptions.
&amp;#8203;​ Constructor let encoder = new TextEncoder(); &amp;#8203;​ Properties encoding DOMString read-only The name of the encoder as a string describing the method the TextEncoder uses (always utf-8).</description></item><item><title>Fetch</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/fetch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/fetch/</guid><description>FetchThe Fetch API External link icon Open external link provides an interface for asynchronously fetching resources via HTTP requests inside of a Worker.
The fetch method is implemented on the ServiceWorkerGlobalScope. Refer to MDN documentation External link icon Open external link for more information.
Asynchronous tasks such as fetch are not executed at the top level in a Worker script and must be executed within a FetchEvent handler such as respondWith.</description></item><item><title>FetchEvent</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/fetch-event/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/fetch-event/</guid><description>FetchEvent &amp;#8203;​ Background In Workers, any incoming HTTP requests are referred to as &amp;quot;fetch&amp;quot; events. A Worker will respond to the HTTP request with the handler method that was assigned to the &amp;quot;fetch&amp;quot; event.
Both the Service Worker and Module Worker formats are able to handle &amp;quot;fetch&amp;quot; events, but with significant differences in their authoring syntax.
&amp;#8203;​ Syntax: Service Worker In the Service Worker format, events are handled by using addEventListener to assign a handler to an event name.</description></item><item><title>Headers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/headers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/headers/</guid><description>Headers &amp;#8203;​ Background All HTTP request and response headers are available through the Headers API External link icon Open external link .
When a header name possesses multiple values, those values will be concatenated as a single, comma-delimited string value. This means that Headers.get will always return a string or a null value. This applies to all header names except for Set-Cookie, which requires Headers.getAll. This is documented below in Differences.</description></item><item><title>HTMLRewriter</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/html-rewriter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/html-rewriter/</guid><description>HTMLRewriter &amp;#8203;​ Background The HTMLRewriter class allows developers to build comprehensive and expressive HTML parsers inside of a Cloudflare Workers application. It can be thought of as a jQuery-like experience directly inside of your Workers application. Leaning on a powerful JavaScript API to parse and transform HTML, HTMLRewriter allows developers to build deeply functional applications.
The HTMLRewriter class should be instantiated once in your Workers script, with a number of handlers attached using the on and onDocument functions.</description></item><item><title>KV</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/kv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/kv/</guid><description>KV &amp;#8203;​ Background Workers KV is a global, low-latency, key-value data store. It stores data in a small number of centralized data centers, then caches that data in Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s data centers after access. KV supports exceptionally high read volumes with low latency, making it possible to build highly dynamic APIs and websites that respond as quickly as a cached static file would. While reads are periodically revalidated in the background, requests which are not in cache and need to hit the centralized back end can see high latencies.</description></item><item><title>R2</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/r2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/runtime-apis/r2/</guid><description>R2The in-Worker R2 API is accessed by binding an R2 bucket to a Worker. The Worker you write can expose external access to buckets via a route, or manipulate R2 objects internally.
The R2 API includes some extensions and semantic differences from the S3 API. If you need S3 compatibility, consider using the S3 compatible API.
&amp;#8203;​ Concepts R2 organizes the data you store, called objects, into containers, called buckets.</description></item></channel></rss>