<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>API Gateway</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/api-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/api-gateway/</guid><description>API GatewayAPI Gateway is a package of features that will do everything for your APIs, including:
Security: Protect your API from malicious traffic with API Discovery, Schema Validation, mTLS validation, and more. Management and monitoring: Streamline API management with Endpoint Management and tools External link icon Open external link like analytics, routing, and authentication. Logging, quota management, and more: All of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s established features External link icon Open external link , like caching, load balancing, and log integrations work natively with API Gateway.</description></item><item><title>Management and Monitoring</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/management-and-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/management-and-monitoring/</guid><description>Endpoint ManagementMonitor the health of your API endpoints by saving, updating, and monitoring performance metrics using API Shield’s Endpoint Management.
Add endpoints allows customers to save endpoints directly from API Discovery or manually by method, path, and host.
This will add the specified endpoints to your list of managed endpoints. You can view your list of saved endpoints in the Endpoint Management page.
Cloudflare will start collecting performance data on your endpoint when you save an endpoint.</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/api-shield/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;#8203;​ Why are my API endpoints not found by API Discovery? In most cases, this is due to the system not observing enough valid requests over a continuous period.
API Discovery only looks at requests that satisfy all of the following criteria:
For customers outside of the Machine Learning-based API Discovery closed beta, requests must send the session identifier or identifiers (HTTP header or Cookie) that have been configured for the zone.</description></item></channel></rss>