<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage gateways</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/manage-gateways/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/manage-gateways/</guid><description>Manage gatewaysA Cloudflare Web3 gateway provides HTTP-accessible interfaces to various Web3 networks. You can interact with a gateway in several ways.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a gateway Dashboard API To create a gateway using the dashboard:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . Select your account and website. Go to Web3. Click Create Web3 Gateway. Enter the following information: Hostname: Enter a hostname to use as your gateway, which has to be a subdomain of the current Cloudflare zone.</description></item><item><title>Subscribe to gateways</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/enable-gateways/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/enable-gateways/</guid><description>Subscribe to gatewaysBefore you can create a new gateway, you need to subscribe to one or more gateways.
&amp;#8203;​ Create new subscription To subscribe to a Web3 gateway (if you have not already subscribed):
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . Select your account and website. Go to Web3. Click Subscribe to Web3 Gateways. Choose which gateways you want to subscribe to. Click Proceed to Payment Details.</description></item><item><title>Use Ethereum gateway</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/use-ethereum-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/use-ethereum-gateway/</guid><description>Use the Ethereum gatewayOnce you have an Ethereum gateway — meaning that you create a new gateway with a target of Ethereum — you can interact with different Ethereum networks by specifying the correct JSON blob for your query.
&amp;#8203;​ Read from the network The Cloudflare Ethereum Gateway allows HTTP requests where the body of the request is set to be the JSON body of the request you would like to make.</description></item><item><title>Use IPFS gateway</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/use-ipfs-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/use-ipfs-gateway/</guid><description>Use the IPFS gatewayOnce you have an IPFS gateway — meaning that you create a new gateway with a target of IPFS — you can get data from the IPFS network by using a URL.
&amp;#8203;​ Read from the network Every time you access a piece of content through Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s IPFS Gateway, you need a URL with two parts: the gateway hostname and the request path.
&amp;#8203;​ Gateway hostname Your gateway hostname will be the Hostname value you supplied when you created the gateway.</description></item><item><title>Use Polygon gateway</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/use-polygon-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/use-polygon-gateway/</guid><description>Use the Polygon gatewayOnce you have a Polygon gateway — meaning that you create a new gateway with a target of Polygon — you can interact with different Polygon networks by specifying the correct JSON blob for your query.
&amp;#8203;​ Read from the network The Cloudflare Polygon Gateway allows HTTP requests where the body of the request is set to be the JSON body of the request you would like to make.</description></item><item><title>Customize Cloudflare settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/customize-cloudflare-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/customize-cloudflare-settings/</guid><description>Customize Cloudflare settingsOnce your gateway becomes active, you can customize the Cloudflare settings associated with your hostname.
Since your traffic is automatically proxied through Cloudflare, you customize your website settings to take advantage of various security, performance, and reliability benefits.</description></item><item><title>Restrict gateway access</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/restrict-gateway-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/web3/how-to/restrict-gateway-access/</guid><description>Restrict gateway accessIf you are using a Web3 gateway for internal application calls, you may want to restrict gateway access to specific backend services.
You can achieve this goal by creating general Access policies to block normal traffic and then creating service tokens to allow access by your backend service.</description></item></channel></rss>