<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account-scoped datasets on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/</link><description>Recent content in Account-scoped datasets on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access requests</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/access_requests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/access_requests/</guid><description>Access requestsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for access_requests.
Field Value Type Action What type of record is this. login | logout. string Allowed If request was allowed or denied. bool AppDomain The domain of the Application that Access is protecting. string AppUUID Access Application UUID. string Connection Identity provider used for the login. string Country Request&amp;rsquo;s country of origin. string CreatedAt The date and time the corresponding access request was made (for example, &amp;lsquo;2021-07-27T00:01:07Z&amp;rsquo;).</description></item><item><title>Audit logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/audit_logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/audit_logs/</guid><description>Audit logsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for audit_logs.
Field Value Type ActionResult Whether the action was successful. bool ActionType Type of action taken. string ActorEmail Email of the actor. string ActorID Unique identifier of the actor in Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s system. string ActorIP Physical network address of the actor. string ActorType Type of user that started the audit trail. string ID Unique identifier of an audit log. string Interface Entry point or interface of the audit log.</description></item><item><title>DNS Firewall Logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/dns_firewall_logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/dns_firewall_logs/</guid><description>DNS Firewall LogsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for dns_firewall_logs.
Field Value Type ClientResponseCode Integer value of response code. For more information refer to Response code External link icon Open external link . int ClusterID The ID of the cluster which handled this request. string ColoCode IATA airport code of data center that received the request. string EDNSSubnet EDNS Client Subnet (IPv4 or IPv6). For more information refer to EDNS Client Subnet.</description></item><item><title>Gateway DNS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/gateway_dns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/gateway_dns/</guid><description>Gateway DNSThe descriptions below detail the fields available for gateway_dns.
Field Value Type ApplicationID ID of the application the domain belongs to (for example, 1, 2). Set to 0 when no ApplicationID is matched. int ColoCode The name of the colo that received the DNS query (for example, &amp;lsquo;SJC&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;MIA&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;IAD&amp;rsquo;). string ColoID The ID of the colo that received the DNS query (for example, 46, 72, 397). int Datetime The date and time the corresponding DNS request was made (for example, &amp;lsquo;2021-07-27T00:01:07Z&amp;rsquo;).</description></item><item><title>Gateway HTTP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/gateway_http/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/gateway_http/</guid><description>Gateway HTTPThe descriptions below detail the fields available for gateway_http.
Field Value Type AccountID Cloudflare account tag. string Action Action performed by gateway on the HTTP request. string BlockedFileHash Hash of the file blocked in the response, if any. string BlockedFileName File name blocked in the request, if any. string BlockedFileReason Reason file was blocked in the response, if any. string BlockedFileSize File size(bytes) blocked in the response, if any.</description></item><item><title>Gateway Network</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/gateway_network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/gateway_network/</guid><description>Gateway NetworkThe descriptions below detail the fields available for gateway_network.
Field Value Type AccountID Cloudflare account tag. string Action Action performed by gateway on the session. string Datetime The date and time the corresponding network session was made (for example, &amp;lsquo;2021-07-27T00:01:07Z&amp;rsquo;). int or string DestinationIP Destination IP of the network session. string DestinationPort Destination port of the network session. int DeviceID UUID of the device where the network session originated from.</description></item><item><title>Magic IDS Detections</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/magic_ids_detections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/magic_ids_detections/</guid><description>Magic IDS DetectionsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for magic_ids_detections.
Field Value Type Action What action was taken on the packet. Possible values are pass | block. string ColoCity The city where the detection occurred. string ColoCode The IATA airport code corresponding to where the detection occurred. string DestinationIP The destination IP of the packet which triggered the detection. string DestinationPort The destination port of the packet which triggered the detection.</description></item><item><title>Network Analytics Logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/network_analytics_logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/network_analytics_logs/</guid><description>Network Analytics LogsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for network_analytics_logs.
Field Value Type AttackCampaignID Unique identifier of the attack campaign that this packet was a part of, if any. string AttackID Unique identifier of the mitigation that matched the packet, if any. string ColoCity The city where the Cloudflare datacenter that received the packet is located. string ColoCode The Cloudflare datacenter that received the packet (nearest IATA airport code).</description></item><item><title>Workers Trace Events</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/workers_trace_events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/account/workers_trace_events/</guid><description>Workers Trace EventsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for workers_trace_events.
Field Value Type DispatchNamespace The Cloudflare Worker dispatch namespace. string Event Details about the source event. object EventTimestampMs The timestamp of when the event was received, in milliseconds. int EventType The event type that triggered the invocation. Possible values are fetch. string Exceptions List of uncaught exceptions during the invocation. array[object] Logs List of console messages emitted during the invocation.</description></item></channel></rss>