<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access Control Lists (ACLs) on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/zone-transfers/access-control-lists/</link><description>Recent content in Access Control Lists (ACLs) on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/zone-transfers/access-control-lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloudflare IP addresses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/zone-transfers/access-control-lists/cloudflare-ip-addresses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/zone-transfers/access-control-lists/cloudflare-ip-addresses/</guid><description>Cloudflare IP addressesAccess Control Lists (ACLs) define allowed source IP addresses from where servers accept incoming data or control messages.
When setting up new DNS zone transfers (incoming or outgoing), you will need to update the ACLs at your other DNS provider to prevent communication from Cloudflare from being blocked.
Depending on the setup (Cloudflare as Primary or Cloudflare as Secondary), you need to configure slightly different Cloudflare IP addresses at your other DNS provider.</description></item><item><title>Create ACL</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/zone-transfers/access-control-lists/create-new-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/zone-transfers/access-control-lists/create-new-list/</guid><description>Create a new Access Control ListYou need to create an Access Control List (ACL) in certain situations:
If Cloudflare is your primary DNS provider, create an ACL to specify additional IPs Cloudflare should accept zone transfer requests from. If Cloudflare is your secondary DNS provider, create an ACL to specify additional NOTIFY IPs that Cloudflare should listen to. An ACL is configured at the account level, which means that it will apply to every primary and secondary zone in your account.</description></item></channel></rss>