<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HTTP policies on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/</link><description>Recent content in HTTP policies on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/common-policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/common-policies/</guid><description>Common HTTP policiesThe following policies are commonly used to secure HTTP traffic.
&amp;#8203;​ Block content categories Block content categories which go against your organization’s acceptable use policy.
Selector Operator Value Action Content categories in Adult Themes, Gambling Block &amp;#8203;​ Block applications Block content categories which go against your organization’s acceptable use policy.
Selector Operator Value Action Application in Netflix Block After 7 days, view your Shadow IT analytics and block additional applications based on what your users are accessing.</description></item><item><title>Global rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/global-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/global-rules/</guid><description>Global rulesCloudflare Zero Trust applies a set of global rules to all accounts.
Criteria Value Action Description Hostname *.cloudflareclient.com bypass engage.cloudflareclient.com is used by client for registration. This policy ensures that customers cannot accidentally block themselves from making account changes. Hostname *.assets.browser.run bypass Do not inspect assets.browser.run or *.assets.browser.run Hostname *.cloudflare-gateway.com bypass Ensure we bypass requests to cloudflare-gateway.com DNS endpoint Hostname *.cloudflarestatus.com bypass Bypass cloudflarestatus.com so customers can reach the page in case of Gateway outage Hostname *.</description></item><item><title>HTTP/3</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/http3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/http3/</guid><description>HTTP/3 inspectionGateway supports inspection of HTTP/3 traffic, which uses the QUIC protocol over UDP. To enable HTTP/3 inspection, go to Settings &amp;gt; Network and enable Proxy for UDP.
&amp;#8203;​ Browser limitations The following browsers do not support HTTP/3 inspection:
Google Chrome Safari Firefox Gateway will automatically force all traffic from these browsers to fall back to HTTP/2, thus allowing you to enforce your HTTP policies.</description></item><item><title>TLS decryption</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/tls-decryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/tls-decryption/</guid><description>TLS decryptionCloudflare Gateway can perform SSL/TLS decryption External link icon Open external link in order to inspect HTTPS traffic for malware and other security risks. When you enable TLS decryption, Gateway will decrypt all traffic sent over HTTPS, apply your HTTP policies, and then re-encrypt the request with the Cloudflare certificate.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable TLS decryption In the Zero Trust dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; Network.</description></item><item><title>Tenant control</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/tenant-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/tenant-control/</guid><description>Tenant controlCloudflare Zero Trust offers IT administrators a way to ensure users have access to SaaS applications for corporate use, while at the same time blocking access to their personal accounts. This helps prevent the loss of sensitive or confidential data from a corporate network.
You can create Gateway HTTP policies to control access to your corporate SaaS applications. When creating an HTTP policy with an Allow action, you will have the option to configure custom headers.</description></item><item><title>AV scanning</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/antivirus-scanning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/http-policies/antivirus-scanning/</guid><description>AV scanningCloudflare Gateway protects users as they navigate the Internet. When users download or upload a file to an origin on the Internet, that file could potentially contain malicious code that may cause their device to perform undesired behavior.
To prevent this, Cloudflare Gateway allows admins to enable Anti-Virus (AV) scanning of files that are uploaded or downloaded by users as the file passes through Gateway.
AV scanning of files requires organizations to enable Proxy mode under Settings &amp;gt; Network &amp;gt; Layer 7 Firewall.</description></item></channel></rss>