<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technology Partners on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/</link><description>Recent content in Technology Partners on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Console Connect</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/console-connect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/console-connect/</guid><description> Console Connect Users Click + to create a new connection. From the Choose source port dropdown, choose your source port. Select Another Company and then enter Cloudflare. For Rate Limit (speed), choose your rate limit. Select Next. Review the pricing information, and when you are done, click Save Payment. Cloudflare will accept the connection and your Account Team will get in touch with next steps for BGP session establishment</description></item><item><title>Equinix Fabric</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/equinix-fabric/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/equinix-fabric/</guid><description>Equinix Users &amp;#8203;​ Order an Equinix Fabric Connection After you confirm the locations and speed with you account team, order the Equinix Fabric connections to Cloudlfare.
Navigate to https://fabric.equinix.com/ External link icon Open external link Under I want to connect to:, choose A Service Provider. Under Select a Service Provider, search for Cloudflare and click Select. Choose Magic Transit or Cloudflare NaaS. If you&amp;rsquo;re unsure, choose Cloudflare NaaS which can can be used to configure any service.</description></item><item><title>Megaport</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/megaport/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/megaport/</guid><description>Megaport Users &amp;#8203;​ Create a VXC with a service key The Cloudflare account team creates the Service Key and sends it to you via email. After the Service Key is sent, anyone who has the key can use it to create a connection.
Log in to the Megaport Portal External link icon Open external link .
Find the Megaport you want to use for the connection and click +Connection.</description></item><item><title>PacketFabric</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/packet-fabric/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/network-interconnect/partners/packet-fabric/</guid><description>PacketFabric Users From the PacketFabric dashboard, select Marketplace. In the Search bar, enter Cloudflare. Select Cloudflare as the provider. From Choose a Location, choose a location from the dropdown. Under Select Source Port, choose a port. Under Select Virtual Circuit Speed, choose a speed from the dropdown. Click Place Order. Click Okay in the Virtual Circuit Request Dispatched notice. Cloudflare will accept the connection and your account team will contact you to establish the BGP session.</description></item></channel></rss>