<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/</link><description>Recent content in Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/configure-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/configure-dashboard/</guid><description>Configure Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection in the dashboardYou can customize the action and sensitivity of the rules in the Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset in the following ways:
Override all the rules in the ruleset Override one or more rules You define overrides for the Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset at the account level. Tag and rule overrides have greater priority than ruleset overrides.
For more information on the available parameters and allowed values, refer to Managed ruleset parameters.</description></item><item><title>Configure via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/configure-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/configure-api/</guid><description>Configure Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection via APIConfigure the Cloudflare Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset by defining overrides at the account level using the Rulesets API.
Each account has the Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset enabled by default. This means that you do not need to deploy the managed ruleset to the ddos_l4 phase entry point ruleset explicitly. You only have to create a rule in the phase entry point to deploy the managed ruleset if you need to configure overrides.</description></item><item><title>Rule categories</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/rule-categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/rule-categories/</guid><description>Rule categoriesRules in the Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset belong to the following categories (also known as tags):
Name Description gre Rules for DDoS attacks over Generic Routing Encapsulation (GRE) that usually target GRE endpoints. esp Rules for DDoS attacks related to the Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP) protocol, which is part of the IPSec secure network protocol suite. advanced Rules related to features available to Enterprise customers, such as Adaptive DDoS Protection.</description></item><item><title>Parameters</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/override-parameters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/override-parameters/</guid><description>Ruleset parametersDefine overrides for the Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset to change the action applied to a given attack or modify the sensitivity level of the detection mechanism. You can define overrides in the Cloudflare dashboard or define overrides via Rulesets API.
The available parameters are the following:
Action Sensitivity Level &amp;#8203;​ Action API property name: &amp;quot;action&amp;quot;.
The action performed for packets that match specific rules of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s DDoS mitigation services.</description></item><item><title>Override expressions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/override-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/managed-rulesets/network/override-expressions/</guid><description>Override expressionsSet an override expression for the Network-layer DDoS Attack Protection managed ruleset to define a specific scope for sensitivity level or action adjustments. For example, you can set different sensitivity levels for different destination IP addresses or ports: a medium sensitivity level for destination IP address A and a low sensitivity level for destination IP address B.
&amp;#8203;​ Available expression fields You can use the following fields in override expressions:</description></item></channel></rss>