<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S3 API on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/</link><description>Recent content in S3 API on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S3 API Compatibility</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/api/</guid><description>S3 API compatibilityR2 implements the S3 API to allow users and their applications to migrate easily. When comparing to AWS S3, Cloudflare has removed some API operations&amp;rsquo; features and added others. The S3 API operations are listed below with their current implementation status. Feature implementation is currently in progress. Refer back to this page for updates. The API is available via the https://&amp;lt;ACCOUNT_ID&amp;gt;.r2.cloudflarestorage.com endpoint. Find your account ID in the Cloudflare dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Extensions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/extensions/</guid><description>ExtensionsR2 implements some extensions on top of the basic S3 API. This page outlines these additional, available features.
&amp;#8203;​ Extended metadata using Unicode The Workers R2 API supports Unicode in keys and values natively without requiring any additional encoding or decoding for the customMetadata field. These fields map to the x-amz-meta--prefixed headers used within the R2 S3-compatible API endpoint.
HTTP header names and values may only contain ASCII characters, which is a small subset of the Unicode character library.</description></item><item><title>Generate an S3 Auth token</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/tokens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/tokens/</guid><description>Generate an S3 Auth tokenIn this guide, you will learn how to generate an API token to serve as the Access Key for usage with existing S3-compatible SDKs and/or XML APIs.
You must purchase R2 before you can generate an API token.
To create an API token:
In Account Home, select R2. Select Manage R2 API Tokens on the right side of the dashboard. Select Create API token. Select the pencil icon or R2 Token text to edit your API token name.</description></item><item><title>Presigned URLs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/presigned-urls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/r2/data-access/s3-api/presigned-urls/</guid><description>Presigned URLsPresigned URLs are an S3 concept External link icon Open external link for sharing direct access to your bucket without revealing your token secret. A presigned URL authorizes anyone with the URL to perform an action to the S3 compatibility endpoint for an R2 bucket. By default, the S3 endpoint requires an AUTHORIZATION header signed by your token. Every presigned URL has S3 parameters and search parameters containing the signature information that would be present in an AUTHORIZATION header.</description></item></channel></rss>