<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access integrations on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/</link><description>Recent content in Access integrations on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure AD</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/azure-ad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/azure-ad/</guid><description>Azure AD Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link Windows WARP with Gateway All plans Cloudflare Access can integrate with Azure AD&amp;rsquo;s Conditional Access feature to require that users connect to certain applications from managed devices. To enable, you must integrate Azure AD with Cloudflare Access as a cloud app that requires managed device connections. You can configure per-app identity providers to segment which Access applications require Azure AD with managed devices and which only require Azure AD logins.</description></item><item><title>Mutual TLS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/mutual-tls-authentication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/mutual-tls-authentication/</guid><description>Mutual TLS Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link All systems WARP not required Enterprise plans Adding mTLS to your application using your own certificate authority (CA) is only available on the Cloudflare enterprise plan. Mutual TLS (mTLS) authentication External link icon Open external link ensures that traffic is both secure and trusted in both directions between a client and server.</description></item><item><title>Tanium</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/tanium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/access-integrations/tanium/</guid><description>Tanium Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link Any OS supported by Tanium WARP with Gateway All plans Cloudflare Access can use endpoint data from Tanium™ External link icon Open external link to determine if a request should be allowed to reach a protected resource. When users attempt to connect to a resource protected by Access with a Tanium rule, Cloudflare Access will validate the user&amp;rsquo;s identity, and the browser will connect to the Tanium agent before making a decision to grant access.</description></item></channel></rss>