<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WARP client checks on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/</link><description>Recent content in WARP client checks on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Application check</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/application-check/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/application-check/</guid><description>Application check Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link macOS, Windows, Linux WARP with Gateway All plans The Application Check device posture attribute checks that a specific application process is running on a device. You can create multiple application checks for each operating system you need to run it on, or if you need to check for multiple applications.
&amp;#8203;​ Configure an application check In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client.</description></item><item><title>Carbon Black</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/carbon-black/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/carbon-black/</guid><description>Carbon Black Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Minimum WARP version required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link macOS, Windows, Linux WARP with Gateway macOS: 1.4.34, Windows: 1.4.33.0 All plans Cloudflare Zero Trust can check if Carbon Black External link icon Open external link is running on a device to determine if a request should be allowed to reach a protected resource.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before you start, make sure Carbon Black installed on your machine.</description></item><item><title>Device serial numbers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/corp-device/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/corp-device/</guid><description>Device serial numbers Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link macOS, Windows, Linux WARP with Gateway All plans Cloudflare Zero Trust allows you to build Zero Trust rules based on device serial numbers. You can create these rules so that access to applications is granted only to users connecting from company devices.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a list of serial numbers To create rules based on device serial numbers, you first need to create a Gateway List of numbers.</description></item><item><title>Disk encryption</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/disk-encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/disk-encryption/</guid><description>Disk encryption Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link macOS, Windows WARP with Gateway All plans The Disk Encryption device posture attribute ensures that disks are encrypted on a device.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable the disk encryption check In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client. Scroll down to WARP client checks and select Add new.</description></item><item><title>Domain joined</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/domain-joined/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/domain-joined/</guid><description>Domain joined Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link Windows WARP with Gateway All plans The Domain Joined device posture attribute ensures that a user is a member of a specific Windows Active Directory domain.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable the Domain Joined check In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client. Scroll down to WARP client checks and select Add new.</description></item><item><title>File check</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/file-check/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/file-check/</guid><description>File check Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link macOS, Windows, Linux WARP with Gateway All plans The File Check device posture attribute checks for the presence of a file on a device. You can create multiple file checks for each operating system you need to run it on, or if you need to check for multiple files.
&amp;#8203;​ Configure a file check In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client.</description></item><item><title>Firewall</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/firewall/</guid><description>Firewall Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link macOS, Windows WARP with Gateway All plans The Firewall device posture attribute ensures that a firewall is running on a device.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable the firewall check In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client. Scroll down to WARP client checks and select Add new.</description></item><item><title>OS version</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/os-version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/os-version/</guid><description>OS version Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link All WARP with Gateway All plans The OS Version device posture attribute checks whether the version of a device’s operating system matches, is greater than or lesser than the configured value.
&amp;#8203;​ Enable the OS version check In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Settings &amp;gt; WARP Client.</description></item><item><title>Require Gateway</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/require-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/require-gateway/</guid><description>Require Gateway Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link All systems WARP with Gateway All plans With Require Gateway, you can allow access to your applications only to devices enrolled in your organization&amp;rsquo;s instance of Gateway. Unlike Require WARP, which will check for any WARP instance (including the consumer version), Require Gateway will only allow requests coming from devices whose traffic is filtered by your organization&amp;rsquo;s Cloudflare Gateway configuration.</description></item><item><title>Require WARP</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/require-warp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/warp-client-checks/require-warp/</guid><description>Require WARP Feature availability Operating Systems WARP mode required Zero Trust plans External link icon Open external link All systems WARP with Gateway All plans This device posture attribute will check for all versions of WARP, including the consumer version. Cloudflare Zero Trust enables you to restrict access to your applications to devices running the Cloudflare WARP client. This allows you to flexibly ensure that a user&amp;rsquo;s traffic is secure and encrypted before allowing access to a resource protected behind Cloudflare Zero Trust.</description></item></channel></rss>