<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Basic tasks on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in Basic tasks on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage pools</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/create-pool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/create-pool/</guid><description>Manage origin server poolsA pool is a group of origin servers, with each origin identified by its IP address or hostname. For more background information on pools, refer to Origin pools.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a pool Dashboard API You can create a pool within the load balancer workflow or in the Origin Pools section of the dashboard:
Go to Traffic &amp;gt; Load Balancing.
Click Manage Pools.
Click Create.
For your pool, enter the following information:</description></item><item><title>Manage monitors</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/create-monitor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/create-monitor/</guid><description>Manage monitorsA monitor issues health checks at regular intervals to evaluate the health of an origin pool. When a pool becomes unhealthy, your load balancer takes that pool out of the server rotation. For more details about monitors, refer to Monitors.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a monitor Dashboard API Set up the monitor
You can create a monitor within the load balancer workflow or in the Monitors section of the dashboard:</description></item><item><title>Manage load balancers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/create-load-balancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/create-load-balancer/</guid><description>Manage load balancersA load balancer distributes traffic among origin pools according to pool health and its steering policy. Each load balancer is identified by its DNS hostname (lb.example.com, www.example.com, etc.). For more details about load balancers, refer to Load balancers.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a load balancer Dashboard API To create a load balancer in the dashboard:
Go to Traffic &amp;gt; Load Balancing.
Click Create Load Balancer.
On the Hostname page:</description></item><item><title>Enable Load Balancing</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/enable-load-balancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/how-to/enable-load-balancing/</guid><description> Enable Load BalancingLoad balancing is an add-on for your account, meaning your account needs a billing profile.
To enable Load Balancing External link icon Open external link in the dashboard:
Log in to your Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account and domain. Go to Traffic &amp;gt; Load Balancing. Select Enable Load Balancing. Choose your plan options and confirm payment.</description></item></channel></rss>