<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Migration on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/</link><description>Recent content in Migration on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Migrating from Wrangler 1</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/migrating-from-wrangler-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/migrating-from-wrangler-1/</guid><description>&amp;#8203;​ Migrate from Wrangler 1 This document describes the steps to migrate a project from Wrangler 1 to Wrangler 2.
Wrangler 2 ships with new features and improvements that may require some changes to your configuration.
The CLI itself will guide you through the upgrade process.
To learn more about the improvements to Wrangler, refer to the Comparing Wrangler 1 &amp;amp; 2 page. &amp;#8203;​ Update Wrangler version &amp;#8203;​ 1. Uninstall Wrangler 1 If you had previously installed Wrangler 1 globally using NPM, you can uninstall it with:</description></item><item><title>Deprecations</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/deprecations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/deprecations/</guid><description>DeprecationsThis document describes the difference between Wrangler 1 and 2, specifically deprecations and breaking changes.
Wrangler 2 introduces some new fields for configuration, while also deprecating some redundant fields.
&amp;#8203;​ Common deprecations Here are common fields that are no longer required.
type is no longer required. Wrangler will infer the correct project type automatically. zone_id is no longer required. It can be deduced from the routes directly. build.upload.format is no longer used.</description></item><item><title>Ejecting webpack</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/eject-webpack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/migration/eject-webpack/</guid><description>Migrate webpack projects from Wrangler version 1Previous versions of Wrangler offered rudimentary support for webpack External link icon Open external link with the type and webpack_config keys in wrangler.toml. Starting with Wrangler 2, Wrangler no longer supports the type and webpack_config keys, but you can still use webpack with your Workers.
As a developer using webpack with Workers, you may be in one of four categories:
I use [build] to run webpack (or another bundler) external to wrangler.</description></item></channel></rss>