<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Request Header Modification Rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/</link><description>Recent content in Request Header Modification Rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a rule in the dashboard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/create-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/create-dashboard/</guid><description>Create an HTTP Request Header Modification Rule in the dashboardCreate HTTP Request Header Modification Rules in the Transform Rules tab under Rules. Refer to Request header modification examples for examples of rule definitions.
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and website.
Go to Rules &amp;gt; Transform Rules.
Click Create transform rule &amp;gt; Modify Request Header.
Enter a descriptive name for the HTTP Request Header Modification Rule in Rule name.</description></item><item><title>Create a rule via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/create-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/create-api/</guid><description>Create an HTTP Request Header Modification Rule via APIUse the Rulesets API to create HTTP Request Header Modification Rules via API. Define the header modification configuration in the action_parameters field. Refer to Request header modification examples for examples of rule definitions.
When creating an HTTP Request Header Modification Rule via API, make sure you:
Set the rule action to rewrite. Define the header modification parameters in the action_parameters field according to the operation to perform (set or remove header).</description></item><item><title>Request header modification examples</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/rules/transform/request-header-modification/examples/</guid><description>Request header modification examplesThe following examples illustrate how to perform request header modifications with Transform Rules:
Add an HTTP request header with a static value Add an HTTP request header with the current bot score Remove an HTTP request header &amp;#8203;​ Add an HTTP request header with a static value The following HTTP Request Header Modification Rule adds a header named X-Source with a static value (Cloudflare) to the request:</description></item></channel></rss>