<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced TCP Protection on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced TCP Protection on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/setup/</guid><description>Advanced TCP Protection setupFollow the steps described in the following sections to get started with Advanced TCP Protection.
&amp;#8203;​ Step 1 – Request initial configuration When you get access to Advanced TCP Protection, there are no configured thresholds in your account.
Thresholds are based on your network&amp;rsquo;s individual behavior, derived from your traffic profile as monitored by Cloudflare. Defining the thresholds will effectively determine what the High, Medium, and Low sensitivities will be for your specific case.</description></item><item><title>Concepts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/concepts/</guid><description>Concepts &amp;#8203;​ Prefixes Advanced TCP Protection protects the IP prefixes you select from sophisticated TCP attacks. A prefix can be an IP address or an IP range in CIDR format. You must add prefixes to Advanced TCP Protection so that Cloudflare can analyze incoming packets and offer protection against sophisticated TCP DDoS attacks.
Prefixes added to Advanced TCP Protection must be one of the following:
A prefix onboarded to Magic Transit.</description></item><item><title>Rule settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/rule-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/rule-settings/</guid><description>Rule settingsEach rule type has the following settings: scope, mode, burst sensitivity, and rate sensitivity.
You may need to adjust the burst or rate sensitivity of a rule in case of false positives or due to specific traffic patterns.
&amp;#8203;​ Scope Advanced TCP Protection rules can have one of the following scopes:
Global: The rule will apply to all incoming packets. Region: The rule will apply to incoming packets in a selected region.</description></item></channel></rss>