<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/analytics/</guid><description>DDoS analyticsYou can view DDoS analytics in different dashboards, depending on your service and plan:
The Security Events dashboard provides you with visibility into L7 security events that target your zone, including HTTP DDoS attacks and TCP attacks.
The Network Analytics dashboard External link icon Open external link provides you with visibility into L3/4 traffic and DDoS attacks that target your IP ranges or Spectrum applications.
&amp;#8203;​ Availability Service Free Pro Business Enterprise WAF/CDN Activity log only Security Events Security Events Security Events Spectrum – – – Network Analytics Magic Transit – – – Network Analytics &amp;#8203;​ Remarks In some situations, the analytics dashboards will not show you the ID of the DDoS managed rule that handled a packet/request.</description></item><item><title>Reports</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/reports/</guid><description>DDoS reportsTo download an ad-hoc DDoS report, generate a PDF report file by selecting Print report in your analytics dashboard. WAF/CDN customers can download a weekly report by navigating to Account Home &amp;gt; Security Center, selecting Security Reports, and downloading the desired weekly report.
Additionally, if you are a Magic Transit or Spectrum BYOIP customer, you will receive weekly DDoS reports by email with a snapshot of the DDoS attacks that Cloudflare detected and mitigated in the previous week.</description></item><item><title>Alerts</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/alerts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/alerts/</guid><description>DDoS alertsConfigure notifications to receive real-time alerts (within ~1 minute) about L3/4 and L7 DDoS attacks on your Internet properties, depending on your plan and services. You can choose from different delivery methods.
Each notification email includes the following information:
Description Detection and mitigation time of attack Attack type Maximum rate of attack Attack target Notifications for HTTP DDoS alerts delivered through webhook or PagerDuty will also include the target hostname.</description></item><item><title>Logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/logs/</guid><description>DDoS logsRetrieve HTTP events using Cloudflare Logs to integrate them into your Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) systems.
Additionally, if you are a Magic Transit or a Spectrum customer on an Enterprise plan, you can export L3/4 traffic and DDoS attack logs using the Network Analytics logs. You can also export logs using the GraphQL API — for more information, refer to the Export GraphQL data to CSV tutorial.</description></item><item><title>Simulating test DDoS attacks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/simulate-ddos-attack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/reference/simulate-ddos-attack/</guid><description>Simulating test DDoS attacksAfter onboarding to Cloudflare, you may want to simulate DDoS attacks against your Internet properties to test the protection, reporting, and alerting mechanisms. Follow the guidelines in this section to simulate a DDoS attack.
You can only launch DDoS attacks against your own Internet properties — your zone, Spectrum application, or IP range (depending on your Cloudflare services) — and provided that:
The Internet properties are not shared with other organizations or individuals.</description></item></channel></rss>