<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Additional configuration on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/</link><description>Recent content in Additional configuration on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloudflare Tunnel</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/cloudflare-tunnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/cloudflare-tunnel/</guid><description>Route traffic through a Cloudflare TunnelCloudflare Tunnel (formerly Argo Tunnel) establishes a secure outbound connection which runs in your infrastructure to connect the applications and machines to Cloudflare.
For more details, refer to Route tunnel traffic using a load balancer.</description></item><item><title>Railgun</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/railgun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/railgun/</guid><description>Use a load balancer with RailgunRailgun is a web proxy system that allows dynamic content for a website — such as news sites or personalized content — to be cached while also allowing changes to the site to take effect almost instantly. Railgun is currently available to customers with a Business or Enterprise plan or via one of Cloudflare’s Optimised Partners.
By adding a load balancer to Railgun, you speed up connections between Cloudflare data centers and DNS origin servers so that uncacheable requests have minimal latency.</description></item><item><title>Spectrum</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/spectrum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/spectrum/</guid><description>Add load balancing to Spectrum applicationsYou can configure a load balancer to provide TCP healthchecks, failover, and traffic steering to bring resiliency to your Spectrum applications.
For more details, refer to Create a Spectrum application using a Load Balancer.</description></item><item><title>Perform planned maintenance</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/planned-maintenance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/planned-maintenance/</guid><description>Perform planned maintenanceWhen you change application settings or add new assets, you will likely want to make these changes on one origin server at a time. Going server by server reduces the risk of changes and ensures a more consistent user experience.
To take servers out of rotation gradually (important for session-based load balancing), enable origin drain on your load balancer. This option is only available for proxied load balancers (orange-clouded).</description></item><item><title>Containerized applications</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/deploy-containerized-applications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/deploy-containerized-applications/</guid><description>Deploy containerized applicationsCloudflare’s Load Balancer distributes global traffic intelligently across Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) and Amazon Web Services EC2 (AWS). Cloudflare’s native Kubernetes support provides a multi-cloud deployment that is transparent to end users.
For more details on implementation, refer to our Support Knowledgebase External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>Load shedding</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-shedding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/load-shedding/</guid><description>Load sheddingUse load shedding to prevent an at-risk origin from becoming unhealthy and starting the failover process.
Once you configure load shedding on a pool, that pool will begin diverting traffic to other pools according to your load shedding settings and the load balancer&amp;rsquo;s steering policy.
&amp;#8203;​ Step 1 — Identify at-risk origins Using your internal metrics, identify origins at risk of reaching their failure threshold.
If your origin is seeing increased traffic but is not yet at risk of failure, start with Step 2.</description></item><item><title>Override HTTP Host headers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/override-http-host-headers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/override-http-host-headers/</guid><description>Override HTTP Host headersWhen your application needs specialized routing (CNAME setup or custom hosts like Heroku), you can customize the Host header used in health checks on a per-origin or per-monitor level.
ImportantIf you set a header override on an individual origin, it will take precedence over a header override set on a monitor.
Also, if you configure an Origin Rule that overrides the hostname and set up a header override in your Load Balancer configuration, the Origin Rule will take precedence over the Load Balancer configuration.</description></item><item><title>Integrate with PagerDuty</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/pagerduty-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/pagerduty-integration/</guid><description>Integrate with PagerDutyTo integrate Cloudflare Health Check notifications with PagerDuty, follow the steps outlined in PagerDuty’s Email Integration Guide External link icon Open external link . If you do not have a PagerDuty account, you will first need to set that up.
PagerDuty will generate an email address that will create incidents based on emails sent to that address. For help locating that email address, refer to the PagerDuty documentation External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>Additional DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/additional-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/additional-options/additional-dns-records/</guid><description>Load balance additional DNS recordsIn addition to load balancing between DNS records used for IP resolution — A, AAAA, and CNAME records — Enterprise customers can also load balance between MX, SRV, and TXT records.
&amp;#8203;​ MX records To load balance between multiple mail servers:
Make sure you have the required DNS records for your mail servers. Create a monitor with a Type of SMTP. Create a pool with your mail servers and attach the newly created monitor.</description></item></channel></rss>