<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloudflare Images on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/</link><description>Recent content in Cloudflare Images on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Make your first API request</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/api-request/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/api-request/</guid><description>Make your first API requestTo make your first request to the Images API, you must obtain these pieces of information:
Your Cloudflare Account ID Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and website. In Overview, scroll down to find your Account ID. Your Global API Key or API Token To use Cloudflare Images you need to create a custom token with the correct Read and Update permissions:</description></item><item><title>Make an image private</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/make-an-image-private/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/make-an-image-private/</guid><description>Make an image privateYou can require an image to only be accessible with a signed URL token. To make an image private, pass a JSON blob with the requireSignedURLs property set to true at the time you request a one-time upload URL:
curl --request POST \ --url https://api.cloudflare.com/client/v4/accounts/&amp;lt;ACCOUNT_ID&amp;gt;/images/v1/direct_upload \ --header &amp;#39;Content-Type: application/json&amp;#39; \ --header &amp;#39;Authorization: Bearer &amp;lt;API_TOKEN&amp;gt;&amp;#39; \ --data &amp;#39;{ &amp;#34;requireSignedURLs&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;true&amp;#34; }&amp;#39; If an image is marked to require signed URLs, it can only be accessed using a signed URL token or using a Variant with Always allow public access property checked.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/images-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/images/cloudflare-images/images-analytics/</guid><description>Images analyticsCloudflare Images gives you access to analytics data for your account, such as:
How many images have been served during the current month. How many images are stored. Your account&amp;rsquo;s storage capacity. To check analytics for your Images account:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account. Select Images. Scroll down to Usage. &amp;#8203;​ Quota errors If you exceed your account&amp;rsquo;s quota, you will not be able to upload more images.</description></item><item><title>API reference</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>