<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Custom domain support on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/</link><description>Recent content in Custom domain support on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Verify custom hostnames</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/hostname-verification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/hostname-verification/</guid><description>Verify custom hostnamesCloudflare verifies ownership of each new hostname before traffic is allowed to proxy. There are four methods to verify ownership: TXT record, HTTP token, CNAME, or Apex.
If a custom hostname is already on Cloudflare, then traffic will only shift to your fallback origin once the DNS target has changed. &amp;#8203;​ CNAME &amp;#8203;​ Full setup Cloudflare iterates over the CNAME chain starting from the hostname. The value of the last CNAME must contain the domain that owns the custom hostname record.</description></item><item><title>Migrating custom hostnames</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/migrating-custom-hostnames/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/migrating-custom-hostnames/</guid><description>Migrating Custom HostnamesAs a SaaS provider, you may want, or have, multiple zones to manage hostnames. Each zone can have different configurations or origins, as well as correlate to varying products. You might shift custom hostnames between zones to enable or disable certain features. Cloudflare allows migration within the same account through the steps below:
&amp;#8203;​ CNAME If your custom hostname uses a CNAME record, add the custom hostname to the new zone and update your DNS record to point to the new zone.</description></item><item><title>Custom metadata</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/custom-metadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/custom-metadata/</guid><description>Custom metadataYou may wish to configure per-hostname (customer) settings beyond the scale of Page Rules or Rate Limiting, which have a maximum of 125 rules each.
To do this, you will first need to reach out to your account team to enable access to Custom Metadata. After configuring custom metadata, you can use it in the following ways:
Read the metadata JSON from Cloudflare Workers (requires access to Workers) to define per-hostname behavior.</description></item><item><title>Using a Worker as your origin</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/worker-as-origin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-for-platforms/cloudflare-for-saas/domain-support/worker-as-origin/</guid><description>Using a Worker as your originIf you are building your application on Cloudflare Workers, you can use a Worker as the origin for your SaaS zone (also known as your fallback origin).
In your SaaS zone, create and set a fallback origin, but use a &amp;ldquo;fake&amp;rdquo; proxied DNS record.
Example: service.example.com AAAA 100:: In that same zone, navigate to Workers.
Click Add route.
Decide whether you want traffic bound for your SaaS zone (example.</description></item></channel></rss>