<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Managed rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/</link><description>Recent content in Managed rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy in the dashboard for a zone</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/deploy-zone-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/deploy-zone-dashboard/</guid><description>Deploy a managed ruleset in the dashboard for a zoneYou can deploy and configure managed rulesets for a zone in Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Managed rules.
To deploy a managed ruleset for several Enterprise domains in your account, refer to Deploy a managed ruleset in the dashboard for an account.
&amp;#8203;​ Deploy a managed ruleset To deploy a managed ruleset with the default configuration, under Managed Rulesets select Deploy next to a managed ruleset.</description></item><item><title>Deploy in the dashboard for an account</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/deploy-account-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/deploy-account-dashboard/</guid><description>Deploy a managed ruleset in the dashboard for an accountYou can enable and configure managed rulesets for an account in Account Home &amp;gt; Application Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Managed rulesets.
Account-level WAF configuration requires an Enterprise plan with a paid add-on. To deploy a managed ruleset for a single zone, refer to Deploy a managed ruleset in the dashboard for a zone.
&amp;#8203;​ Deploy a managed ruleset Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account.</description></item><item><title>Deploy via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/deploy-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/managed-rules/deploy-api/</guid><description>Deploy managed rulesets via APIUse the Rulesets API to deploy managed rulesets at the account level or at the zone level.
Deploy WAF managed rulesets to the http_request_firewall_managed phase. Other managed rulesets, like DDoS Attack Protection managed rulesets, must be deployed to a different phase. Check the specific managed ruleset documentation for details.
You can define overrides to customize the behavior of the rules included in a managed ruleset.</description></item></channel></rss>