<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learning on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/</link><description>Recent content in Learning on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Queues Works</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/how-queues-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/how-queues-works/</guid><description>How Queues worksCloudflare Queues is a flexible messaging queue that allows you to queue messages for asynchronous processing. Message queues are great at decoupling components of applications, like the checkout and order fulfillment services for an e-commerce site. Decoupled services are easier to reason about, deploy, and implement, allowing you to ship features that delight your customers without worrying about synchronizing complex deployments. Queues also allow you to batch and buffer calls to downstream services and APIs.</description></item><item><title>Delivery guarantees</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/delivery-guarantees/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/delivery-guarantees/</guid><description>Delivery guaranteesDelivery guarantees define how strongly a messaging system enforces the delivery of messages it processes.
As you make stronger guarantees about message delivery, the system needs to perform more checks and acknowledgments to ensure that messages are delivered, or maintain state to ensure a message is only delivered the specified number of times. This increases the latency of the system and reduces the overall throughput of the system. Each message may require an additional internal acknowledgements, and an equivalent number of additional roundtrips, before it can be considered delivered.</description></item><item><title>Batching and Retries</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/batching-retries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/queues/learning/batching-retries/</guid><description>Batching and Retries &amp;#8203;​ Batching When configuring a consumer Worker for a queue, you can also define how messages are batched as they are delivered.
Batching can:
Reduce the total number of times your consumer Worker needs to be invoked (which can reduce costs). Allow you to batch messages when writing to an external API or service (reducing writes). Disperse load over time, especially if your producer Workers are associated with user-facing activity.</description></item></channel></rss>