<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Triggers on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/</link><description>Recent content in Triggers on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cron Triggers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/cron-triggers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/cron-triggers/</guid><description>Cron Triggers &amp;#8203;​ Background Cron Triggers allow users to map a cron expression to a Worker script using a ScheduledEvent listener that enables Workers to be executed on a schedule. Cron Triggers are ideal for running periodic jobs for maintenance or calling third-party APIs to collect up-to-date data. Workers scheduled by Cron Triggers will run on underutilized machines to make the best use of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s capacity and route traffic efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Custom Domains</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/custom-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/custom-domains/</guid><description>Custom Domains &amp;#8203;​ About Custom Domains Custom Domains allow you to connect your Worker to a hostname, without having to make changes to your DNS settings or do extra certificate management. Cloudflare will create DNS records and issue necessary certificates on your behalf. The created DNS records will point directly to your Worker.
&amp;#8203;​ Build a Custom Domain To create a Custom Domain, you must have:
An active Cloudflare zone.</description></item><item><title>Routes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/routes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/platform/triggers/routes/</guid><description>Routes &amp;#8203;​ Background Routes allow users to map a URL pattern to a Worker script to enable Workers to run in front of Custom Domains or their own application servers.
&amp;#8203;​ Customize your routes For zones proxied on Cloudflare, route patterns decide what (if any) script is matched based on the URL of that request. Requests are routed through a Workers script when the URL matches a route pattern assigned to that script.</description></item></channel></rss>