<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WARP modes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/warp-modes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/warp-modes/</guid><description>WARP modesThe WARP client has several modes to better suit different connection needs.
&amp;#8203;​ 1.1.1.1 1.1.1.1 is Cloudflare’s public DNS resolver. It offers a fast and private way to browse the Internet. It also offers a DNS encryption service through DNS over HTTPS (DoH) or DNS over TLS (DoT) for increased security and privacy.
Refer to 1.1.1.1 resolver to learn more about DNS encryption.
&amp;#8203;​ 1.1.1.1 with WARP The WARP application uses BoringTun External link icon Open external link to encrypt and secure the traffic from your device, and send it directly to Cloudflare’s edge network.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/privacy/</guid><description>PrivacyThe WARP Client application uses a VPN profile and/or service that enables us to intercept and secure your DNS queries and to transmit data from your device through the Cloudflare network, depending on the services you have enabled. We only collect limited DNS query and traffic data (excluding payload) that is sent to our network when you have the app enabled on your device. All information is handled in accordance with our Privacy Policy External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/known-issues-and-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/known-issues-and-faq/</guid><description>FAQBelow you will find answers to our most commonly asked questions regarding the WARP client. If you cannot find the answer you are looking for, refer to the community page External link icon Open external link to explore more resources.
&amp;#8203;​ Why am I not connecting to a closer Cloudflare data center? As our Network Map External link icon Open external link shows, we have locations all over the globe.</description></item></channel></rss>