<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User-side certificates on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/user-side-certificates/</link><description>Recent content in User-side certificates on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/user-side-certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install the Cloudflare certificate</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/user-side-certificates/install-cloudflare-cert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/user-side-certificates/install-cloudflare-cert/</guid><description>Install the Cloudflare certificateThis procedure is only required to enable specific Cloudflare Zero Trust features, and should only be done at the direction of your IT department. This procedure is not required to enable the WARP client for consumers. Installing the Cloudflare certificate allows you to apply HTTP policies to encrypted websites, display custom block pages, and more. If you are installing certificates manually on all of your devices, these steps will need to be performed on each new device that is to be subject to HTTP filtering.</description></item><item><title>Deploy a custom certificate</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/user-side-certificates/custom-certificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/user-side-certificates/custom-certificate/</guid><description>Deploy a custom certificateOnly available on Enterprise plans. Enterprise customers who do not wish to install the Cloudflare certificate have the option to upload their own root certificate to Cloudflare. Gateway will use your uploaded certificate to encrypt all sessions between the end user and Gateway, enabling all HTTPS inspection features that previously required the Cloudflare certificate. You can upload multiple certificates to your account, but only one can be active at any given time.</description></item></channel></rss>