<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enable</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/enable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/enable/</guid><description>Enable Version ManagementBy default, Version Management is not enabled on a zone.
To enable Version Management External link icon Open external link :
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link . Select your account and zone. Go to Version Management. Select Enable versioning. If you cannot enable Version Management, make sure your zone, account, and user meet the requirements. Once you enable Version Management, Cloudflare will automatically create Version 1 of your zone (along with a Baseline version), as well as environments for Production, Staging, and Development.</description></item><item><title>Manage environments</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/environments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/environments/</guid><description>Manage environmentsAn environment is a place to test different versions of your zone configurations. During the open beta, you can only interact with applications and versions using the Cloudflare dashboard. &amp;#8203;​ Create environment Once you enable Version Management, Cloudflare will automatically create Version 1 of your zone (along with a Baseline version), as well as environments for Production, Staging, and Development. Based on your organization&amp;rsquo;s needs, you may need to create additional environments to test and roll out changes.</description></item><item><title>Manage versions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/version-management/how-to/versions/</guid><description>Manage versionsA version is a collection of configuration settings related to your zone, such as Firewall Rules, Page Rules, and other optimization settings. During the open beta, you can only interact with environments and versions using the Cloudflare dashboard. &amp;#8203;​ Create version Once you enable Version Management, Cloudflare will automatically create Version 1 of your zone (along with a Baseline version), as well as environments for Production, Staging, and Development.</description></item></channel></rss>