<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Use IP Lists on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/</link><description>Recent content in Use IP Lists on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Work with lists</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/manage-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/manage-lists/</guid><description>Work with lists &amp;#8203;​ Create an IP List To create an IP List, follow these steps:
In the Lists interface, select Create new list.
Enter a name for your list, observing the following guidelines:
Use only lowercase letters, numbers and the underscore (_) character in the name. A valid name satisfies this regular expression:
^[a-z0-9_]+$ The maximum length for a list name is 50 characters.
Use a descriptive name for your list so that the list is informative in the context of a firewall rule expression.</description></item><item><title>Manage IP List items</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/manage-items/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/manage-items/</guid><description>Manage IP List items &amp;#8203;​ View items in an IP List Access the Lists interface available at Manage Account &amp;gt; Configurations &amp;gt; Lists.
Select Edit next to the list you want to view.
The list of items displays sorted by IP address, ascending:
NoteYou cannot download a list in CSV format from the dashboard. If you need to download the contents of a list to your device, use the Get lists operation to fetch them.</description></item><item><title>Use lists in expressions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/use-lists-in-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-dashboard/rules-lists/use-lists-in-expressions/</guid><description>Use lists in expressions &amp;#8203;​ Expression Builder To use an IP List in the Expression Builder:
Select is in list or is not in list from the Operator drop-down list.
Select an IP List from the Value drop-down list. Depending on your plan, you may be able to select an IP List managed by Cloudflare.
When you are done composing your rule, select Deploy to commit your changes and enable your rule.</description></item></channel></rss>