<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Phases</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/phases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/phases/</guid><description>PhasesA phase defines a stage in the life of a request where you can execute rulesets. Phases are defined by Cloudflare and cannot be modified.
Phases exist at two levels: at the account level and at the zone level. For the same phase, rules defined at the account level are evaluated before the rules defined at the zone level.
Currently, phases at the account level are only available in Enterprise plans.</description></item><item><title>Rulesets</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/rulesets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/rulesets/</guid><description>RulesetsA ruleset is an ordered set of rules that you can apply to traffic at the edge. Rulesets belong to a phase and can only execute in the same phase. To deploy a ruleset to a phase, add a rule that executes the ruleset to the phase entry point ruleset.
Rulesets are versioned. Each ruleset modification creates a new version of the ruleset. You can have several versions of a ruleset in use at the same time.</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/about/rules/</guid><description>RulesA rule defines a filter and an action to perform on the incoming requests that match the filter. The rule filter expression defines the scope of the rule and the rule action defines what happens when there is a match for the expression. Rule filter expressions are defined using the Rules language.
For example, consider the following ruleset with four rules (R1, R2, R3, and R4). For a given incoming request, the expression of the first two rules matches the request properties.</description></item></channel></rss>