<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/</link><description>Recent content in About on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Actions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/actions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/actions/</guid><description>Firewall rules actionsThe action of a firewall rule tells Cloudflare how to handle HTTP requests that have matched the rule expression.
&amp;#8203;​ Supported actions The table below lists the actions available in firewall rules. These actions are listed in order of precedence. If the same request matches two different rules which have the same priority, precedence determines the action to take.
For example, the Allow action takes precedence over the Block action.</description></item><item><title>IP Lists</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/rules-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/rules-lists/</guid><description>IP ListsUse IP Lists to refer to a group of IP addresses collectively, by name, in your firewall rule expression. You can create your own custom lists of IP addresses or use lists managed by Cloudflare.
For example, use a list of known office IP addresses in a firewall rule that allows requests from the addresses on the list to bypass security features. Or you may want to block requests that do not come from the known office addresses.</description></item><item><title>Order and priority</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/order-priority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/firewall/cf-firewall-rules/order-priority/</guid><description>Order and priority &amp;#8203;​ Overview Cloudflare Firewall Rules is part of a larger evaluation chain for HTTP requests, as illustrated in the diagram below. For example, Firewall Rules only evaluates requests that first clear IP Access rules. If a request is blocked by a rule at any stage in the chain, Cloudflare does not evaluate the request further.
Important You can use IP Access rules to allowlist requests under certain conditions, effectively excluding these requests from all security checks.</description></item></channel></rss>