<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account and billing on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/</link><description>Recent content in Account and billing on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Log into Cloudflare</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/login/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/login/</guid><description>Log into CloudflareTo log into the Cloudflare dashboard:
Go to the Login page External link icon Open external link . Choose your sign-in option. &amp;#8203;​ Sign-in options Cloudflare offers the following sign-in options:
Email and password: Enter your email address and password. Single sign on (SS0): Enter your email address (available if your admin has enabled SSO). Sign in with Apple: Same Cloudflare account email as Apple ID: You can either sign in with your email and password or sign in with Apple.</description></item><item><title>Non-contract services</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/non-contract-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/account-and-billing/non-contract-products/</guid><description>Non-contract servicesWith Cloudflare non-contract services, contracted customers can get full access to certain products and features, free of metered usage fees, limits, and certain other restrictions.
&amp;#8203;​ Available features and products To enable a non-contract service, use the Dashboard link in the following table. Then, select Enable. And that’s it! You will have instant access to the product or feature you selected so you can begin determining if it’s right for your business’ needs.</description></item></channel></rss>