<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configuration on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/</link><description>Recent content in Configuration on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration file</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/configuration-file/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/configuration-file/</guid><description>Configuration fileIf you are running quick tunnels, you do not need a configuration file. Configuring tunnels through a YAML file (what we refer to as a configuration file) allows you to have fine-grained control over how an instance of cloudflared will operate. In your configuration file you can specify top-level properties for your cloudflared instance, as well as configure origin-specific properties by writing ingress rules and adding parameters to them.</description></item><item><title>Ingress rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/ingress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/ingress/</guid><description>Ingress rulesEach incoming request received by cloudflared causes cloudflared to send a request to a local service.
To specify which local services a request should be proxied to, you can define ingress rules in your configuration file.
&amp;#8203;​ Requirements Configuration files that contain ingress rules must always include a catch-all rule that concludes the file.
In the following example, - service: http_status:404 serves as the catch-all rule for the file.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflared parameters</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/arguments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/install-and-setup/tunnel-guide/local/local-management/arguments/</guid><description>Cloudflared parametersThis page lists general-purpose configuration options for a Cloudflare Tunnel. You can add these flags to the cloudflared tunnel run command for remotely-managed and locally-managed tunnels. These flags can also be added to the configuration file for locally-managed tunnels.
Example: The following command runs the mytunnel tunnel by proxying traffic to port 8000 and disabling chunked transfer encoding.
cloudflared tunnel --url localhost:8000 --no-chunked-encoding run mytunnel config edge-ip-version autoupdate-freq no-autoupdate origincert metrics metrics-update-freq tag retries pidfile protocol logfile loglevel transport-loglevel &amp;#8203;​ config Syntax Default config value ~/.</description></item></channel></rss>