<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Properties reference</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/properties-reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/properties-reference/</guid><description>Properties referenceCloudflare Zaraz offers properties that you can use when configuring the product. They are helpful to send data to a third-party tool or to create triggers as they have context about a specific user&amp;rsquo;s browser session and the actions they take on the website. Below is a list of the properties you can access from the Cloudflare dashboard and their values.
&amp;#8203;​ Web API Property Description Track Name Returns the name of the event sent using the Track method of the Web API.</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/settings/</guid><description>Zaraz settingsTo configure Zaraz&amp;rsquo;s general settings, select Zaraz External link icon Open external link &amp;gt; Settings.
&amp;#8203;​ Workflow Allows you to choose between working in Real-time or Preview &amp;amp; Publish modes. By default, Zaraz instantly publishes all changes you make in your account. Choosing Preview &amp;amp; Publish lets you test your settings before committing to them. Refer to Preview mode for more information.
&amp;#8203;​ Web API &amp;#8203;​ Debug Key The debug key is used to enable Debug Mode.</description></item><item><title>Third-party tools</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/supported-tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/supported-tools/</guid><description>Supported toolsCloudflare Zaraz supports the following third-party tools:
Name Category Bing Advertising Branch Marketing automation Facebook Pixel Advertising Floodlight Advertising Google Ads Advertising Google Analytics Analytics Google Analytics 4 Analytics Google Conversion Linker Miscellaneous Google Maps - Reserve with Google Advertising / Miscellaneous HubSpot Marketing automation iHire Marketing automation / Recruiting Impact Radius Marketing automation Indeed Recruiting LinkedIn Insight Advertising Mixpanel Analytics Outbrain Advertising Pinterest Advertising Pod Sights Advertising / Analytics Quora Advertising Reddit Advertising Segment Customer Data Platform Snapchat Advertising Taboola Advertising Tatari Advertising TikTok Advertising Twitter Pixel Advertising Upward Recruiting ZipRecruiter Recruiting For any other tool, use the custom integrations below:</description></item><item><title>Triggers and rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/triggers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/zaraz/reference/triggers/</guid><description>Triggers and rulesTriggers define the conditions under which a tool will start an action. In most cases, your objective will be to create triggers that match specific website events that are relevant to your business. A trigger can be based on an event that happened on your website, like after selecting a button or loading a specific page.
These website events can be passed to Cloudflare Zaraz in a number of ways.</description></item></channel></rss>