<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SSO integration on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/</link><description>Recent content in SSO integration on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Generic SAML 2.0</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/generic-saml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/generic-saml/</guid><description>Generic SAML 2.0Cloudflare Zero Trust integrates with any identity provider that supports SAML 2.0. If your identity provider is not listed in the integration list of login methods on the Zero Trust Dashboard, it can be configured using SAML 2.0 (or OpenID if OIDC based). Generic SAML can also be used if you would like to pass additional SAML headers or claims for an IdP in the integration list.</description></item><item><title>SAML | Centrify</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/saml-centrify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/saml-centrify/</guid><description>SAML | CentrifyCentrify secures access to infrastructure, DevOps, cloud, and other modern enterprise so you can prevent the #1 cause of breaches – privileged access abuse.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up Centrify (SAML) To set up SAML with Centrify as your identity provider:
Log in to your Centrify admin portal and click Apps.
Select Add Web Apps.
Click the Custom tab.
Next to the SAML icon click Add.
Enter the required information for your application.</description></item><item><title>Azure AD®</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/azuread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/azuread/</guid><description>Microsoft Azure AD®You can integrate Microsoft Azure AD® (Active Directory) with Cloudflare Zero Trust and build rules based on user identity and group membership. Users will authenticate with their Azure AD credentials and connect to Zero Trust.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up Azure AD as an identity provider Log in to the Azure dashboard External link icon Open external link .
Click Azure Active Directory in the Azure Services section.
Navigate to Manage &amp;gt; App registrations and click + New registration.</description></item><item><title>SAML | OneLogin</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/onelogin-saml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/onelogin-saml/</guid><description>SAML | OneLoginOneLogin provides SSO identity management. Cloudflare Access supports OneLogin as an SAML identity provider.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up OneLogin (SAML) To set up OneLogin (SAML) as your identity provider:
Log in to your OneLogin admin portal.
Select Apps &amp;gt; Add Apps.
Under Find Applications, search for Cloudflare Access.
Select the result sponsored by Cloudflare, Inc. You can customize the name or logo.
Select Save. You can change this information at any time.</description></item><item><title>Workspace ONE</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/workspace-one/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/workspace-one/</guid><description>Workspace ONEDevice posture with Workspace ONE requires that the Workspace ONE agent and the Cloudflare WARP client are deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the check.
&amp;#8203;​ Obtain Workspace ONE Settings The following Workspace ONE values are needed to set up the Workspace ONE posture check:</description></item><item><title>SAML | Jumpcloud</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/jumpcloud-saml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/jumpcloud-saml/</guid><description>SAML | JumpcloudJumpCloud provides Directory-as-a-Service® External link icon Open external link to securely connect user identities to systems, apps, files, and networks. Cloudflare Access integrates with JumpCloud using the SAML protocol. This documentation from JumpCloud External link icon Open external link can help you configure applications within your JumpCloud deployment.
These steps focus on requirements specific to Cloudflare Zero Trust.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up Jumpcloud SAML To set up JumpCloud SAML as your identity provider:</description></item><item><title>SAML | Active Directory®</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/adfs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/adfs/</guid><description>SAML | Active Directory®Active Directory is a directory service developed by Microsoft for Windows domain networks. It is included in most Windows Server operating systems as a set of processes and services. Active Directory integrates with Cloudflare Access for using Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML).
&amp;#8203;​ Before you start To get started, you need:
An Active Directory Domain Controller where all users have an email attribute Generic SAML enabled for your Access Identity Provider (IdP) A Microsoft server running with Active Directory Federation Services (ADFS) installed.</description></item><item><title>PingFederate®</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/pingfederate-saml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/pingfederate-saml/</guid><description>PingFederate®The PingFederate® offering from PingIdentity provides SSO identity management. Cloudflare Access supports PingFederate as a SAML identity provider.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up PingFederate as an identity provider Log in to your Ping dashboard and navigate to Applications.
Click Add Application.
Select New SAML Application.
Complete the fields for name, description, and category.
These can be any value. A prompt displays to select a signing certificate to use.
In the SAML attribute configuration dialog select Email attribute &amp;gt; urn:oasis:names:tc:SAML:1.</description></item><item><title>PingOne®</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/pingone-saml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/pingone-saml/</guid><description>PingOne®The PingOne® cloud platform from PingIdentity provides SSO identity management. Cloudflare Access supports PingOne as a SAML identity provider.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up PingOne as an identity provider In your PingIdentity environment, navigate to Connections &amp;gt; Applications.
Click Add Application.
Enter an Application Name.
Select SAML Application.
Click Configure.
To fill in your Cloudflare Access metadata:
Select Import from URL. Set the Import URL to: https://&amp;lt;your-team-name&amp;gt;.cloudflareaccess.com/cdn-cgi/access/saml-metadata where &amp;lt;your-team-name&amp;gt; is your Cloudflare Zero Trust team name.</description></item><item><title>SAML | Citrix ADC</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/citrixadc-saml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/idp-integration/citrixadc-saml/</guid><description>SAML | Citrix ADCCloudflare Zero Trust can integrate with Citrix ADC (formerly Citrix NetScaler ADC) as a SAML IdP. Documentation from Citrix shows you how to configure Citrix ADC as a SAML IdP External link icon Open external link . These steps are specific to Cloudflare Zero Trust.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up Citrix ADC (SAML) To set up Citrix ADC (SAML) as your identity provider:
First, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to configure 2 SAML certificates:</description></item></channel></rss>