<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edge certificates on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/</link><description>Recent content in Edge certificates on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enforce HTTPS connections</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/encrypt-visitor-traffic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/encrypt-visitor-traffic/</guid><description>Enforce HTTPS connectionsEven with an active SSL/TLS certificate, visitors can still access resources over unsecured HTTP connections.
It is best to redirect this traffic over HTTPS, as well as ensure other resources (such as images) are also loaded over HTTPS.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Before trying to enforce HTTPS connections, make sure that your application has an active edge certificate. Otherwise, visitors will not be able to access your application at all.</description></item><item><title>Staging environment (Beta)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/staging-environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/staging-environment/</guid><description>Staging environment (Beta)Use your certificate staging environment to test new custom (modern) certificates before pushing them to your production environment. This process helps you solve potential certificate problems before there&amp;rsquo;s an incident, such as when:
You make a mistake when uploading a new custom certificate. You misunderstand the order of your certificates. Clients have previously pinned your custom certificate, causing a TLS termination error. &amp;#8203;​ Availability Free Pro Business Enterprise Availability No No No Yes(open beta) &amp;#8203;​ Use your staging environment &amp;#8203;​ Step 1 — Upload certificate To upload custom (modern) certificates to your staging environment:</description></item><item><title>Backup certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/backup-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/edge-certificates/backup-certificates/</guid><description>Backup certificatesIf Cloudflare is providing authoritative DNS for your domain, Cloudflare will issue a backup Universal SSL certificate for every standard Universal certificate issued.
Backup certificates are wrapped with a different private key and issued from a different Certificate Authority — either Google Trust Services or Sectigo — than your domain&amp;rsquo;s primary Universal SSL certificate.
These backup certificates are not normally deployed, but they will be deployed automatically by Cloudflare in the event of a certificate revocation or key compromise.</description></item></channel></rss>