<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/</link><description>Recent content in Access on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage Access policies</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/policy-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/policy-management/</guid><description>Manage Access policiesAccess policies are properties of applications. When setting up an Access application, you will be prompted to create at least one policy for the application. You can go back and create, edit, or delete policies at any time.
&amp;#8203;​ Create a policy To create an Access policy for an existing application:
In the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , navigate to Access &amp;gt; Applications.</description></item><item><title>Require Purpose Justification</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/require-purpose-justification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/require-purpose-justification/</guid><description>Require Purpose Justification after loginCloudflare Access allows security and IT teams to present users with a purpose justification screen directly after they log in to an Access application. This allows organizations to audit not only for who is accessing their resources, but also for why they are requesting access.
The purpose justification screen will show for any new sessions of an application. For example, if an Access application has a session time of eight hours, a user will see the purpose justification screen once every eight hours.</description></item><item><title>External Evaluation rules</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/external-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/external-evaluation/</guid><description>External Evaluation rulesWith Cloudflare Access, you can create Allow or Block policies which evaluate the user based on custom criteria. This is done by adding an External Evaluation rule to your policy. The External Evaluation selector requires two values:
Evaluate URL — the API endpoint containing your business logic. Keys URL — the key that Access uses to verify that the response came from your API After the user authenticates with your identity provider, Access sends the user&amp;rsquo;s identity to the external API at Evaluate URL.</description></item><item><title>Application paths</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/app-paths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/app-paths/</guid><description>Application pathsCloudflare Zero Trust allows you to create unique rules for parts of an application that share a root path. Imagine an example application is deployed at dashboard.com/eng that anyone on the engineering team should be able to access. However, a tool deployed at dashboard.com/eng/exec should only be accessed by the executive team.
When multiple rules are set for a common root path, the more specific rule takes precedence. For example, when setting rules for dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Enforce MFA</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/mfa-requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/mfa-requirements/</guid><description>Enforce MFAWith Zero Trust policies, you can require that users log in to certain applications with specific types of multifactor authentication (MFA) methods. For example, you can create rules that only allow users to reach a given application if they authenticate with a physical hard key.
This feature is only available if you are using the following identity providers:
Okta Azure AD OpenID Connect (OIDC) To enforce an MFA requirement to an application:</description></item><item><title>Temporary authentication</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/temporary-auth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/access/temporary-auth/</guid><description>Temporary authenticationWith Cloudflare Access, you can require that users obtain approval before they can access a specific application. The administrator will receive an email notification to approve or deny the request. Unlike a typical Allow policy, the user will have to request access at the end of each session. This allows you to define the users who should have persistent access and those who must request temporary access.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up temporary authentication On the Zero Trust dashboard External link icon Open external link , go to Access &amp;gt; Applications.</description></item></channel></rss>