<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Available integrations on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/</link><description>Recent content in Available integrations on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Box</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/box/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/box/</guid><description>BoxThe Box integration detects a variety of data loss prevention, account misconfiguration, and user security risks in an integrated Box account that could leave you and your organization vulnerable.
&amp;#8203;​ Integration prerequisites A Box account on a Business plan (Business, Business Plus, Enterprise, Enterprise Plus)
Access to a Box Business account with Admin permission
&amp;#8203;​ Integration permissions For the Box integration to function, Cloudflare CASB requires the following Box permissions via an OAuth 2.</description></item><item><title>GitHub</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/github/</guid><description>GitHubThe GitHub integration detects a variety of user security, data loss prevention, and misconfiguration risks in an integrated GitHub Organization that could leave you and your organization vulnerable.
&amp;#8203;​ Integration prerequisites A GitHub account with a Free, Pro, or Enterprise plan Membership to a GitHub Organization with Owner or GitHub App manager permissions &amp;#8203;​ Integration permissions For the GitHub integration to function, Cloudflare CASB requires the following GitHub API permissions:</description></item><item><title>Google Workspace</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/google-workspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/google-workspace/</guid><description>Google WorkspaceThe Google Workspace integration detects a variety of user security, data loss prevention, and misconfiguration risks in an integrated Google Workspace account that could leave you and your organization vulnerable.
&amp;#8203;​ Integration prerequisites A Google Workspace account with a Business Starter, Business Standard, Business Plus or Enterprise plan. Super Admin privileges External link icon Open external link in Google Workspace. &amp;#8203;​ Integration permissions For the Google Workspace integration to function, Cloudflare CASB requires the following Google API permissions:</description></item><item><title>Microsoft 365</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/microsoft-365/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/microsoft-365/</guid><description>Microsoft 365The Microsoft 365 (M365) integration detects a variety of user security, data loss prevention, and misconfiguration risks in an integrated Microsoft 365 account that could leave you and your organization vulnerable.
This integration covers Microsoft 365 products, including OneDrive and SharePoint.
&amp;#8203;​ Integration prerequisites A Microsoft 365 account with an active Microsoft Business Basic, Microsoft Business Standard, Microsoft 365 E3, Microsoft 365 E5, or Microsoft 365 F3 subscription. Global admin role External link icon Open external link or equivalent permissions in Microsoft 365.</description></item><item><title>Salesforce</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/salesforce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/salesforce/</guid><description>SalesforceThe Salesforce integration detects a variety of misconfiguration, data loss prevention, and user security risks in an integrated Salesforce environment that could leave you and your organization vulnerable.
&amp;#8203;​ Integration prerequisites A Salesforce environment (most editions are compatible).
Permissions to a Salesforce organization with either:
System Administrator permission Permissions for View Setup and Configuration, Customize Applications, and Modify All Data &amp;#8203;​ Integration permissions For the Salesforce integration to function, Cloudflare CASB requires the following Salesforce permissions via a Connected App:</description></item><item><title>Slack</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/slack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/applications/scan-apps/casb-integrations/slack/</guid><description>SlackThe Slack integration detects a variety of user security, data loss prevention, and misconfiguration risks in an integrated Slack Workspace that could leave you and your organization vulnerable.
&amp;#8203;​ Integration prerequisites A Slack user account Membership in a Slack Workspace (Free, Pro, Business+, or Enterprise Grid) If you are not the Workspace Owner and the Require App Approval setting is enabled for the Workspace, request permission External link icon Open external link to install apps.</description></item></channel></rss>