<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Partial (CNAME) setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Partial (CNAME) setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/setup/</guid><description>Set up a partial (CNAME) zoneA partial (CNAME) setup allows you to use Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s reverse proxy while maintaining your primary and authoritative DNS provider.
Use this option to proxy only individual subdomains through Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s global edge network when you cannot change your authoritative DNS provider.
A partial setup is only available to customers on a Business or Enterprise plan. &amp;#8203;​ Step 1 — Add your domain to Cloudflare Create a Cloudflare account and add your domain.</description></item><item><title>Convert to full setup</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/convert-partial-to-full/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/convert-partial-to-full/</guid><description>Convert partial setup to full setupIf you initially set up a partial domain on Cloudflare, you can later migrate it to a full setup.
&amp;#8203;​ Step 1 — Prepare Cloudflare SSL/TLS In the Cloudflare dashboard, either order an advanced certificate or upload a custom SSL certificate for your application.
You also should verify that the status of your SSL certificate is Active.
Universal SSL only supports first-level subdomains. For more coverage and additional flexibility, you can purchase an Advanced Certificate or upload a Custom SSL certificate.</description></item><item><title>DNS resolution</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/dns-resolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/partial-setup/dns-resolution/</guid><description>DNS resolution in partial zonesWhen you have a partial zone1, Cloudflare handles DNS records a bit differently from full zones in order to internally resolve the origin server where proxied HTTP requests are sent to.
&amp;#8203;​ Records within the same zone When you create a new DNS record in a partial zone, Cloudflare automatically checks whether any of your CNAME records point to existing A, AAAA, or CNAME records within the same zone.</description></item></channel></rss>