<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Common tasks on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/</link><description>Recent content in Common tasks on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Review Security Insights</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/review-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/review-insights/</guid><description>Review Security InsightsAfter enabling Security Insights and letting the first scan run, check the Security Insights tab for a list of detected insights that you should address.
For each detected insight, you can resolve it or archive it, after understanding its risks.
&amp;#8203;​ Resolve an insight Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Go to Account Home &amp;gt; Security Center &amp;gt; Security Insights.</description></item><item><title>Review the infrastructure</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/review-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/review-infrastructure/</guid><description> Review the infrastructureAfter enabling Security Insights and letting the first scan run, the Infrastructure tab displays an overview of the infrastructure associated with your Cloudflare account.
To open the Infrastructure tab, go to Account Home &amp;gt; Security Center &amp;gt; Infrastructure.
You can perform the following actions:
Filter the displayed information Print or download a PDF report</description></item><item><title>Start a new scan</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/start-scan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/security-center/tasks/start-scan/</guid><description>Start a new scanOnce you enable Security Insights, Cloudflare performs scans at a regular frequency, according to your Cloudflare plan.
Additionally, if your account has at least one Business or Enterprise zone, or if your account is on the Teams Standard or Teams Enterprise plan, you can manually start a new scan.
To manually start a scan:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account.</description></item></channel></rss>