<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edit videos on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/</link><description>Recent content in Edit videos on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add captions</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/adding-captions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/adding-captions/</guid><description>Add captionsAdding captions and subtitles to your video library.
&amp;#8203;​ Add or modify a caption To create or modify a caption on a video a Cloudflare API Token External link icon Open external link is required.
The &amp;lt;LANGUAGE_TAG&amp;gt; must adhere to the BCP 47 format External link icon Open external link . For convenience, the most common language codes are provided at the bottom of this document. If the language you are adding isn&amp;rsquo;t included in the table, you can find the value through the The IANA registry External link icon Open external link , which maintains a list of language codes.</description></item><item><title>Apply watermarks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/applying-watermarks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/applying-watermarks/</guid><description>Apply watermarksYou can add watermarks to videos uploaded using the Stream API.
To add watermarks to your videos, first create a watermark profile. A watermark profile describes the image you would like to be used as a watermark and the position of that image. Once you have a watermark profile, you can use it as an option when uploading videos.
&amp;#8203;​ Quick start Watermark profile has many customizable options. However, the default parameters generally work for most cases.</description></item><item><title>Clip videos</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/video-clipping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/edit-videos/video-clipping/</guid><description>Clip videosWith video clipping, also referred to as &amp;ldquo;trimming&amp;rdquo; or changing the length of the video, you can change the start and end points of a video so viewers only see a specific &amp;ldquo;clip&amp;rdquo; of the video. For example, if you have a 20 minute video but only want to share a five minute clip from the middle of the video, you can clip the video to remove the content before and after the five minute clip.</description></item></channel></rss>