<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Block file uploads to Google Drive</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-uploads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-uploads/</guid><description>Block file uploads to Google DriveYou can use Cloudflare Gateway and the Cloudflare WARP client application to prevent enrolled devices from uploading files to an unapproved cloud storage provider.
This tutorial covers how to:
Create a Gateway policy to block file uploads to a specific provider Enroll devices into a Zero Trust account where this rule will be enforced Log file type upload attempts Time to complete:
10 minutes</description></item><item><title>Block sites by host and URL</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-football/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-football/</guid><description>Block sites by host and URLYou can use Cloudflare Gateway and the Cloudflare WARP client to inspect HTTP traffic in order to block attempts to reach hostnames or to block URL paths without blocking the entire hostname.
In this mode, the Cloudflare WARP client runs on user devices and proxies all Internet-bound traffic to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network. Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network will then inspect the HTTP traffic to apply policies based on user identity and destination.</description></item><item><title>Block sites by TLD</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-tld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-tld/</guid><description>Block sites by TLDYou can use Cloudflare Gateway to block DNS queries a entire top level domain (TLD). These policies will block any hostname in a specific TLD.
This tutorial covers how to:
Build a policy in Gateway to block entire TLDs Time to complete:
5 minutes
&amp;#8203;​ Before you start Add Gateway to your account &amp;#8203;​ Build a policy to block by TLD Visit the Zero Trust dashboard. Open the Policies page in the Gateway section and select the DNS tab.</description></item><item><title>Block sites for specific users</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-football-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/block-football-users/</guid><description>Block sites for specific usersYou can use Cloudflare Gateway and the Cloudflare WARP client application to block attempts to reach hostnames or to block URL paths without blocking the rest of the hostname. You can build these rules globally for your entire organization or for specific users.
This tutorial covers how to:
Create a Gateway policy to block URLs that contain a hostname for a specific set of users Enroll devices into Gateway Review the block events in the Gateway logs Time to complete:</description></item><item><title>Configure a Hubspot account for Access for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/hubspot-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/hubspot-saas/</guid><description>Configure a Hubspot account for Access for SaaSThis tutorial covers how to set up Cloudflare as the SSO provider for Hubspot. Before you start, please note that Hubspot SSO typically requires an Enterprise license.
Time to complete: 15 minutes
&amp;#8203;​ Configure Hubspot Go to Settings &amp;gt; Account, and from there, navigate to Defaults &amp;gt; Security. Select Single Sign-on. Copy the values for Audience URI and Sign on URL. &amp;#8203;​ Configure Cloudflare Access On the Zero Trust Dashboard, navigate to Access &amp;gt; Applications and create a SaaS application.</description></item><item><title>Configure AWS SSO with Access for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/aws-sso-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/aws-sso-saas/</guid><description>Configure AWS SSO with Access for SaaSIn this tutorial we will configure AWS SSO with Access for SaaS. Cloudflare Access for SaaS allows you to layer additional network and device posture policies on top of existing identity authentication from your identity provider. In this example, we are using Okta as an identity provider, but any supported identity provider can be leveraged.
For this tutorial, you will need:
A Zero Trust account An integrated IdP Admin access to an AWS account Time to complete:</description></item><item><title>Configure local domains and split tunnel mode</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/split-tunnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/split-tunnel/</guid><description>Configure local domains and split tunnel modeYou can configure Cloudflare Zero Trust to exclude domains and IP addresses from being sent to the Cloudflare proxy. When excluded, domains will rely on local DNS resolution.
This walkthrough covers how to:
Manage the default lists of excluded domains and IP addresses Add a domain or IP address to the exclusion list Time to complete:
10 minutes
&amp;#8203;​ Configure domains to resolve locally You can configure domains to use the device&amp;rsquo;s local resolver.</description></item><item><title>Configure Zendesk SSO with Access for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/zendesk-sso-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/zendesk-sso-saas/</guid><description>Configure Zendesk SSO with Access for SaaSThis tutorial covers how to configure Zendesk SSO with Access for SaaS.
For this tutorial, you will need:
A Zero Trust Account An integrated identity provider (IdP) Admin access to your Zendesk account Time to complete:
20 minutes
&amp;#8203;​ Configure Zendesk and Cloudflare Navigate to your Zendesk administrator dashboard, typically available at &amp;lt;yourdomain&amp;gt;.zendesk.com/admin/security/sso.
In a separate tab or window, open the Zero Trust Dashboard External link icon Open external link , select your account, and go to Access &amp;gt; Applications.</description></item><item><title>Configure Zero Trust Network Access in Cloudflare Zero Trust</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/zero-trust-network-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/zero-trust-network-access/</guid><description>Configure Zero Trust Network Access in Cloudflare Zero TrustIn this tutorial we will cover how to configure a Zero Trust Private Network in Cloudflare Zero Trust by combining device enrollment rules, Cloudflare Tunnels, and identity-based network policies.
This tutorial covers how to:
Create device enrollment rules and connect a device to Zero Trust Connect your private network server to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge using Cloudflare Tunnels Create identity-aware network policies Time to complete:</description></item><item><title>Connect from WARP to a private network on Cloudflare using Cloudflare Tunnel</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/warp-to-tunnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/tutorials/warp-to-tunnel/</guid><description>Connect from WARP to a private network on Cloudflare using Cloudflare TunnelYou can use Cloudflare Tunnel to connect applications and services to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network. Cloudflare Tunnel relies on a piece of software, cloudflared, to create those connections.
You can create and configure Cloudflare Tunnel connections to support multiple HTTP origins or multiple protocols simultaneously. You can also use Cloudflare Tunnel to connect any service that relies on a TCP-based protocol to Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network.</description></item></channel></rss>