<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requirements</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/requirements/</guid><description> RequirementsReview the following requirements to install Railgun:
&amp;nbsp; Business and Enterprise Users Optimized Partners Hardware Dual core processor 4 GB RAM 64-bit Architecture Quad core processor 8 GB RAM 64-bit Architecture Software Memcache &amp;gt;= 1.4 with at least 512 MB of storage (&amp;gt;1 GB recommended) Memcache &amp;gt;= 1.4 with at least 1 GB of storage (&amp;gt;2 GB recommended) Operating System Debian 8, 9 Ubuntu Linux 12.04, 14.04, 16.04 Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6, 7 CentOS 6, 7 &amp;nbsp; Network Port 2408 open to traffic from our IPs &amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Railgun execution</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/railgun-execution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/railgun-execution/</guid><description>Railgun executionRailgun consists of two programs: rg-listener and rg-sender. rg-listener is to be installed at a hosting provider or end-user environment and listens for WAN connections. rg-sender is to be installed at Cloudflare locations and establishes connections across the WAN.
rg-sender acts as an HTTP proxy and accepts HTTP requests (with the CF-ORIGIN-IP and CF-WAN-ID headers) and sends them across the WAN to the rg-listener which then contacts the real web server.</description></item><item><title>Administration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/administration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/administration/</guid><description>AdministrationMultiple Railguns may be added to a Cloudflare account. Only one registered and activated Railgun may be used per domain.
Railgun can be load-balanced and multiple Railgun daemons can be used per activated public IP and token. There is no need to register each Railgun daemon.
&amp;#8203;​ Adding a Railgun Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account. Go to Manage Account &amp;gt; Configurations &amp;gt; Railgun.</description></item><item><title>Using Railgun with Origin CA Certificates</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/railgun-ca-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/railgun-ca-certificates/</guid><description>Using Railgun with Origin CA CertificatesWhile using Railgun and configuring Origin CA certificates, you will need additional steps to avoid service impact for HTTPS requests being sent from the listener to the site&amp;rsquo;s origin (where the origin CA certificates are installed). This happens because the default trust store shipped with the Railgun Listener is an identical copy of the root certificates that it trusts (identical to what NSS/Mozilla trusts).</description></item><item><title>Railgun and load balancers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/load-balancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/railgun/user-guide/load-balancer/</guid><description>Best practices for Railgun and a load balancerIf you are looking to use Cloudflare Railgun to optimize the load times of dynamic (non-cached) content and you currently use a load balancer, a firewall, or a NAT scheme in front of your application, review the following configurations and best practices associated with each setup.
&amp;#8203;​ Single origin, multiple web servers, single Railgun listener Cloudflare recommends installing the Railgun client (rg-listener) in front of the load balancer/firewall/NAT scheme, as shown in illustration above.</description></item></channel></rss>