<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Android</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/android/</guid><description>Android mobile clientBy default, 1.1.1.1:Faster Internet is configured to WARP mode. You can also configure it to only encrypt your DNS queries and leave the remaining traffic unencrypted.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up 1.1.1.1: Faster Internet Download 1.1.1.1: Faster Internet from Google Play External link icon Open external link for free. Launch 1.1.1.1: Faster Internet and accept the Terms of Service. Toggle the WARP button to Connected. Install the VPN profile that allows your phone to connect securely to 1.</description></item><item><title>iOS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/ios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/ios/</guid><description>iOS mobile clientBy default, 1.1.1.1:Faster Internet is configured to WARP mode. You can also configure it to only encrypt your DNS queries and leave the remaining traffic unencrypted.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up 1.1.1.1: Faster Internet Download 1.1.1.1: Faster Internet from the App Store External link icon Open external link for free. Launch 1.1.1.1: Faster Internet and accept the Terms of Service. Install the VPN profile that allows your phone to connect securely to 1.</description></item><item><title>Linux</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/linux/</guid><description>Linux desktop clientYou have two ways of installing WARP on Linux, depending on the distro you are using:
Find the latest WARP client. Package repository External link icon Open external link . APT/YUM repository External link icon Open external link . Install the cloudflare-warp package that suits your distro: apt-based OS (like Ubuntu): sudo apt install cloudflare-warp. yum-based OS (like CentOS or RHEL): sudo yum install cloudflare-warp. If you get an error message when trying to install via the terminal, download the package that suits your distro from the package repository External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>macOS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/macos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/macos/</guid><description>macOS desktop client Download Cloudflare WARP for macOS External link icon Open external link . Navigate to your predefined download folder and open the .pkg file. Follow the instructions to complete installation. Cloudflare WARP will automatically launch and appear in your menu bar with the Cloudflare logo. Select Next and Accept Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy. Turn on the toggle to enable WARP. WARP is now running and protecting your Internet connection.</description></item><item><title>Windows</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/warp-client/get-started/windows/</guid><description>Windows desktop client Download Cloudflare WARP for Windows External link icon Open external link . Navigate to your predefined download folder and open the executable file to install WARP. Follow the instructions to complete installation. Cloudflare WARP will automatically launch and appear in your menu bar with the Cloudflare logo. Select Next and Accept Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy. Turn on the toggle to enable WARP. WARP is now running and protecting your Internet connection.</description></item></channel></rss>