<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bypass WARP on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/exclude-traffic/</link><description>Recent content in Bypass WARP on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/exclude-traffic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Local Domain Fallback</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/exclude-traffic/local-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/exclude-traffic/local-domains/</guid><description>Configure Local Domain FallbackBy default, Cloudflare Zero Trust excludes common top level domains used for local resolution from being sent to Gateway for processing. These domains are resolved by the local DNS resolver configured for the device on its primary interface. Since these DNS requests bypass the Gateway resolver, they are not subject to Gateway DNS policies or DNS logging.
You can add additional domains to the Local Domain Fallback list and specify a DNS server to use in place of the Gateway resolver.</description></item><item><title>Split Tunnels</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/exclude-traffic/split-tunnels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-devices/warp/exclude-traffic/split-tunnels/</guid><description>Configure Split TunnelsSplit Tunnels mode can be configured to exclude or include IP addresses or domains from going through WARP. This feature is commonly used to run WARP alongside a VPN (in Exclude mode) or to provide access to a specific Tunnel (in Include mode).
Split Tunnel configuration only impacts the flow of IP traffic. DNS requests are still resolved by Gateway and subject to DNS policies unless you add the domains to your Local Domain Fallback configuration.</description></item></channel></rss>