<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage videos on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/</link><description>Recent content in Manage videos on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use webhooks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/using-webhooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/using-webhooks/</guid><description>Use webhooksWebhooks notify your service when videos successfully finish processing and are ready to stream or if your video enters an error state.
&amp;#8203;​ Subscribe to webhook notifications To subscribe to receive webhook notifications on your service or modify an existing subscription, you will need a Cloudflare API token External link icon Open external link .
The webhook notification URL must include the protocol. Only http:// or https:// is supported.</description></item><item><title>Manage creators</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/creator-id/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/creator-id/</guid><description>Associate videos with creatorsYou can set the creator field with an internal user ID at the time a tokenized upload URL is requested. When the video is uploaded, the creator property is automatically set to the internal user ID which can be used for analytics data or when searching for videos by a specific creator.
For basic uploads, you will need to add the Creator ID after you upload the video.</description></item><item><title>Search for videos</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/searching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/manage-video-library/searching/</guid><description>Search for videosYou can search for videos by name through the Stream API by adding a search query parameter to the list media files endpoint.
&amp;#8203;​ What you will need To make API requests you will need a Cloudflare API token External link icon Open external link and your Cloudflare account ID External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ cURL example This example lists media where the name matches puppy.</description></item></channel></rss>