<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Cloudflare?</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/what-is-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/what-is-cloudflare/</guid><description>What is Cloudflare?Cloudflare is a global network of edge servers External link icon Open external link .
When you add your application to Cloudflare, we use this edge network to sit in between requests and your origin server External link icon Open external link .
This position allows us to do several things — speeding up content delivery and user experience ( CDN External link icon Open external link ), protecting your website from malicious activity ( DDoS External link icon Open external link , Firewall External link icon Open external link ), routing traffic (Load balancing, Waiting Room), and more.</description></item><item><title>How Cloudflare works</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/how-cloudflare-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/how-cloudflare-works/</guid><description>How Cloudflare worksFundamentally, Cloudflare is a large network of servers that can improve the security, performance, and reliability of anything connected to the Internet.
Cloudflare does this by serving as a reverse proxy External link icon Open external link for your web traffic. All requests to and from your origin flow through Cloudflare and — as these requests pass through our network — we can apply various rules and optimizations to improve security, performance, and reliability.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare IP addresses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/cloudflare-ip-addresses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/cloudflare-ip-addresses/</guid><description>Cloudflare IP addressesCloudflare has several IP address ranges External link icon Open external link which are shared by all proxied hostnames.
Together, these IP addresses form the backbone of our Anycast network External link icon Open external link , helping distribute traffic amongst various edge network servers.
&amp;#8203;​ Allow Cloudflare IP addresses Because of how Cloudflare works, all traffic to your origin server will appear to be coming from Cloudflare IP addresses.</description></item><item><title>Accounts, zones, and profiles</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/accounts-and-zones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/accounts-and-zones/</guid><description>Accounts, zones, and profilesWithin the Cloudflare ecosystem, there are three organizing concepts that control where specific settings live: user profiles, accounts, and zones.
flowchart LR accTitle: Accounts contain zones and user profiles contain user settings subgraph Account subgraph Zone - example.com A[WAF] B[DNS] end subgraph Zone - example2.com C[Cache rules] D[Waiting Room] end Workers K[Account members] end subgraph User profile G[Email address] H[Language] I[Communication preferences] end &amp;#8203;​ User profiles Each user has a profile that contains several settings, such as Communication preferences and Language preferences.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare challenges</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/cloudflare-challenges/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/cloudflare-challenges/</guid><description>Cloudflare challengesWhen a website is protected by Cloudflare, there are several occasions when it will challenge visitor traffic:
The visitor&amp;rsquo;s IP address has shown suspicious behavior online (as tracked by Project Honeypot External link icon Open external link ). The website owner has blocked the country associated with the visitor&amp;rsquo;s IP address. The visitor&amp;rsquo;s actions have activated a firewall rule enabled by the website owner. If the visitor passes the challenge, their request is allowed.</description></item><item><title>Network Layers</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/network-layers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/fundamentals/get-started/concepts/network-layers/</guid><description> Network layersBelow is a list of the different layers that makes up the open systems interconnection (OSI) model External link icon Open external link and the associated Cloudflare products.
The list of related products is representative but not comprehensive. Network layer Protocol and related products 7 Application layer HTTP, DNS Authoritative DNS, CDN External link icon Open external link , Cloudflare Tunnel, Stream, Load Balancing, WAF, Bot Management 6 Presentation layer 5 Session layer 4 Transport layer TCP/UDP Spectrum, Argo Smart Routing, Load Balancing 3 Network layer IP, GRE, any packet/protocol Magic Transit, Magic Firewall, Magic WAN 2 Datalink layer Direct connection Cloudflare Network Interconnect (CNI) 1 Physical layer Direct connection Cloudflare Network Interconnect (CNI)</description></item><item><title>Reference architectures</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>