<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bot Management variables</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/bot-management-variables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/bot-management-variables/</guid><description>Bot Management variablesBot Management provides access to several new variables within the Firewall expression builder.
Bot Score: An integer between 1-99 that indicates Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s level of certainty that a request comes from a bot. Verified Bot: A boolean value that is true if the request comes from a good bot, like Google or Bing. Most customers choose to allow this traffic. For more details, see Traffic from known bots. Serves Static Resource: An identifier that matches file extensions for many types of static resources.</description></item><item><title>JavaScript detections</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/javascript-detections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/javascript-detections/</guid><description>JavaScript detectionsCloudflare&amp;rsquo;s bot products include JavaScript detections via a lightweight, invisible code injection that honors Cloudflare’s strict privacy standards External link icon Open external link . A small amount of JavaScript is injected into client devices using Google’s Picasso fingerprinting technique External link icon Open external link . Picasso results are factored into bot scores and help Cloudflare classify traffic as automated or human. BotScoreSrc: Not Computed and a score of 0 are relevant to Picasso JavaScript Fingerprinting requests.</description></item><item><title>Machine Learning models</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/machine-learning-models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/machine-learning-models/</guid><description>Machine Learning Models &amp;#8203;​ Enable Auto-updates to the Machine Learning Models Cloudflare allows Enterprise customers to enable Auto-updates to its Machine Learning models for the newest bot detection models as they are released.
To enable Auto-updates:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard and select your account and domain. Go to Security &amp;gt; Bots. Select Configure Bot Management. Enable Auto-updates to the Machine Learning Model. NoteIf you enable Auto-updates for the Machine Learning model, you will be upgraded to the latest version immediately.</description></item><item><title>Static resource protection</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/static-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/static-resources/</guid><description>Static resource protectionPro, Business, and Enterprise customers can use Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s bot solutions to protect their static resources from bots.
WarningIf you enable static resource protection, you may block good bots — like mail clients — that routinely fetch static resources. Make sure you understand your existing infrastructure before enabling this feature. &amp;#8203;​ Super Bot Fight Mode To enable this feature as a Pro or Business customer or an Enterprise customer without Bot Management:</description></item><item><title>Verified Bots Policy</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/verified-bots-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/verified-bots-policy/</guid><description>Verified Bots PolicyIn order to be listed by Cloudflare as a Verified Bot, your bot must conform to the below requirements. To provide the best possible protection to our customers, this policy may change in the future as we adapt to new bot behaviors.
&amp;#8203;​ Bot Policy &amp;#8203;​ Minimum Traffic A bot or proxy must have a minimum amount of traffic for Cloudflare to be able find it in the sampled data.</description></item><item><title>WordPress Loopback error</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/wordpress-loopback-issue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/bots/reference/wordpress-loopback-issue/</guid><description>WordPress Loopback errorCloudflare has observed that when users attempt to run diagnostics in the Site Status page for WordPress installations, loopback issues arise when our bot detection services block them.
In WordPress 6.0.1 with no additional plugins or themes, the page generated the following 3 requests:
Error Method URI User-Agent The REST API encountered an unexpected result GET /wp-json/wp/v2/types/post WordPress/6.0.1 &amp;lt; site-hostname &amp;gt; Your site could not complete a loopback request GET / WordPress/6.</description></item></channel></rss>