<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authorization cookie on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/</link><description>Recent content in Authorization cookie on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Validate JWTs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/validating-json/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/validating-json/</guid><description>Validate JWTsWhen Cloudflare sends a request to your origin, the request will include an application token as a Cf-Access-Jwt-Assertion request header and as a CF_Authorization cookie.
Cloudflare signs the token with a key pair unique to your account. You should validate the token with your public key to ensure that that the request came from Access and not a malicious third party.
&amp;#8203;​ Access signing keys The public key for the signing key pair is located at https://&amp;lt;your-team-name&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title>Application token</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/application-token/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/application-token/</guid><description>Application tokenCloudflare Access includes the application token with all authenticated requests to your origin. A typical JWT looks like this:
eyJhbGciOiJSUzI1NiIsImtpZCI6IjkzMzhhYmUxYmFmMmZlNDkyZjY0.eyJhdWQiOlsiOTdlMmFhZ TEyMDEyMWY5MDJkZjhiYzk5ZmMzNDU5MTNh.zLYsHmLEginAQUXdygQo08gLTExWNXsN4jBc6PKdB
As shown above, the JWT contains three Base64-URL values separated by dots:
Header Payload Signature Unless your application is connected to Access through Cloudflare Tunnel, your application must validate the token to ensure the security of your origin. Validation of the header alone is not sufficient — the JWT and signature must be confirmed to avoid identity spoofing.</description></item><item><title>CORS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/cors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/authorization-cookie/cors/</guid><description>Access and CORSCross-Origin Resource Sharing ( CORS External link icon Open external link ) is a mechanism that uses HTTP headers to grant a web application running on one origin permission to reach selected resources in a different origin. The web application executes a cross-origin HTTP request when it requests a resource that has a different origin from its own, including domain, protocol, or port.
For a CORS request to reach a site protected by Access, the request must include a valid CF-Authorization cookie.</description></item></channel></rss>