<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Steering policies on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/</link><description>Recent content in Steering policies on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Standard</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/standard-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/standard-options/</guid><description>Standard steering policiesStandard steering policies include Off - Failover and Random.
These are the only steering policies available to non-Enterprise customers who have not purchased Traffic Steering.
&amp;#8203;​ Off - Failover Failover steering uses the pool order to determine failover priority (the failover order).
Failover directs traffic from unhealthy pools — determined by health checks and the Health Threshold — to the next healthy pool in the configuration. Customers commonly use this option to set up active - passive failover.</description></item><item><title>Geo</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/geo-steering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/geo-steering/</guid><description>Geo steeringGeo Steering directs traffic to pools tied to specific countries, regions, or — for Enterprise customers only — data centers. This option is extremely useful when you want site visitors to access the origin server closest to them, which improves page-loading performance.
&amp;#8203;​ Pool assignment You can assign multiple pools to the same area and the load balancer will use them in failover order. Any options not explicitly defined — whether in data centers, countries, or regions — will fall back to using default pools and failover.</description></item><item><title>Dynamic</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/dynamic-steering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/dynamic-steering/</guid><description>Dynamic steeringDynamic Steering uses health check data to identify the fastest pool for a given Cloudflare Region or data center.
Dynamic Steering creates Round Trip Time (RTT) profiles based on an exponential weighted moving average (EWMA) of RTT to determine the fastest pool. If there is no current RTT data for your pool in a region or colocation center, Cloudflare directs traffic to the pools in failover order.
When enabling Dynamic Steering the first time for a server pool, allow 10 minutes for the change to take effect while Cloudflare builds an RTT profile for that pool.</description></item><item><title>Proximity</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/proximity-steering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/load-balancing/understand-basics/traffic-steering/steering-policies/proximity-steering/</guid><description>Proximity steeringProximity Steering routes visitors or internal services to the closest physical data center.
To use proximity steering on a load balancer, you first need to add GPS coordinates to each origin pool.
&amp;#8203;​ When to add proximity steering For new pools, add GPS coordinates when you create a pool. For existing pools, add GPS coordinates when managing pools or in the Add Traffic Steering step of creating a load balancer.</description></item></channel></rss>