<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Zone-scoped datasets on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/</link><description>Recent content in Zone-scoped datasets on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DNS logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/dns_logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/dns_logs/</guid><description>DNS logsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for dns_logs.
Field Value Type ColoCode IATA airport code of data center that received the request. string EDNSSubnet EDNS Client Subnet (IPv4 or IPv6). For more information refer to EDNS Client Subnet. string EDNSSubnetLength EDNS Client Subnet length. For more information refer to EDNS Client Subnet. int QueryName Name of the query that was sent. string QueryType Integer value of query type.</description></item><item><title>Firewall events</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/firewall_events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/firewall_events/</guid><description>Firewall eventsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for firewall_events.
Field Value Type Action The code of the first-class action the Cloudflare Firewall took on this request. Possible actions are unknown | allow | block | challenge | jschallenge | log | connectionclose | challengesolved | challengefailed | challengebypassed | jschallengesolved | jschallengefailed | jschallengebypassed | bypass | managedchallenge | managedchallengeskipped | managedchallengenoninteractivesolved | managedchallengeinteractivesolved | managedchallengebypassed. string ClientASN The ASN number of the visitor.</description></item><item><title>HTTP requests</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/http_requests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/http_requests/</guid><description>HTTP requestsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for http_requests.
Field Value Type BotDetectionIDs List of IDs that correlate to the Bot Management Heuristic detections made on a request. Available in Logpush v2 only. array[int] BotScore Cloudflare Bot Score. Scores below 30 are commonly associated with automated traffic. Available for Bot Management customers (please contact your account team to enable). int BotScoreSrc Detection engine responsible for generating the Bot Score.</description></item><item><title>NEL reports</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/nel_reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/nel_reports/</guid><description> NEL reportsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for nel_reports.
Field Value Type ClientIPASN Client ASN. int ClientIPASNDescription Client ASN description. string ClientIPCountry Client country. string LastKnownGoodColoCode IATA airport code of colo client connected to. string Phase The phase of connection the error occurred in; dns | connection | application | unknown. string Timestamp Timestamp for error report. int or string Type The type of error in the phase. string</description></item><item><title>Spectrum events</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/spectrum_events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/logs/reference/log-fields/zone/spectrum_events/</guid><description>Spectrum eventsThe descriptions below detail the fields available for spectrum_events.
Field Value Type Application The unique public ID of the application on which the event occurred. string ClientAsn Client AS number. int ClientBytes The number of bytes read from the client by the Spectrum service. int ClientCountry Country of the client IP address. string ClientIP Client IP address. string ClientMatchedIpFirewall Whether the connection matched any IP Firewall rules. UNKNOWN = No match or Firewall not enabled for spectrum; UNKNOWN | ALLOW | BLOCK_ERROR | BLOCK_IP | BLOCK_COUNTRY | BLOCK_ASN | WHITELIST_IP | WHITELIST_COUNTRY | WHITELIST_ASN.</description></item></channel></rss>