<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Additional options on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/</link><description>Recent content in Additional options on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create scheduled events</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/create-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/create-events/</guid><description>Create scheduled eventsWhen you want to customize the behavior of a waiting room for a specific period of time — such as changing the queueing method or increasing the total active users — set up a scheduled event. You can do this from the dashboard or via the API.
Any properties set on the event will override the default property on the waiting room for the duration of the event.</description></item><item><title>Embed in an iFrame</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/embed-waiting-room-in-iframe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/embed-waiting-room-in-iframe/</guid><description>Embed in an iFrameBecause of how a waiting room tracks visitor progress, you need to specify certain cookie attributes to properly embed a waiting room in an iFrame.
&amp;#8203;​ Background The SameSite attribute of a cookie External link icon Open external link specifies whether that cookie can be shared with other domains that load on the same page (ad banners, iFrames). By default, browsers do not send cookies on cross-site subrequests to prevent attackers from stealing or manipulating information present in your cookies.</description></item><item><title>Combine with SSL for SaaS</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/ssl-for-saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/ssl-for-saas/</guid><description>Combine with SSL for SaaSIf your application is using a custom hostname — meaning your SaaS provider is using SSL for SaaS — your application can support a waiting room.
&amp;#8203;​ Applications on Cloudflare If your application is already using Cloudflare, create a waiting room using the normal process.
&amp;#8203;​ Applications not on Cloudflare If your application is not using Cloudflare, you need to ask your SaaS provider to configure a waiting room on their SSL for SaaS zone (using your custom hostname as the Hostname value).</description></item><item><title>Test a waiting room</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/test-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waiting-room/additional-options/test-waiting-room/</guid><description>Test a waiting roomFollow this tutorial to test your waiting room behavior in response to load. To accurately simulate traffic through your waiting room with a load test, run your test script or planner for a period of time longer than a minute, ideally more than 2-3 minutes. You can run a load test using a variety of tools including loader.io External link icon Open external link , jmeter External link icon Open external link , and postman.</description></item></channel></rss>