<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add a prefix</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/add-prefix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/add-prefix/</guid><description>Add a prefix &amp;#8203;​ Before you start Cloudflare recommends that you switch any Advanced TCP Protection rules currently in mitigation mode to monitoring mode before adding a new prefix to Advanced TCP Protection. Refer to Rule settings for more information on execution modes.
To add a prefix to Advanced TCP Protection:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account.
Go to Account Home &amp;gt; Network Security &amp;gt; DDoS &amp;gt; Advanced TCP Protection.</description></item><item><title>Add an IP or prefix to the allowlist</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/add-prefix-allowlist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/add-prefix-allowlist/</guid><description>Add an IP address or prefix to the allowlistTo add an IP address or prefix to the Advanced TCP Protection allowlist:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Go to Account Home &amp;gt; Network Security &amp;gt; DDoS &amp;gt; Advanced TCP Protection. Under General settings &amp;gt; Allowlist, select Edit. Enter a prefix and (optionally) a description in Prefix and Description, respectively. To exclude the current prefix from the allowlist instead of including it, uncheck the Enabled checkbox.</description></item><item><title>Create a rule</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/create-rule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/create-rule/</guid><description>Create a ruleTo create a SYN flood rule or an out-of-state TCP rule:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account.
Go to Account Home &amp;gt; Network Security &amp;gt; DDoS &amp;gt; Advanced TCP Protection.
Depending on the rule you are creating, do one of the following:
Under SYN Flood Protection, select Create SYN flood rule. Under Out-of-state TCP Protection, select Create out-of-state TCP rule.</description></item><item><title>Exclude a prefix</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/exclude-prefix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ddos-protection/tcp-protection/how-to/exclude-prefix/</guid><description>Exclude a prefix or a prefix subsetTo exclude a prefix or a prefix subset from Advanced TCP Protection:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Go to Account Home &amp;gt; Network Security &amp;gt; DDoS &amp;gt; Advanced TCP Protection. Add the prefix you previously onboarded to Magic Transit to Advanced TCP Protection. Add the prefix (or subset) you wish to exclude as a new, separate prefix in Advanced TCP Protection.</description></item></channel></rss>