<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get started on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Get started on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DNS filtering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/dns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/dns/</guid><description>Set up DNS filteringSecure Web Gateway allows you to inspect DNS traffic and control which websites users can visit.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Connect to Gateway &amp;#8203;​ Connect devices To filter DNS requests from an individual device such as a laptop or phone:
Install the WARP client on your device. In the WARP client Settings, log in to your organization’s Zero Trust instance. (Optional) If you want to display a custom block page, install the Cloudflare root certificate on your device .</description></item><item><title>Network filtering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/network/</guid><description>Set up network filteringSecure Web Gateway allows you to apply policies at the network level (Layers 3 and 4) to control which websites and non-HTTP applications users can access.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Connect to Gateway &amp;#8203;​ Connect devices To filter network traffic from a device such as a laptop or phone:
Install the WARP client on your device. In the WARP client Settings, log in to your organization’s Zero Trust instance.</description></item><item><title>HTTP filtering</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/http/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/policies/filtering/initial-setup/http/</guid><description>Set up HTTP filteringSecure Web Gateway allows you to inspect HTTP traffic and control which websites users can visit.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Connect to Gateway To filter HTTP requests from a device:
Install the Cloudflare root certificate on your device . Install the WARP client on your device. In the WARP client Settings, log in to your organization’s Zero Trust instance. Enable the Gateway proxy: In the Zero Trust dashboard External link icon Open external link , navigate to Settings &amp;gt; Network.</description></item></channel></rss>