<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wrangler 1 (legacy) on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/</link><description>Recent content in Wrangler 1 (legacy) on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install / Update</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/install-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/install-update/</guid><description>Install / UpdateWrangler has launched a new version. This is documentation for Wrangler 1. Access the new Wrangler documentation by visiting the new Wrangler homepage. &amp;#8203;​ Install &amp;#8203;​ Install with npm $ npm i @cloudflare/wrangler -g EACCESS errorYou may have already installed npm. It is possible that an EACCES error may be thrown while installing Wrangler. This is related to how many systems install the npm binary. It is recommended that you reinstall npm using a Node version manager like nvm External link icon Open external link or Volta External link icon Open external link .</description></item><item><title>Authentication</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/authentication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/authentication/</guid><description>AuthenticationWrangler has launched a new version. This is documentation for Wrangler 1. Access the new Wrangler documentation by visiting the new Wrangler homepage. &amp;#8203;​ Background In Cloudflare’s system, a user can have multiple accounts and zones. As a result, your user is configured globally on your machine via a single Cloudflare Token. Your account(s) and zone(s) will be configured per project, but will use your Cloudflare Token to authenticate all API calls.</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/commands/</guid><description>CommandsWrangler has launched a new version. This is documentation for Wrangler 1. Access the new Wrangler documentation by visiting the new Wrangler homepage. Complete list of all commands available for wrangler External link icon Open external link , the Workers CLI.
&amp;#8203;​ generate Scaffold a Cloudflare Workers project from a public GitHub repository.
$ wrangler generate [$NAME] [$TEMPLATE] [--type=$TYPE] [--site] Default values indicated by =value.
$NAME =worker optional
The name of the Workers project.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/configuration/</guid><description>ConfigurationWrangler has launched a new version. This is documentation for Wrangler 1. Access the new Wrangler documentation by visiting the new Wrangler homepage. &amp;#8203;​ Background Your project will need some configuration before you can publish your Worker. Configuration is done through changes to keys and values stored in a wrangler.toml file located in the root of your project directory. You must manually edit this file to edit your keys and values before you can publish.</description></item><item><title>Webpack</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/webpack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/workers/wrangler/cli-wrangler/webpack/</guid><description>WebpackWrangler has launched a new version. This is documentation for Wrangler 1. Access the new Wrangler documentation by visiting the new Wrangler homepage. Wrangler allows you to develop modern ES6 applications with support for modules. This support is possible because of Wrangler&amp;rsquo;s webpack External link icon Open external link integration. This document describes how Wrangler uses webpack to build your Workers and how you can bring your own configuration.</description></item></channel></rss>