<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service providers on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/</link><description>Recent content in Service providers on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CrowdStrike</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/crowdstrike/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/crowdstrike/</guid><description>CrowdStrikeDevice posture with CrowdStrike requires the CrowdStrike agent and the Cloudflare WARP client to be deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the integration.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up CrowdStrike as a service provider &amp;#8203;​ 1. Get CrowdStrike settings The following CrowdStrike values are needed to set up the CrowdStrike posture check:</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Endpoint Manager</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/microsoft/</guid><description>Microsoft Endpoint ManagerCloudflare Zero Trust can integrate with Microsoft Endpoint Manager and Intune to require that users connect to certain applications from managed devices. Our service-to-service posture check identifies devices based on their serial numbers.
&amp;#8203;​ Prerequisites Device posture with Microsoft Endpoint Manager requires:
An Intune license Microsoft Endpoint Manager managing the device Cloudflare WARP client deployed on the device &amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain Microsoft Graph settings The following values are required:</description></item><item><title>Tanium</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/taniums2s/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/taniums2s/</guid><description>TaniumService-to-service device posture with Tanium requires the Tanium agent and the Cloudflare WARP client to be deployed on your devices. Unlike the previous Tanium with Cloudflare Access integration, this integration reads Tanium endpoint data via the WARP client. You can use either Tanium Cloud or on-premise installations of Tanium.
&amp;#8203;​ Set up Tanium as a service provider &amp;#8203;​ 1. Get Tanium settings The following Tanium values are needed to set up the Tanium posture check:</description></item><item><title>Uptycs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/uptycs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/uptycs/</guid><description>UptycsDevice posture with Uptycs requires that the Uptycs agent and the Cloudflare WARP client are deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the check.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain Uptycs Settings The following Uptycs values are needed to set up the Uptycs posture check:
Client key Client Secret Customer ID To obtain these values:</description></item><item><title>Workspace ONE</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/workspace-one/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/identity/devices/service-providers/workspace-one/</guid><description>Workspace ONEDevice posture with Workspace ONE requires the Workspace ONE agent and the Cloudflare WARP client to be deployed on your devices. For this integration to function, our service-to-service posture check relies on the serial_number being the same in both clients. Follow the instructions below to set up the posture check.
&amp;#8203;​ 1. Obtain Workspace ONE Settings The following Workspace ONE values are needed to set up the Workspace ONE posture check:</description></item></channel></rss>