<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work with managed rulesets on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/</link><description>Recent content in Work with managed rulesets on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy a managed ruleset</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/deploy-managed-ruleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/deploy-managed-ruleset/</guid><description>Deploy a managed rulesetYou can deploy a managed ruleset at the account level or at the zone level.
To deploy a managed ruleset to a phase, use the Rulesets API.
&amp;#8203;​ Deploy a managed ruleset to a phase at the account level Use the following workflow to deploy a managed ruleset to a phase at the account level.
Get your account ID. Get the ID of the managed ruleset you wish to deploy.</description></item><item><title>Override a managed ruleset</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-managed-ruleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ruleset-engine/managed-rulesets/override-managed-ruleset/</guid><description>Override a managed rulesetTo customize the behavior of a managed ruleset, override the ruleset at deployment. When you override a ruleset you specify changes to be executed on top of the default configuration. These changes take precedence over the ruleset&amp;rsquo;s default behavior.
For example, to test a managed ruleset before enforcing it, consider executing the ruleset with all rules set to log instead of their default actions. To do this, override the configured behavior of the managed ruleset at the ruleset level, so that each rule uses the log action.</description></item></channel></rss>