<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rate limiting rules on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/</link><description>Recent content in Rate limiting rules on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Determining the rate</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/request-rate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/request-rate/</guid><description>Determining the rateCloudflare keeps separate rate counters for rate limiting rules for each value combination of the rule characteristics.
Consider a rule configured with the following characteristics:
IP address HTTP header x-api-key In this case, two incoming requests with the same value for the HTTP header X-API-Key with different IP addresses are counted separately, since the value combination is different. Additionally, counters are not shared across data centers.
The counting model of this rate limiting rule is based on the number of incoming requests.</description></item><item><title>Create in the dashboard for a zone</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/create-zone-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/create-zone-dashboard/</guid><description>Create rate limiting rules in the dashboard for a zoneCreate rate limiting rules for a zone in Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Rate limiting rules.
For guidance on the previous version of rate limiting rules, refer to Configuring Cloudflare Rate Limiting External link icon Open external link .
&amp;#8203;​ Create a rate limiting rule To create a new rate limiting rule:
Log in to the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link , and select your account and domain.</description></item><item><title>Create in the dashboard for an account</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/create-account-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/create-account-dashboard/</guid><description>Create rate limiting rules in the dashboard for an accountAt the account level, you must first create a custom rate limiting ruleset, containing one or more rate limiting rules, and then deploy it to one or more zones on an Enterprise plan.
Both operations are available in the dashboard in Account Home &amp;gt; Application Security &amp;gt; WAF &amp;gt; Rate limiting rulesets.
Notes Account-level rate limiting configuration requires an Enterprise plan with a paid add-on.</description></item><item><title>Create via API</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/create-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/create-api/</guid><description>Create rate limiting rules via APIUse the Rulesets API to create a rate limiting rule via API.
For API guidance on the previous version of rate limiting rules, refer to the Cloudflare API documentation. A rate limiting rule is similar to a regular rule handled by the Ruleset Engine, but contains an additional ratelimit field with the rate limiting configuration. Refer to Rate limiting parameters for more information on this field and its parameters.</description></item><item><title>Rate limiting parameters</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/parameters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/parameters/</guid><description>Rate limiting parametersThe available rate limiting rule parameters are the following:
If incoming requests match String
Field name in the API: expression (rule field). Defines the criteria for the rate limiting rule to match a request. Choose action String
Field name in the API: action (rule field). Action to perform when the rate specified in the rule is reached. Use one of the following values: block, challenge, js_challenge, managed_challenge, or log.</description></item><item><title>Rule examples</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/use-cases/</guid><description>Rate limiting rule examplesThe examples below include sample rate limiting rule configurations.
&amp;#8203;​ Example 1 The following rule performs rate limiting on incoming requests from the US addressed at the login page, except for one allowed IP address.
Expression:
(http.request.uri.path eq &amp;quot;/login&amp;quot; and ip.geoip.country eq &amp;quot;US&amp;quot; and ip.src ne 192.0.0.1)
Rule characteristics:
Data center ID (included by default when creating the rule in the dashboard) IP Address &amp;#8203;​ Example 2 The following rule performs rate limiting on incoming requests with a given base URI path, incrementing on the IP address and the provided API key.</description></item><item><title>Best practices</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/best-practices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/waf/rate-limiting-rules/best-practices/</guid><description>Rate limiting best practicesThe following sections cover typical rate limiting configurations for common use cases. You can combine the provided example rules and adjust them to your own scenario.
The main use cases for rate limiting are the following:
Enforce granular access control to resources. Includes access control based on criteria such as user agent, IP address, referrer, host, country, and world region. Protect against credential stuffing and account takeover attacks.</description></item></channel></rss>