<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Proxy status</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/proxied-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/proxied-dns-records/</guid><description>Proxy statusThe Proxy status of a DNS record affects how Cloudflare treats incoming traffic to that record.
Cloudlare recommends enabling our proxy for all A, AAAA, and CNAME records.
&amp;#8203;​ Proxied records When an A, AAAA, or CNAME record is Proxied — also known as being orange-clouded — DNS queries for these will resolve to Cloudflare Anycast IPs instead of their original DNS target. This means that all requests intended for proxied hostnames will go to Cloudflare first and then be forwarded to your origin server.</description></item><item><title>DNS record types</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/dns-record-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/dns-record-types/</guid><description>DNS record typesThis page provides reference information about the different types of DNS records. For guidance on adding DNS records, refer to Manage DNS records.
&amp;#8203;​ IP address resolution At least one IP address resolution record is required for each domain on Cloudflare. These records are the only ones you can proxy through Cloudflare.
&amp;#8203;​ A and AAAA A and AAAA records External link icon Open external link map a domain name to one or multiple IPv4 or IPv6 address(es).</description></item><item><title>Time to Live (TTL)</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/ttl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/ttl/</guid><description>Time to Live (TTL)Time to Live (TTL) is a field on DNS records that controls how long each record is valid and — as a result — how long it takes for record updates to reach your end users.
Longer TTLs speed up DNS lookups External link icon Open external link by increasing the chance of cached results, but a longer TTL also means that updates to your records take longer to go into effect.</description></item><item><title>Record attributes</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/record-attributes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/record-attributes/</guid><description>Record attributesUse DNS record comments and tags to categorize and clarify the purpose of DNS records within Cloudflare.
Comments provide a unique descriptions for specific records, whereas tags group similar records into categories.
These attributes are particularly useful when:
Multiple teams are managing DNS records within the same zone. Your zone contains a large number of DNS records. You want to filter your DNS records based on matching attributes (for example, when they are managed by the same team or used for the same application).</description></item><item><title>Wildcard DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/wildcard-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/reference/wildcard-dns-records/</guid><description>Wildcard DNS recordsNormal DNS records map a domain name to one or multiple IP addresses or other associated resources to a specific domain name (a one-to-many mapping).
Wildcard DNS records allow you to have a many-to-many mapping, for example if you had hundreds or thousands of subdomains you wanted to point to the same resources. Wildcard records are used as the response for all subdomains that are not specifically covered by another DNS record.</description></item></channel></rss>