<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stream live video on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/</link><description>Recent content in Stream live video on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Start a live stream</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/start-stream-live/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/start-stream-live/</guid><description>Start a live streamYou can start a live stream using the Stream dashboard or the API. After you subscribe to Stream, you can create Live Inputs and begin sending your live video to Cloudflare Stream using RTMPS or SRT. SRT supports newer video codecs and makes using accessibility features, such as captions and multiple audio tracks, easier.
Stream only supports the SRT caller mode, which is responsible for broadcasting a live stream after a connection is established.</description></item><item><title>Add custom ingest domains</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/custom-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/custom-domains/</guid><description>Add custom ingest domainsWith custom ingest domains, you can configure your RTMPS feeds to use an ingest URL that you specify instead of using live.cloudflare.com.
Log in to your Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Click Stream &amp;gt; Live Inputs. Click the Settings button above the list. The Custom Input Domains page displays. Under Domain, add your domain and click Add domain. At your DNS provider, add a CNAME record that points to live.</description></item><item><title>Watch a live stream</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/watch-live-stream/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/watch-live-stream/</guid><description>Watch a live streamWhen an input begins receiving the live stream, a new video with HLS and DASH URLs is automatically created as long as the mode property for the input is set to automatic.
&amp;#8203;​ Use the API A live input can have multiple video UIDs associated with it. To get the video UID representing the current live stream for a given input, make a GET request to the /stream endpoint.</description></item><item><title>Download live stream videos</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/download-stream-live-videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/download-stream-live-videos/</guid><description>Download live stream videosYou can enable downloads for live stream videos from the Cloudflare dashboard. Videos are available for download after they enter the Ready state.
Log in to your Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link and select your account. Click Stream &amp;gt; Live Inputs. Click a live input from the list to select it. Under Videos created by live input, locate your video and click to select it.</description></item><item><title>Record and replay live streams</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/replay-recordings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/replay-recordings/</guid><description>Record and replay live streamsLive streams are automatically recorded, and available instantly once a live stream ends. To get a list of recordings for a given input ID, make a GET request to /live_inputs/&amp;lt;UID&amp;gt;/videos and filter for videos where state is set to ready:
--- header: Request --- curl -X GET \ -H &amp;#34;Authorization: Bearer &amp;lt;API_TOKEN&amp;gt;&amp;#34; \ https://dash.cloudflare.com/api/v4/accounts/&amp;lt;ACCOUNT_ID&amp;gt;/stream/live_inputs/&amp;lt;LIVE_INPUT_UID&amp;gt;/videos --- header: Response highlight: [10] --- { &amp;#34;result&amp;#34;: [ ... { &amp;#34;uid&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;6b6972f427f51793099c6b427783398e&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;thumbnail&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;https://customer-m033z5x00ks6nunl.</description></item><item><title>Simulcast (restream) videos</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/simulcasting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/simulcasting/</guid><description>Simulcast (restream) videosSimulcasting lets you forward your live stream to third-party platforms such as Twitch, YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, and more. You can simulcast to up to 50 concurrent destinations from each live input. To begin simulcasting, select an input and add one or more Outputs.
&amp;#8203;​ Add an Output using the API Add an Output to start retransmitting live video. You can add or remove Outputs at any time during a broadcast to start and stop retransmitting.</description></item><item><title>Receive Live Webhooks</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/webhooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/stream/stream-live/webhooks/</guid><description>Receive Live WebhooksStream Live supports webhooks that notify your service when an Input connects or disconnects to Stream Live.
&amp;#8203;​ Subscribe to Stream Live Webhooks Log in to your Cloudflare account and click Notifications. From the Notifications page, click the Destinations tab. On the Destinations page under Webhooks, click Create. Enter the information for your webhook and click Save and Test. To create the notification, from the Notifications page, click the All Notifications tab.</description></item><item><title>Stream Live API docs</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>