<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authenticated origin pull on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/authenticated-origin-pull/</link><description>Recent content in Authenticated origin pull on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/authenticated-origin-pull/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How authenticated origin pulls work</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/authenticated-origin-pull/explanation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/authenticated-origin-pull/explanation/</guid><description>How authenticated origin pulls work &amp;#8203;​ Simple explanation When visitors request content from your domain, Cloudflare first attempts to serve content from the cache. Failing that, Cloudflare sends a request — or an origin pull — back to your origin web server to get the content.
Authenticated origin pulls make sure that all of these origin pulls come from Cloudflare. Put another way, authenticated origin pulls ensure that any HTTPS requests outside of Cloudflare will not receive a response from your origin.</description></item><item><title>Set up authenticated origin pulls</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/authenticated-origin-pull/set-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/ssl/origin-configuration/authenticated-origin-pull/set-up/</guid><description>Set up authenticated origin pullsSet up authenticated origin pulls via one of the following options:
Zone-Level Authenticated Origin Pull using Cloudflare certificate Zone-Level Authenticated Origin Pull using customer certificates Per-Hostname Authenticated Origin Pull using customer certificates Authenticated Origin Pull does not work when your SSL/TLS encryption mode is set to Off or Flexible.
&amp;#8203;​ Zone-Level — Cloudflare certificate &amp;#8203;​ Certificate value Cloudflare uses a specific CA to sign certificates for the Authenticated Origin Pull service.</description></item></channel></rss>