<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/create-dns-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/create-dns-records/</guid><description>Manage DNS recordsWhen you add a new domain to Cloudflare, Cloudflare automatically scans for common records and adds them to your account&amp;rsquo;s DNS &amp;gt; Records page.
This scan is not guaranteed to find all existing DNS records, so make sure that all DNS records are added in the Cloudflare DNS &amp;gt; Records page before changing your nameservers to Cloudflare nameservers.
If you want more control over which DNS records are imported and how, use the bulk imports.</description></item><item><title>Import and export records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/import-and-export/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/import-and-export/</guid><description>Import and export recordsWhen you add a new domain to Cloudflare, Cloudflare automatically scans for common records and adds them to your account&amp;rsquo;s DNS &amp;gt; Records page.
This scan is not guaranteed to find all existing DNS records, so make sure that all DNS records are added in the Cloudflare DNS &amp;gt; Records page before changing your nameservers to Cloudflare nameservers.
If you want more control over which DNS records are imported and how, use the bulk import functionality.</description></item><item><title>Create root domain</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/create-root-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/create-root-domain/</guid><description>Create a root domain recordWhen you add a domain to Cloudflare, you may also need to create a DNS record for your root domain (example.com).
To do this, you would create a corresponding A, AAAA, or CNAME record for your root domain (specified by using @ for the Name).
Type Name IPv4 address Proxy status A @ 192.0.2.1 Proxied &amp;#8203;​ Domain redirects Once you create a domain, you may want to route that traffic to other places.</description></item><item><title>Create subdomain</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/create-subdomain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/create-subdomain/</guid><description>Create a subdomain recordMost subdomains serve a specific purpose within the overall context of your website. For example, blog.example.com might be your blog, support.example.com could be your customer help portal, and store.example.com would be your e-commerce site.
&amp;#8203;​ Subdomain records To create a new subdomain, you would first add the subdomain content at your host.
Then, you would create a corresponding A, AAAA, or CNAME record for that subdomain (blog, store).</description></item><item><title>Set up email records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/email-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/email-records/</guid><description>Set up email recordsThere are two reasons to set up email records for your domain: to make sure email reaches your mail server and to prevent other email senders from spoofing your domain.
&amp;#8203;​ Add MX records To route emails to your mail server, you need to create two DNS records within Cloudflare:
An A or AAAA record for your mail subdomain that points to the IP address of your mail server.</description></item><item><title>Use dynamic IP addresses</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/managing-dynamic-ip-addresses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/managing-dynamic-ip-addresses/</guid><description>Use dynamic IP addressesSome hosting providers dynamically update their customer&amp;rsquo;s IP addresses. These customers must then update the new origin server IPs in their Cloudflare DNS.
&amp;#8203;​ Cloudflare API Create a script to monitor IP address changes and then have that script push changes to the Cloudflare API.
&amp;#8203;​ ddclient ddclient External link icon Open external link is a third-party Perl client used to update dynamic DNS entries for accounts on various DNS providers.</description></item><item><title>Load balancing with DNS records</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/dns-load-balancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/manage-dns-records/how-to/dns-load-balancing/</guid><description>Load balancing with DNS recordsTo randomly distribute traffic across multiple servers, set up multiple DNS A or AAAA records for the same hostname.
Use this setup for simple, round-robin load balancing External link icon Open external link . If you need more fine-grained control over traffic distribution — including automatic failover, intelligent routing, and more — set up our add-on load balancing service.
&amp;#8203;​ Example scenario The following example illustrates how you would distribute traffic intended for www.</description></item></channel></rss>