<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Subdomain setup on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Subdomain setup on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/setup/</guid><description>Set up a child domainWhen using a subdomain setup, the steps to create a child domain depend on the parent domain&amp;rsquo;s setup and whether the child domain already exists.
flowchart TD accTitle: DNS resolution flow with CNAME target in same partial zone A[example.com] --> B[docs.example.com] A[example.com] --> C[blog.example.com] subgraph Parent domain A end subgraph Child domain B C end &amp;#8203;​ Available setups Parent zone Child zone Available Full or Secondary Full Yes Full or Secondary Secondary Yes Full or Secondary Partial No Partial Full Yes Partial Secondary Yes Partial Partial Yes &amp;#8203;​ Parent domain on full setup If the parent domain is using a full setup1, your child domain setup depends on whether the child domain already exists.</description></item><item><title>Migrate to new account</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/move-to-new-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/move-to-new-account/</guid><description>Migrate subdomain to a new accountWhen using a subdomain setup, you can have your child subdomain as a separate zone within the same account as the parent domain or within a different account.
If you have already created a standalone subdomain zone within the same account, you still can move it to a separate account.
Add the subdomain to a new Cloudflare account. Import all DNS records. Cloudflare recommends exporting records from the parent domain, deleting all unnecessary records, and then importing the records into your new zone.</description></item><item><title>Enable DNSSEC</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/dnssec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/dns/zone-setups/subdomain-setup/dnssec/</guid><description>Enable DNSSEC for a subdomain setupAs opposed to the normal process for enabling DNSSEC, DNSSEC with a subdomain setup requires a few additional steps.
&amp;#8203;​ Requirements In order to use DNSSEC for a subdomain setup, DNSSEC must be enabled on the parent zone.
Ideally, you should also wait 12 to 24 hours after enabling DNSSEC on the parent zone to ensure DNS resolvers provide the same DNS query responses.</description></item></channel></rss>