<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Zero Trust logs on Security365 Docs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/logs/</link><description>Recent content in Zero Trust logs on Security365 Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access audit logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/logs/audit-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/logs/audit-logs/</guid><description>Access audit logsCloudflare Access generates two types of audit logs:
Authentication audit logs maintain a record of authentication events. Per-request audit logs record HTTP requests to protected URI paths. &amp;#8203;​ Authentication audit logs Cloudflare Access logs an authentication event whenever a user or service attempts to log in to an application, whether the attempt succeeds or not.
Identity-based authentication refers to login attempts that matched on user email, IdP group, SAML group, or OIDC claim.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel audit logs</title><link>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/logs/tunnel-audit-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://panthere2k.github.io/cloudflare-one/analytics/logs/tunnel-audit-logs/</guid><description>Tunnel audit logsAudit logs for Tunnel are available in the account section of the Cloudflare dashboard External link icon Open external link which you can find by clicking on your name or email in the upper right-hand corner of the dashboard. The following actions are logged:
Action Description Registered This is logged when Tunnel is started and connects to the Cloudflare edge. Unregistered This is logged when Tunnel is disconnected from the Cloudflare edge.</description></item></channel></rss>